They just walked out of there.
Yeah, I know,
I was sort of sitting next to you.
The whole Waters family,
theyjust walked right out of there.
- Again, I was in the room.
- How do they always manage that?
They're good.
They're greedy and they'll do it again.
And next time, we're going to
catch them in the act.
How?
- No good?
- They always know we're coming.
- How do they always know?
They're good, they work at it.
- They're never going to stop.
- Well, neither are we.
- Greg.
- In the act!
The only way we're going to do this,
in the act!
You still blocking it?
Yeah, very efficiently hacked.
They must be bloody pleased
with themselves.
They must be.
Right, then.
Ah, no.
You go make the arrest.
This one's yours, boss.
You've never called me boss before.
No? Well, look what happens
when you're good.
You know how most days aren't good days?
- This is a good day.
- Not for the Waters family.
Okay, 10 men on the roof
All exits covered.
The bank's closed
so we've no hostages to worry about.
Sorry, no, go on, go on.
Um, we've got
the tunnel entrance covered
and Davis, Well and Christie
are heading up.
- Armed Response aren't mucking around.
Sorry, I'd better get this.
It's him, isn't it?
- I... I have to go.
- What?
- You make the arrest.
- No way.
Sorry, you'll be fine.
I'm cool with this.
Jones will get all the credit
if you leave now and you know he will.
Yeah, well... Yeah, it doesn't matter,
I'll have to go.
Backup, I need maximum backup.
Baker Street, now.
What's going on?
- This is hard.
- What?
Really hard.
Hardest thing I've ever had to do.
Do you know
any funny stories about John?
What?
I need anecdotes.
Didn't go to any trouble, did you?
- Shut up, Mrs Hudson.
- I haven't said a word.
You're formulating a question
and it's physically painful
watching you think.
I thought it was you playing.
It was me playing.
I am composing.
You were dancing.
- I was road-testing.
- You what?
Why are you here?
I'm bringing you your morning tea.
You're not usually awake.
You bring me tea in the morning?
Where do you think
it came from?
I don't know,
I just thought it sort of happened.
Your mother has a lot to answer for.
Mmm, I know. I have a list.
Mycroft has a file.
So, it's the big day, then.
What big day?
The wedding.
John and Mary are getting married.
Two people who currently who live
together are about to attend church,
have a party, go on a short holiday,
then carry on living together.
What's big about that?
It changes people, marriage.
Mmm, no, it doesn't.
Well, you wouldn't understand
'cause you always live alone.
Your husband was executed
for double murder,
you're hardly an advert
for companionship.
Marriage changes you as a person
in ways that you can't imagine.
As does lethal injection.
My best friend, Margaret,
she was my chief bridesmaid,
we were going to be
best friends forever,
we always said that.
But I hardly saw her after that.
Aren't there usually biscuits?
- I've run out.
- Have the shops?
She cried the whole day, saying,
Ooh, it's the end of an era.
I'm sure the shop on the corner is open.
She was probably right, really.
I remember she left early.
I mean, who leaves a wedding early?
So sad.
Mmm. Anyway, you've got things to do.
No, not really.
I've got plenty of time...
- Biscuits!
I really am going to have a word
with your mother.
You can if you like,
she understands very little.
Right, then.
Into battle.
Congratulations!
Okay, hold it there,
I want to get this shot
of the newlyweds.
Ah, just the bride and groom, please.
- Sherlock.
- Oh, sorry.
Okay. Three, two, one.
- Cheese.
The famous Mr Holmes.
I'm very pleased to meet you.
- But no sex, okay?
- Sorry?
You don't have to look so scared.
I'm only messing.
Bridesmaid, best man,
it's a bit traditional.
Is it?
But not obligatory.
If that's the sort of thing
you're looking for,
the man over there
in blue is your best bet.
Recently divorced doctor
with a ginger cat,
a barn conversion and a history
of erectile dysfunction.
Reviewing that information,
possibly not your best bet.
Yeah, maybe not.
Sorry, there was one more deduction
there than I was expecting.
Mr Holmes,
you're going to be incredibly useful.
Hello, lovely to meet you.
- How are you?
- Beautiful, Mary.
Thank you.
David.
Mary. Congratulations.
- You look, um, very nice.
- Thanks.
John, congratulations.
You're a lucky man.
Thank you.
Um, David, this is Sherlock.
- Mmm.
- Um, yeah, we've, um...
We've met.
So what exactly are my duties
as an usher?
Let's talk about Mary first.
- Sorry, what?
- Oh, I think you know what.
You went out with her for two years.
Ages ago.
We're just good friends now.
Is that a fact?
Whenever she tweets,
you respond within five minutes,
regardless of time or current location,
suggesting you have her on text alert.
In all your Facebook photographs
of the happy couple,
Mary takes centre frame,
whereas John is always partly
or entirely excluded.
Wait, you can't assume from that
that I've still got some kind of
interest in Mary?
You've volunteered to be
a shoulder to cry on
on no less than
three separate occasions.
Do you have anything
to say in your defence?
I think from now on we'll downgrade you
to casual acquaintance,
no more than three planned
social encounters a year
and always in John's presence.
I have your contact details.
I will be monitoring.
They're right about you.
You're a bloody psychopath.
High-functioning sociopath.
With your number.
Hello.
Thanks for coming, thank you.
Oh.
Yes, um, well done
in the service, Archie.
He's really come out of his shell.
I don't know how you did it.
Um...
Basically, it's a cute smile
to the bride's side,
cute smile to the groom's side
and then the rings.
- No.
- And you have to wear the outfit.
- You really do have to wear the outfit.
- What for?
- Grownups like that sort of thing.
Why?
I don't know. I'll ask one.
You're a detective?
Yep.
- Have you solved any murders?
- Sure, loads.
Can I see?
Yeah, all right.
What's all that stuff in his eye?
Maggots.
- Cool.
- Hmm.
He said you had some pictures for him
as a treat.
Er, yes, if he's good.
Beheadings.
Lovely little village.
Hmm? What did you say?
Hold it.
Nice.
- Vol-au-vent?
- I'm starving.
- Thanks.
- I had to lose so much weight
- to get into this dress.
Mmm. He's nice.
Traces of two leading
brands of deodorant,
both advertised for their strength.
Suggestive of a chronic
body odour problem
manifesting under stress.
Okay, done there.
What about his friend?
Long-term relationship.
Compulsive cheat.
- Seriously?
- Waterproof cover on the smartphone.
Yet his complexion doesn't indicate
outdoor work.
Suggests he's in the habit of taking
his phone into the shower with him,
which means he often receives texts
and emails he'd rather went unseen.
- Can I keep you?
- Do you like solving crimes?
Do you have a vacancy?
- So, Harry?
- Uh, no, no show.
Darling, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, it was a bit of a punt asking,
I suppose.
Still, free bar,
wouldn't have been a good mix.
Oh. God, wow.
- Is that...
- He came.
So that's him.
- Major Sholto.
- Uh-huh.
If they're such good friends,
why does he barely even mention him?
He mentions him all the time to me.
Never shuts up about him.
- About him?
- Mmm-hmm.
Ugh, I chose this wine.
It's bloody awful.
Yes, but it's definitely him
that he talks about?
Mmm-hmm.
I'm very, very glad to see you, sir.
I know you don't really
do this sort of thing.
Well, I do for old friends, Watson.
John.
- It's good to see you.
- You, too.
Civilian life suiting you, then?
Er, yes, well, I think so, sir.
No more need for the trick cyclist?
No, I go now and then.
Sort of a top-up.
Therapy can be very helpful.
Where are you living these days?
Oh, way out in the middle of nowhere.
You wouldn't know it.
You look well.
- I've never even heard him say his name.
Well, he's almost a recluse.
- You know, since...
- Yes.
I didn't think he'd show up at all.
John says he's the most unsociable man
he's ever met.
- He is? He's the most unsociable?
- Mmm.
Ah, that's why he's bouncing around him
like a puppy.
Oh, Sherlock.
Neither of us were the first, you know.
- Stop smiling.
- It's my wedding day.
Yes. What?
- Sherlock.
- Why are you out of breath?
Filing.
Either I've caught you
in a compromising position
or you've been working out again.
Favour the latter.
- What do you want?
- I need your answer, Mycroft,
as a matter of urgency.
- Answer?
- Even at the eleventh hour
it's not too late to know.
Oh, Lord.
Cars can be ordered,
private jets commandeered.
Today. It's today, isn't it?
No, Sherlock, I will not be coming
to the "night do",
as you so poetically put it.
What a shame.
Mary and John will be extremely...
Delighted not to have me hanging around.
Oh, I don't know.
There should always be a spectre
at the feast.
So, this is it, then? The big day.
I suppose I'll be seeing
a lot more of you from now on.
- What do you mean?
- It'll be just like old times.
No, I don't understand.
Well, it's the end of an era, isn't it?
John and Mary. Domestic bliss.
No, no, no. I prefer to think of it
as the beginning of a new chapter.
- What?
- Nothing.
I know that silence. What?
Well, I'd better let you get back to it.
You have a big speech
or something, don't you?
- What?
- Cakes. Karaoke.
- Mingling.
- Mycroft!
This is what people do, Sherlock.
They get married. I warned you.
Don't get involved.
Involved? I'm not involved.
- No.
- John asked me to be his best man.
- How could I say no?
- Absolutely.
- I'm not involved.
- I believe you.
Really, I do.
Have a lovely day
and do give the happy couple my best.
I will.
Oh, by the way, Sherlock.
Do you remember Redbeard?
I'm not a child any more, Mycroft.
No, of course you're not.
Enjoy not getting involved, Sherlock.
Pray silence for the best man.
Ladies and gentlemen,
family and friends.
And, um...
others.
- Uh...
Also...
- Greg.
- Molly.
I just had a thought.
Is that a brain?
What if John asks Sherlock
to be his best man?
- Well, he will. He's bound to.
- Exactly.
- So?
- So, he'll have to make a speech
in front of people.
There will be actual people there
actually listening.
Well, what's the worst
that could happen?
Helen Louise probably wondered the same.
Helen Louise?
Oh, hello, dear.
I was just thinking,
if John does ask Sherlock...
What, the speech, dear?
I know. It'll be fine.
It's not just the speech, though, is it?
Mrs Hudson?
- Oh, no, darling.
- You all right?
I was going to see Sherlock
and I thought you were....
- No.
...possibly dying.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
The telegrams.
- Sorry, what?
- Oh, sorry.
The telegrams.
Right, um...
- Mmm.
First things first.
Telegrams.
Well, they're not actually telegrams.
We just call them telegrams,
I don't know why.
Wedding tradition.
Because we don't have enough
of that already, apparently.
To Mr and Mrs Watson.
So sorry I'm unable to be with you
on your special day.
Good luck and best wishes,
Mike Stanford."
- Ah, Mike.
- Aw.
To John and Mary.
All good wishes for your special day.
With love and many big...
big squishy cuddles
from Stella and Ted."
- "Mary, lots of love..." Oh!
- Yeah?
- "...poppet."
Oodles of love
and heaps of good wishes from Cam.
Wish your family could have seen this.
- Hey, hmm?
- Yep.
Um..."Special day."
Very special day.
''L ove." "Love." "Love." "Love."
Love. Bit of a theme,
you get the general gist.
People are basically fond.
John Watson.
My friend, John Watson.
John.
When John first broached the subject
of being best man, I was confused.
- Sherlock?
- What was that noise downstairs?
Ah, it was Mrs Hudson laughing.
It sounds like she was torturing an owl.
Yeah, well it was laughter.
Could have been both.
- Busy?
Just occupying myself
Sometimes it's so hard not smoking.
Mind if I interrupt?
Oh, be my guest.
- Tea?
- Ah...
So.
- The big question.
- Mmm-hmm?
The best man.
- The best man?
- What do you think?
Billy Kincaid.
- Sorry, what?
- Billy Kincaid, the Camden Garrotter.
Best man I ever knew.
Vast contributions to charity
never disclosed.
Personally managed to save
three hospitals from closure,
and ran the best and safest
children's homes in North England.
Yes, every now and again
there would be some garrottings,
but stacking up the lives saved
against the garrottings,
- on balance I'd say...
- For my wedding.
For me. I need a best man.
Oh, right.
- Maybe not a garrotter.
- Gavin?
- Who?
- Gavin Lestrade.
He's a man and good at it.
It's Greg.
And he's not my best friend.
Oh, Mike Stanford, I see.
Well, he's nice, um...
Though I'm not sure
how well he'd cope with...
No, Mike's great,
but he's not my best friend.
Look, Sherlock, this is the biggest
and most important day of my life.
- Well...
- No, it is. It is.
And I want to be up there
with the two people
that I love and care about
- most in the world.
- Yes.
- Mary Morstan...
...and...
you.
I confess at first I didn't realise
he was asking me.
When finally I understood,
I expressed to him that I was
both flattered and surprised.
I explained to him that
I had never expected this request
and I was a little daunted
in the face of it.
Sherlock?
I nonetheless promised that I would do
my very best to accomplish a task
which was, for me,
as demanding and difficult
as any I had ever contemplated.
Additionally, I thanked him
for the trust he placed in me
and indicated that I was, in some ways,
very close to being moved by it.
No, it's getting a bit scary now.
It later transpired that I'd said
none of this out aloud.
So, in fact...
- You-you mean...
- Yes.
I'm your... best...
- Man.
...friend?
Yeah, of course you are.
Course you're my best friend.
Well, how was that?
Surprisingly okay.
So you'll have to make a speech,
of course.
So...
Done that. Done that.
Done that bit. Done that bit.
Done that bit.
I'm afraid, John,
I can't congratulate you.
All emotions, and in particular love,
stand opposed to the pure cold reason
I hold above all things.
A wedding is, in my considered opinion,
nothing short of a celebration of
all that is false and specious
and irrational and sentimental
in this ailing
and morally compromised world.
Today we honour the deathwatch beetle
that is the doom of our society
and in time, one feels certain,
our entire species.
But anyway, let's talk about John.
Please.
If I burden myself with
a little helpmate during my adventures,
it is not out of sentiment or caprice,
it is that he has many
fine qualities of his own
that he has overlooked
in his obsession with me.
Indeed, any reputation I have
for mental acuity and sharpness
comes in truth from
the extraordinary contrast
John so selflessly provides.
It is a fact, I believe,
that brides tend to favour
exceptionally plain bridesmaids
for their big day.
There is a certain
analogy there, I feel.
And contrast is, after all,
God's own plan to enhance
the beauty of his creation.
Or it would be if God were not
a ludicrous fantasy
designed to provide a career opportunity
for the family idiot.
The point I'm trying to make
is that I am
the most unpleasant, rude, ignorant
and all-round obnoxious arsehole
that anyone could possibly have
the misfortune to meet.
I am dismissive of the virtuous,
unaware of the beautiful,
and uncomprehending
in the face of the happy.
So if I didn't understand
I was being asked to be best man,
it is because I never expected to be
anybody's best friend.
And certainly not the best friend
of the bravest and kindest
and wisest human being
I have ever had the good fortune
of knowing.
Aw.
John, I am a ridiculous man.
Redeemed only by the warmth
and constancy of your friendship.
But as I am, apparently,
your best friend,
I cannot congratulate you
on your choice of companion.
Actually, now I can.
Mary, when I say you deserve this man,
it is the highest compliment
of which I am capable.
John, you have endured war
and injury
and tragic loss.
So sorry again about that last one.
So know this. Today you sit between
the woman you have made your wife
and the man you have saved.
In short, the two people who
love you most in all this world.
And I know I speak for Mary as well
when I say we will never let you down
and we have a lifetime ahead
to prove that.
- Lf I try and hug him, stop me.
- Certainly not.
Ah, yes. Now onto some
funny stories about John.
What's wrong? What happened?
Why are you all doing that?
John?
Oh, Sherlock.
Did I do it wrong?
No, you didn't. Come here.
- I haven't finished yet.
- Yeah, I know. I know.
- So onto some funny stories...
- Can you wait till I sit down?
So onto some funny stories about John.
If you could all just cheer up a bit,
that would...
...be better.
On we go.
So for funny stories, one has to look
no further than John's blog.
The record of our time together.
Of course, he does tend to romanticise
things a bit but then, you know,
he's a romantic.
We've tackled some strange cases.
The Hollow Client.
The Poisoned Giant.
Get down, John!
We've had some frustrating cases.
What is that?
A French decathlete
found completely out of his mind
surrounded by 1,812 matchboxes,
all empty, except this one.
And what's in that one?
The inexplicable.
Touching cases.
She's going to ring the doorbell.
Oh, no, she's changed her mind.
No, she's going to do it.
No, she's leaving.
She's leaving.
Oh, she's coming back.
She's a client, she's boring.
I've seen those symptoms before.
Hmm?
Oscillation on the pavement
always means there's a love affair.
And of course, I have to mention
The Elephant in the Room.
But we want something very particular
for this special day, don't we?
The Bloody Guardsman.
Need to work on your half
of the church, Mary.
- Looking a bit thin.
- Oh.
Orphan's lot.
Friends, that's all I have.
Lots of friends.
Schedule the organ music
to begin at precisely 11:48...
But the rehearsal's not for
another two weeks. Just calm down.
Calm? I am calm, I'm extremely calm.
Let's get back to the reception.
Come on.
John's cousin, top table?
Hmm, hates you.
Can't even bear to think about you.
- Seriously?
- Second-class post.
Cheap card.
Bought at a petrol station.
Look at the stamp.
Three attempts at licking.
She's obviously unconsciously
retaining saliva.
Aw, let's stick her by the bogs.
- Oh, yes.
Who else hates me?
Oh, great. Thanks.
Priceless painting nicked.
Looks interesting.
- Table four?
- Done.
My husband is three people.
- Table five?
- Major James Sholto. Who he?
Oh, John's old commanding officer.
I don't think he's coming.
He'll be there.
- Well, he needs to RSVP, then.
My husband is three people.
It's interesting.
Says he has three distinct patterns
of moles on his skin.
Identical triplets.
One in half a million births.
Solved it without leaving the flat.
Now, serviettes.
Swan or Sydney Opera House?
Where did you learn to do that?
Many unexpected skills required
in the field of criminal investigation.
- Fibbing, Sherlock.
- I once broke an alibi
by demonstrating
the exact severity of...
I'm not John.
I can tell when you're fibbing.
Okay. I learnt it on YouTube.
Opera House, please.
Oh, hang on. I'm buzzing.
Hello?
Oh, hi, Beth.
Yeah, yeah, I don't see why not.
Actually, if that's Beth,
it's probably for me, too. Hang on.
He knows we don't have
a friend called Beth.
He's going to figure out that it's code.
- He's YouTubing serviettes.
- He's thorough.
- He's terrified.
- Of course he's not.
Right, you know when you're
scared of something,
you start wishing it sooner
just to get it all going?
That's what he's doing.
Why would he be scared
that we're getting married?
It's not going to change anything.
We'll still do stuff.
We need to prove it to him.
I told you to find him a new case.
- I'm trying.
- You need to run him, okay?
Show him it's still the good old days.
That just sort of happened.
Sherlock, um...
mate.
I've....
I've smelled
18 different perfumes.
I've sampled
nine different slices of cake,
which all tasted identical.
I like the bridesmaids in purple.
- Lilac.
Um, there are no more decisions
left to make.
I don't even understand the decisions
that we have made.
I'm faking opinions and it's exhausting.
So please, before she comes back...
.... Pick something.
- Anything, pick one.
- Pick what?
A case.
Your inbox is bursting. Just...
get me out of here.
You want to go out on a case? Now?
Please.
Sherlock, for me.
Don't you worry about anything.
I'll get you out of this.
Oh.
Dear, Mr Holmes, my name is Bainbridge.
I'm a private in
Her Majesty's Household Guard.
I'm writing to you
about a personal matter,
one I don't care to bring
before my superiors,
it would sound so trivial.
But I think someone's stalking me.
I'm used to tourists,
it's part of the job.
But this is different.
Someone's watching me.
He's taking pictures of me every day.
I don't want to mention it
to the manager
but it's really preying on my mind.
Uniform fetishist.
All the nice girls like a soldier.
It's sailor.
And Bainbridge thinks
his stalker is a bloke.
Let's go and investigate.
- Please?
- Elite guard.
Forty enlisted men and officers.
Why this particular grenadier? Curious.
- Now you're talking.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Uh, we're just going to...
I need, um, Sherlock to help me
choose some....
- Tie.
...socks.
- Why don't we go with socks?
- Yeah.
I mean, you've got to get
the right ones.
Exactly. To go with my...
- Tie.
...outfit.
Well, it'll take a while,
right?
- My coat in there?
- Yes.
Just going to take him out for a bit.
- Run him.
- I know.
You said you'd find him a case.
- Coming, Sherlock?
- Coming.
Taxi!
Company, halt!
Right turn!
We're here to see
Private Steven Bainbridge.
He's on duty right now, sir.
I'll certainly let him know
when he's free.
And when will that be?
Another hour.
You think
they give them classes?
Classes?
How to resist the temptation
to scratch their behinds.
Afferent neurons
in the peripheral nervous system.
- Bum itch.
- Oh.
So why don't you see him any more?
- Who?
- Your previous commander, Sholto.
- Previous commander?
- I meant ex.
Previous suggests that
I currently have a commander.
- Which you don't.
- Which I don't.
Of course you don't.
He was decorated, wasn't he?
- A war hero.
- Not to everyone.
He led a team of crows into battle.
- Crows?
- New recruits.
It's standard procedure,
break the new boys in,
but it went wrong.
They all died.
He was the only survivor.
The press and the families
gave him hell.
He gets more death threats than you.
Oh, I wouldn't count on that.
Why have you suddenly taken an interest
in another human being?
I'm chatting.
Won't be trying that again.
Changing the subject completely...
You know it won't alter anything, right?
Me and Mary getting married.
We'll still be doing all this.
Oh, good.
If you were worried.
I wasn't worried.
The thing about Mary,
she has completely
turned my life around.
Changed everything.
But for the record,
over the last few years, there are
two people who have done that and...
the other one is...
a complete dickhead.
Can I ask what this is
in connection with?
Private Bainbridge contacted us
about a personal matter, sir.
Nothing's personal
when it concerns my troops.
- What do you really want?
- I'm here on a legitimate enquiry.
You press?
Digging for some bloody
royal story or something?
No, sir, I'm...
Captain John Watson,
Fifth Northumberland Fusiliers...
Retired.
You could be a used car salesman now,
for all I know.
- Bainbridge?
Gentleman here to see you.
Bainbridge!
I know you, don't I?
Hmm?
I've seen you in the papers.
Hanging around with that detective,
the one with the silly hat.
What the hell does Bainbridge want
with a detective?
I'm afraid I'm not at liberty to say.
You're not at liberty to say?
He's a soldier in my regiment.
I'll be damned if he's going to get up
to cloak-and-dagger nonsense like this.
- Sir.
- What's going on?
It's Bainbridge, sir. He's dead.
My God!
Let me take a look, sir, I'm a doctor.
What?
Sergeant, arrest this man.
What? No, no, I'm a doctor.
Oh, you're a doctor now, too?
- Sergeant.
- Let me examine him, please.
Sir, caught this one snooping around.
Is that what this is all about?
Distracting me so that this man
could get in here and kill Bainbridge?
Kill him with what? Where's the weapon?
- What?
- Where's the weapon?
Go on, search me, no weapon.
Bainbridge was on parade.
He came off duty five minutes ago.
When's this supposed to have happened?
You obviously stabbed him
before he got into the shower.
- No.
- No?
He's soaking wet
and there's still shampoo in his hair.
He got into the shower
and then someone stabbed him.
But the cubicle was locked
from the inside, sir.
I had to break it open.
Must have climbed over the top.
Well, then I'd be soaking wet, too,
wouldn't I?
Major, please. I'm John Watson,
Fifth Northumberland Fusiliers.
Three years in Afghanistan,
a veteran of Kandahar, Helmand
and Barts bloody Hospital!
Let me examine this body!
Thank you.
- Suicide?
- No.
The weapon again, no knife.
Here we are.
There is a wound to the abdomen.
Incredibly fine.
Man stabbed to death.
No murder weapon.
Door locked from the inside.
Only one way in or out of here.
- Sherlock.
- Mmm?
- He's still breathing.
- Oh, my God.
- What do we do?
- Give me your scarf.
- What?
- Quickly, now.
- Call an ambulance.
- What?
Call an ambulance now!
Do it!
Nurse, press here, hard.
- Nurse?
- Yeah, I'm making do.
Keep pressure on that wound.
Steven? Steven, stay with me.
Private Bainbridge had just
come off guard duty.
He'd stood there for hours,
plenty of people watching,
nothing apparently wrong.
He came off duty
and within minutes was nearly dead
from a wound in his stomach
but there was no weapon.
Where did it go?
Ladies and gentlemen,
I invite you to consider this.
A murderer who can walk through walls.
A weapon that can vanish.
But in all of this,
there is only one element
which can be said to be
truly remarkable.
Would anyone like to make a guess?
Come on, come on. There is actually
an element of Q&A to all of this.
Scotland Yard, have you got a theory?
Yeah, you. You're a detective,
broadly speaking. Got a theory?
Er, um...
If the blade
was propelled through the, um...
grating in the air vent...
Maybe a ballista or a catapult,
somebody tiny could crawl in there.
So yeah, we're looking for a dwarf.
- Brilliant.
- Really?
No.
- Next.
He stabbed himself
Hello, who was that? Tom.
Got a theory?
Um, attempted suicide with a blade
made of compacted blood and bone.
Broke after piercing his abdomen,
like a meat....
dagger.
- A meat dagger?
- Yes.
Sit down.
No.
There was one feature
and only one feature of interest
in the whole of this baffling case
and quite frankly, it was the usual.
John Watson.
Who, while I was trying
to solve the murder,
instead saved a life.
There are mysteries worth solving
and stories worth telling.
The best and bravest man I know
and on top of that
he actually knows how to do stuff.
Except wedding planning and serviettes,
he's rubbish at those.
The case itself remains
the most ingenious
and brilliantly planned murder
or attempted murder
I've ever had the pleasure to encounter.
The most perfect locked-room mystery
of which I am aware.
However, I'm not just here
to praise John,
I'm also here embarrass him,
so let's move on to some...
No, wait. So how was it done?
- How was what done?
- The stabbing.
I'm afraid I don't know.
I didn't solve that one, that's...
It can happen sometimes. It's very...
Very disappointing.
Embarrassment leads me on
to the stag night.
Course, there's hours of material here,
but I've cut it down
to the really good bits.
Murder scenes.
Locations of murders?
Mmm, pub crawl, themed.
Yeah, but why can't you just do
Underground stations?
It lacks the personal touch.
We're going to go for a drink in...
In every street
where you've found a corpse.
Delightful.
- Where do I come in?
- Don't want to get ill.
That would ruin it, spoil the mood.
You're a graduate chemist,
can't you just work it out?
I like the practical experience.
Meaning you think I like a drink?
- Occasionally.
- That I'm a drunk?
No. No!
You look well.
- I am.
- How's...
Tom?
- Not a sociopath.
- Still? Good.
And we're having quite a lot of sex.
Okay.
I want you to calculate
John's ideal intake and mine
to remain in the sweet spot
the whole evening.
- Lightheaded good.
- Urinating in wardrobes bad.
Hmm.
Two, er, beers, please.
- Pints?
- 443.7 millilitres.
Ah....
- What, we're on a schedule?
- You'll thank me.
- Cheers.
- Over there.
- What?
Toilets. Any second now, you'll get...
Hang on. Tell me after. I need the loo.
Mmm. On schedule.
- Eh?
- Nothing. Go.
- How long?
- Sorry?
Your visit.
If you could estimate
approximate volume discharge...
Stop talking now.
Oh.
Quick, one more. He mustn't see.
There you go.
Cheers.
I know Ash!
Don't tell me I don't.
That is enough! That is...
Ashton.
I know Ashton!
I have an international reputation.
Do you have an international reputation?
No, I don't have
an international reputation.
No.
And I can't even remember what for.
It's...
crime, something like that.
Oh.
What are you doing back?
I thought you were going to be out late?
Ah, Hudders. What time is it?
You've only been out two hours.
Am I a vegetable?
You or the...
Funny.
- Thank you.
- Come on.
- No, you're not a vegetable.
- It's your go.
Uh...
Am I human?
Sometimes.
Can't have sometimes. Has to be, um...
Yes, you're human.
Yes, I know. And am I man?
- Yep.
- Tall?
Not as tall as people think.
Hmm. Nice?
- Ish.
- Clever?
- I'd say so.
- You would.
Am I important?
To some people.
Do "people" like me?
Er, no, they don't.
You tend to rub them up the wrong way.
- Okay.
Am I the current King of England?
We....
You know we don't have a king.
- Don't we?
- No.
Your go.
I don't mind.
Am I a woman?
What?
Yes.
Am I pretty?
This.
Beauty is a construct
based entirely on childhood impressions,
influences and role models.
Yeah, but am I a pretty lady?
I don't know who you are.
I don't know who you're supposed to be.
You picked the name!
Yeah, but I picked it
at random from the papers.
You're not really getting the hang
of this game, are you, Sherlock?
So I am human,
I'm not as tall as people think I am.
I'm... I'm nice-ish.
Clever. Important to some people.
But I tend to rub them up
the wrong way.
- Got it.
- Go on, then.
I'm you, aren't I?
Client!
Client.
- Hello.
Come.
Which one of you is Sherlock Holmes?
I don't a lot.
I mean, I don't
date all that much and...
He seemed nice, you know?
We seemed to automatically connect.
We had one night, dinner.
Such interesting conversation,
it was lovely.
To be honest,
I'd love to have gone further
but I thought,
No, this is special.
Let's take it slowly.
Exchange numbers."
He said he'd get in touch and then...
Maybe he wasn't quite
as keen as I was but I...
I just thought at least he'd call to say
that we were finished.
I went round there.
To his flat. No trace of him.
Mr Holmes, I honestly think
I had dinner with a ghost.
Mr Holmes?
With a ghost, Mr Holmes!
Boring. Boring. Boring. No!
Fascinating.
John, John, wake up.
Apologise about my, you know...
Rude. Rude!
I checked with the landlord
and the man who lived there died.
Heart attack.
And there we are
having dinner one week on.
And I found this thing online,
sort of chat room thing,
for girls who think they're dating men
from the spirit world.
Don't worry.
I'll find him in 10 minutes.
What's your dog's name?
Yeah, I'll be there if you want...
John, wake up.
Meant to....
You... The game is something...
- Oh.
- Yeah, that, that.
Okay.
Oh, it's nice.
Nice place.
- See anything?
- Hmm?
Any clues, Mr Holmes?
Oh, er...
I'm just going to whip this out.
Mmm-hmm.
- You all right?
- Hmm?
- Yeah, he's clueing.
- What?
He's... Hmm?
He's clueing for looks.
Mr Holmes?
- Mr Holmes?
- I'm calling the police.
Oh, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
This is a famous detective.
It's Sherlock Holmes
and his partner, John Hamish Watson.
What do you think you're doing?
Don't compromise the integrity of the...
Crime scene.
Yeah, that.
Wakey, wakey!
- Oh, my God.
Greg? Is that Greg?
Get up, I'm going to
put you two in a taxi.
Managed to square things
with the desk sergeant.
What a couple of lightweights.
You couldn't even make it
to closing time.
- Can you whisper?
Not really!
Come on.
Well, thanks for, you know,
- an evening.
- It was awful.
- Yep.
- Oh.
I was going to pretend but...
It was, truly.
- That woman Tessa...
- What?
Dated a ghost,
most interesting case for months.
What a wasted opportunity.
Okay.
How are you feeling?
- Mmm.
It's just like old times,
having you back here.
I thought I'd make your favourite.
- One last time.
- Oh.
Don't sound so final about it.
I will be visiting, you know.
Oh, I've heard that one before.
No, it's different now, though,
isn't it?
It's different to when we thought
we'd lost him.
Well, marriage changes everything, John.
- Does it?
- Yeah.
You might not think it but it does.
It's a different phase in your life.
You meet new people
'cause you're a couple.
And then you just
let your old friends slip away.
It won't be like that.
Well, if you've found the right one,
the person that you click with,
it's the best thing in the world.
Well, I have. I know I have.
Oh, I'm sure. She's lovely.
Yeah, I think so.
- What about you?
- Me?
Did you think you'd found the right one
when you married Mr Hudson?
No. It was just
a whirlwind thing for us.
I knew it wouldn't work
- but I just got sort of swept along.
- Right.
And then we moved to Florida.
We had a fantastic time
but of course, I didn't know
what he was up to.
- The drugs.
- Drugs?
He was running, um...
Oh, God, what do you call it?
Um, a...
cartel.
- And got in with a really bad crowd.
- Right.
And then I found out about
all the other women.
I didn't have a clue.
So when he was actually arrested
for blowing someone's head off,
it was quite a relief, to be honest.
Right.
It was purely physical
between me and Frank.
We couldn't keep
our hands off each other.
And, um, there was one night...
Oh, is that Sherlock?
Is it?
No, it's Sherlock.
There are going to be others.
- Others?
- Victims. Women.
Most ghosts tend to haunt
a single house.
This ghost, however,
is willing to commute. Look.
Mmm... not you.
Not you. Not you.
Not you. Not you. Not you.
Not you. Not you. Not you. Not you.
Not you, you, you or you. Or you.
Or you. Not you. Not you.
Not you. Not you.
- Hi.
- Gail.
Charlotte.
Robyn.
Vicky.
How did you meet?
Came up to me in a pub.
Same gym as me.
We just got chatting on the bus.
Online.
- Name?
- Told you.
His name.
- Oscar.
- Mike.
Terry.
Um, Love Monkey.
- Your place?
His place.
Address?
Nothing happened.
It was just very romantic.
Four women in four nights.
He must have something special.
- He was very charming.
- Innocent.
He was sweet.
- He a lovely...
- You okay?
Let your food go cold.
Mrs Hudson will play hell.
Not now, John.
- Sorry about that.
He had a lovely manner.
Different names, different addresses.
- Describe him.
- Short blond hair.
Dark hair. Long.
Ginger. I like gingers.
Couldn't tell.
He had a mask on.
He's stealing
the identity of corpses,
getting their names
from the obituary columns.
All single men.
He's using the dead man's flat
under the assumption
it'll be empty for a while.
Free love nest.
- I feel sick.
- It's gruesome.
- That's awful.
- Clever.
Bastard.
Hello, Tessa.
Meanwhile, back to business.
No one wants to use a dead man's home.
At least not until it's been cleared,
so he disguises himself,
steals the man's home,
steals his identity.
But only for one night.
- And he's gone.
- He's not a ghost, John.
He's a mayfly. He lives for a day.
So what was it he was looking for?
Job?
- Gardener.
- Cook.
- Private nurse.
- I do security work.
Maid.
Obvious. You all work
for the same person.
No, no. Not the same employer.
Damn! Come on, we can do this.
Ideal night out?
- Clay pigeon shooting.
- Line dancing.
- Pictures.
- Wine in front of the telly.
Dungeon.
- Makeup?
- Clarins.
- No7.
- Maybelline.
- Nothing special.
- Whatever's cheap.
Perfume?
- Chanel.
Este Lauder.
Ideal man?
- George Clooney.
- Oh, no.
Home-loving.
He'd have to like cuddling.
Caring.
Ten things.
One, someone who isn't competitive
with other men.
Two, someone who isn't constantly trying
to define himself by his masculinity.
There's a unifying factor,
there has to be.
None of you reported anything stolen.
Security guard, gardener, cook,
maid, private nurse.
He's romancing his way
up the pecking order,
somebody's pecking order.
Come on, think.
Unless...
Do you have a secret
you've never told anyone?
No.
- Gotcha.
- What do you mean?
Everyone has secrets
and they all replied too quickly.
- Got to go.
- See you.
- No, wait.
- Bye-bye.
Sorry, sexy,
some secrets have to stay secret.
Enjoy the wedding.
Yeah.
Why? Why would he date
all of those women
and not return their calls?
You're missing the obvious, mate.
- Am I?
- He's a man.
Why would he change his identity?
Maybe he's married.
Oh.
Married.
Obvious, really.
Our mayfly man was trying to escape
the suffocating chains of domesticity
and instead of endless nights
in watching the telly
or going to barbeques
with the awful, dreadful,
boring people he couldn't stand,
he used his wits, cleverness
and powers of disguise
to play the field.
He was...
On second thoughts,
I probably should have told you
about The Elephant in the Room.
However, it does help
to further illustrate
how invaluable John is to me.
I can read a crime scene
the way he can understand a human being.
I used to think
that's what made me special.
Quite frankly, I still do.
But a word to the wise.
Should any of you require
the services of either of us,
I will solve your murder
but it takes John Watson
to save your life.
Trust me on that. I should know.
He's saved mine so many times
and in so many ways.
This blog
is the story of two men and their
frankly ridiculous adventures.
- Of murder, mystery and mayhem.
But from now on, there's a new story.
A bigger adventure.
Ladies and gentlemen,
pray charge your glasses
and be upstanding.
Today begin the adventures
of Mary Elizabeth Watson
and John Hamish Watson.
The two reasons why every
single one of us is...
What did you say?
You said,
John Hamish Watson.
You said that, you said Hamish.
This is a famous detective,
it's Sherlock Holmes
and his partner, John Hamish Watson.
How did you know?
How did you know his middle name?
Never tells anyone, he hates it.
John H Watson?
Yep.
- Henry?
- Shut up.
- Humphrey?
- Higgins?
Go away!
Took him years to confide in me.
That's my birth certificate.
Yep.
And the woman, she knew.
Hamish.
John Hamish Watson.
Just if you were
looking for baby names.
God knows where she is.
Out of my head, I am busy!
There's only one time
that name's been made public.
Does it have to be
on the invitation?
It's your name.
- It's traditional.
- It's funny.
Enjoy the wedding.
The wedding!
You knew about the wedding.
More importantly,
you'd seen the wedding invitation.
Now, barely a hundred people
had seen that invitation.
The Mayfly Man only saw five women.
For one person to be in both groups...
could be a coincidence.
Oh, Sherlock.
What do we say about coincidence?
The universe is rarely so lazy.
So, the balance of probability is...
Someone went to great lengths
to find out something
about this wedding.
- What great lengths?
- They lied. Assumed false identities.
- Which suggests?
- Criminal intent.
- Also suggests...
- Intelligence. Planning.
Clearly. But more importantly...
The Mayfly Man.
The Mayfly Man is...
...here today.
Ooh, sorry, I...
Another glass, sir?
Thank you, yes. Thank you, yes.
Something is going to happen,
right here.
Now, where were we?
Could be any second.
You have control of the room.
Ah, yes, raising glasses
and standing up.
Very good, thank you.
Don't lose it.
And down again.
Ladies and gentlemen, people tell you
not to milk a good speech.
Get off early, leave them laughing.
Wise advice I'll certainly
try to bear in mind but for now...
Part two! Part two is more action-based.
I'm going to walk around,
shake things up a bit.
Who'd go to a wedding?
That's the question.
Who would bother to go to any lengths
to get themselves to a wedding?
Well, everyone.
Weddings are great! Love a wedding.
- What's he doing?
- Something's wrong.
And John's great, too.
I haven't said that enough,
barely scratched the surface.
I could go on all night about
the depth and complexity of his...
Jumpers.
...jumpers, and he can cook...
Does a thing,
thing with peas....once.
Might not be peas, might not be him.
But he's got a great singing voice
or somebody does....
Too many, too many, too many, too many!
Sorry, too many jokes about John.
Now, uh...
Criminal intent.
Where was I? Ah, yes.
Extraordinary lengths.
Speech! Speech.
Let's talk about...
All of which is suggestive of...
- Murder.
Sorry, did I say "murder"?
I meant to say "marriage".
But, you know, they're...
quite similar procedures,
when you think about it,
the participants tend to know each other
and it's over when one of them's dead.
In fairness,
murder is a lot quicker, though.
Janine, what about this one?
Acceptably hot?
More importantly, his girlfriend's
wearing brand-new, uncomfortable underwear
and hasn't bothered to pick
this thread off of the top of his jacket
or point out the grease smudge
on the back of his neck.
Currently, he's going home alone.
Also, he's a comics and sci-fi geek,
they're always tremendously grateful
when you put the hours in.
- Geoff, the gents.
- The loos, now, please.
- Greg.
- The loos, please.
- Why?
- Oh, I don't know, maybe it's your turn.
Yeah, actually, now you mention it...
Sherlock,
any chance of an end date
for this speech? Gotta cut the cake.
Oh! Ladies and gentlemen,
can't stand it when I finally
get the chance to speak for once,
- Vatican Cameos.
- What did he say? What does that mean?
Battle stations, someone's going to die.
What?
Narrow it down.
No!
No! Not you, not you.
You.
It's always you.
John Watson, you keep me right.
- What do I do?
- You've already done it.
Don't solve the murder, save the life.
Sorry.
Off-piste a bit, back now, phew!
Let's play a game. Let's play Murder.
Sherlock!
Imagine someone's going to get
murdered at a wedding.
Who exactly would you pick?
I think you're a popular choice
at the moment, dear.
If someone could move Mrs Hudson's glass
just slightly out of reach,
that would be lovely.
More importantly,
who could you only kill at a wedding?
Most people you can kill any old place.
As a mental exercise,
I have often planned
the murder of friends and colleagues.
Now, John I'd poison.
Sloppy eater, dead easy.
I've given him chemicals and compounds
that way, he's never even noticed.
He missed a whole Wednesday once,
didn't have a clue.
Lestrade's so easy to kill,
it's a miracle no one's
succumbed to the temptation.
I've got a pair of keys
to my brother's house,
I could easily break in there
and asphyxiate him...
If the whim arose.
He's pissed, isn't he? Ow!
So, once again,
who could you only kill here?
Clearly, it's a rare opportunity,
so it's someone
who doesn't get out much.
Someone for whom
a planned social encounter
known about months in advance
is an exception.
Has to be a unique opportunity.
And since killing someone
in public is difficult,
killing them in private isn't an option.
Someone who lives in an inaccessible
or unknown location, then.
Someone private, perhaps,
obsessed with personal security...
- Possibly someone under threat.
Major James Sholto, who he?
- I don't think he's coming.
- He'll be there.
- Where are you living these days?
- Oh,
way out in the middle of nowhere.
The press and the family's
giving him hell,
he gets more death threats than you.
Oh, a recluse?
Small household staff.
- Job?
- Gardener, cook, private nurse, maid.
High turnover for additional security.
I do security work.
Probably all signed
confidentiality agreements.
Do you have a secret
you've never told anyone?
No.
- There's another question that remains,
however, rather a big one, a huge one.
How would you do it?
How do you kill someone in public?
There has to be a way.
- This has been planned.
- Mr Holmes, Mr Holmes!
Oh, hello again, Archie.
What's your theory?
Get this right and there's
a headless nun in it for you.
The invisible man could do it.
The who, the what,
the when, the why, the where?
The invisible man
with the invisible knife,
the one who tried to kill the guardsman.
Bainbridge? Bainbridge!
Oh, not just planned,
planned and rehearsed.
Ladies and gentlemen,
there will now be a short interlude.
To the bride and groom!
To the bride and the groom.
Major Sholto's going to be murdered.
I don't know how or by whom
but it's going to happen.
Excuse me, coming through, consulting.
- Stay here.
- Please be careful.
Excuse me, coming through.
Excuse me.
Sorry, one moment. Oh, I'm so sorry.
What's happening? What's going on?
How can you not remember which room?
You remember everything!
- I have to delete something!
- 207!
Major Sholto?
Major Sholto!
If someone's about
to make an attempt on my life,
it won't be the first time. I'm ready.
Major, let us in!
- Kick the door down.
I really wouldn't.
I have a gun in my hand
and a lifetime of unfortunate reflexes.
You're not safe in there.
Whoever's after you,
we know that a locked room
doesn't stop him.
The invisible man
with the invisible knife?
I don't know how he does it
so I can't stop him
and that means he'll do it again.
Solve it, then.
I... I'm sorry?
You're the famous Mr Holmes.
Solve the case, on you go.
Tell me how he did it
and I'll open the door.
Please, this is no time for games.
Just let us in, you're in danger!
So are you, so long as you're here.
Please, leave me.
Despite my reputation, I really
don't approve of collateral damage.
- Solve it.
- Sorry?
Solve it and he'll open the door,
like he said.
I couldn't solve it before,
how can I solve it now?
- Because it matters now!
- What are you talking about?
What's she talking about?
Get your wife under control.
She's right.
- Oh, you've changed.
- No, she is. Shut up.
You are not a puzzle solver,
you never have been.
You're a drama queen. Now,
there is a man in there about to die,
the game is on, solve it!
- Bainbridge?
Bainbridge!
Though, in fairness,
- he's a drama queen, too.
- Yeah, I know.
Major Sholto,
no one's coming to kill you.
I'm afraid you've already been killed
several hours ago.
- What did you say?
- Don't take off your belt.
My belt?
His belt, yes.
Bainbridge was stabbed
hours before we even saw him,
- but it was through his belt.
Tight belt, worn high on the waist.
Very easy to push a small blade
through the fabric,
and you wouldn't even feel it.
The belt would bind the flesh together
- when it was tight.
- Exactly.
- And when you took it off...
- Delayed action stabbing.
All the time in the world
to create an alibi.
Major Sholto!
So...
I was to be killed by my uniform.
How appropriate.
He solved the case, Major,
you're supposed to open the door now.
A deal is a deal.
I'm not even supposed
to have this any more.
They gave me
special dispensation to keep it.
I couldn't imagine life
out of this uniform,
I suppose, given the circumstances,
I don't have to.
When so many want you dead,
it hardly seems good manners to argue.
Whatever you're doing in there, James,
stop it right now.
I will kick this door down.
Mr Holmes,
you and I are similar, I think.
Yes, I think we are.
There's a proper time to die,
isn't there?
Of course there is.
And one should embrace it when it comes.
Like a soldier.
Of course one should
but not at John's wedding!
We wouldn't do that,
would we, you and me?
We would never do that to John Watson.
- I'm going to break it down.
- Wait, wait, you won't have to.
Hmm?
I believe I am in need
of medical attention.
I believe I'm your doctor.
Yeah, pretty good, just...
- Hold your nerve when you're turning.
- Why do we have to rehearse?
Because we are about
to dance together in public
and your skills are appalling.
- Well, you're a good teacher.
- Hmm.
And you're a brilliant dancer.
- I'll let you in on something, Janine.
- Go on, then.
- I love dancing. I've always loved it.
- Seriously?
Watch out.
Oh!
That rarely comes up in crime work
but, you know, I live in hope
of the right case.
I wish you weren't...
whatever it is you are.
- I know.
- Well!
Glad to see you've pulled, Sherlock,
what with murderers
running riot at my wedding.
One murder... One nearly murderer.
He loves to exaggerate.
You should try living with him.
Sherlock.
- Got him for you.
- Ah! The photographer, excellent.
Thank you. Um, may I have
a look at your camera?
Uh, what's this about?
I was halfway home.
- You should have driven faster.
Ah, yes. Yes! Very good!
There, you see? Perfect.
What is? You going to tell us?
Try looking yourself
Who? For what?
Is the murderer in these photographs?
It's not what's in the photographs,
it's what's not in them.
Not in any of them.
Sherlock, the showing-off thing,
we've discussed it before.
There is always a man at a wedding
who is not in any photograph,
who can go anywhere,
even carry an equipment bag
around with him if he likes.
And you never even see his face.
You only ever see...
the camera.
What are you doing? What is this?
Jonathan Small, today's substitute
wedding photographer,
known to us as the Mayfly Man.
His brother was one of the raw recruits
killed in that incursion.
Johnny sought revenge on Sholto,
worked his way through Sholto's staff,
found what he needed.
An invitation to a wedding.
The one time Sholto would
have to be out in public.
So, he made his plan
and rehearsed the murder,
making sure of every last detail.
Brilliant, ruthless
and almost certainly a monomaniac.
Though, in fairness,
his photographs are actually quite good.
Everything you need's on that.
You probably ought to
arrest him or something.
- Do you always carry handcuffs?
- Down, girl.
Come on, quick.
It's not me you should
be arresting, Mr Holmes.
Oh, I don't do the arresting,
I just farm that out.
Sholto, he's the killer, not me.
I should have killed him quicker.
I shouldn't have tried to be clever.
You should have driven faster.
Right.
Really?
Whoo! Yeah!
Whoo!
Ladies and gentlemen,
just one last thing
before the evening begins properly.
Apologies for earlier,
a crisis arose and was dealt with.
More importantly, however,
today we saw two people make vows.
I have never made a vow in my life
and after tonight I never will again.
So, here in front of you all,
my first and last vow.
Mary and John...
Whatever it takes, whatever happens,
from now on, I swear
I will always be there, always,
for all three of you.
Uh, I'm sorry, I mean two of you.
All two of you.
Both of you, in fact, I just miscounted.
Anyway, it's time for dancing.
Play the music again, please. Thank you.
Okay everybody, just dance.
Don't be shy.
PLAYS)
- Dancing, please! Very good!
Sorry, that was one more deduction
than I was really expecting.
- Deduction?
- Increased appetite.
- I'm starving!
- Change of taste perception.
Ugh, I chose this wine.
It's bloody awful!
You were sick this morning.
You assumed it was just wedding nerves.
You got angry with me
when I mentioned it to you.
All the signs are there.
The signs?
- The signs of three.
- What?
Mary, I think you should
do a pregnancy test.
The statistics for
the first trimester are...
Shut up!
- Just shut up.
- Sorry.
How did he notice before me?
I'm a bloody doctor.
- It's your day off.
- It's your day off!
- Stop panicking.
- I'm not panicking.
I'm pregnant, I'm panicking.
Don't panic. None of you panic.
Absolutely no reason to panic.
- Oh, and you'd know, of course?
- Yes, I would.
You're already
the best parents in the world,
look at all the practice you've had.
The practice?
Well, you're hardly going to need
me around
now that you've got
a real baby on the way.
Are you all right?
- Yeah!
- Dance!
- Hmm?
Both of you now, go, dance.
We can't just stand here,
people will wonder
what we're talking about.
- Right.
- What about you?
Well, we can't all three dance,
there are limits.
- Yes, there are.
Come on, husband, let's go.
- This isn't a waltz, is it?
- No.
Don't worry, Mary,
I have been tutoring him.
He did, you know.
Baker Street, behind closed curtains.
Mrs Hudson came in one time.
Don't know how those rumours started.