So I sign this, and all the
bribery allegations are gone?
And no one ever knows
a thing.
You never let me tell you
what the money was for.
You didn't listen to me
when I told you I don't care.
Well, do you care
that after Mike grilled me,
I was so impressed with him that
I wonder why I'd forgotten him?
But I couldn't find any record
of him ever being in my class.
Just like they're not gonna
find any record of you
Accepting a bribe
from a student.
Jessica, your secret
is safe with me.
I told him you found out
That I covered up
Daniel hardman's embezzlement.
And now you want me to protect
another one of your secrets.
It's the same secret, Louis,
And you have just as much
invested in it as I do.
You want me to kiss the ring,
Louis, after what you did?
You're damn right I do,
Because I don't care
how it got up there.
My name is on that wall
whether you like it or not.
- Hey.
What do you think of this tie?
I think...
I want to tie you up with it.
Really?
And what brought that on?
I don't know.
I'm feeling powerful.
Okay, well,
Then let's make
That happen.
Wait.
Is this to do things to me
Or just to get control
of the remote?
Why can't it be both?
Rachel, if you think I'm gonna
let you watch game of thrones
While sexually dominating me,
Then you are absolutely right.
Seriously, what's got you
feeling so good?
Oh, it just feels like
such a weight off
Now that Louis doesn't...
- Despise me?
- Mm-hmm.
Ah, you know what else
would feel like a weight off?
- Oh...
- no. No, no, no.
Nobody ever calls
the landline except my parents.
- What if something's wrong?
- It's fine.
Mike.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hello.
Yeah, this is him.
Yeah, of course
I can come meet you.
Can I ask what this is...
hello?
Who was it?
Professor Gerard.
He wants me to go meet him.
Did he say what it was about?
No, he hung up.
When does he want you
to meet him?
Right now.
- Professor Gerard.
- Thanks for coming.
I wouldn't have bothered you
if it wasn't important.
It's not a problem.
What can I help you with?
It's not me.
A former employee at
liberty rail reached out to me.
He claims he was fired
because he knows
The real reason for the crash.
And what was the real reason?
He wouldn't tell me.
Well, what did he tell you?
Enough for me to know
it would be unethical
If somebody didn't
look into this.
But you can't, so you want me
to get Harvey to.
Well, you convinced him
to look into my case
When he didn't want to,
didn't you?
This is different.
We don't take cases like this.
Maybe,
But I believe a man
who can convince Harvey
To hire someone
who never went to law school
Could convince him
to make an exception for this.
What?
He didn't tell you I know.
No, he didn't.
Well, I do.
But what I'm asking you to do
and me knowing
Have nothing
to do with each other.
I appreciate that.
Does that mean that you're
gonna tell him to take the case?
I have a better idea.
Got a second?
Of course.
What do you need?
I'd like you to sign off
on my vacation request.
Paris.
I've never heard you
talk about Paris.
No, but I have heard you
talk about it,
Which is why I'm taking you.
Are you asking me
to go to Paris with you?
I believe I just did.
Jeff, do you have any idea
How much is on my plate
right now?
Actually, I do, all of which
Harvey has agreed to cover.
You went to Harvey with this.
Well, I would have
come to you first,
But then it really
wouldn't be a surprise.
I'll think about it.
Take all the time you need.
But in the meantime,
I'll be thinking about
who else around here I can take.
Really?
Well, you're awfully
sure of yourself.
You think I haven't seen
the way Norma looks at me?
Calls me the black stallion.
Norma.
Taking a case.
What kind of case?
What does it matter?
Because you wouldn't be
announcing it like that
If there wasn't something wrong.
It's a case that came
from Professor Gerard.
What?
A man who used to work
at liberty rail
Says the real cause
of the crash was covered up.
Then refer him to a firm
That takes whistle-blower cases,
because we don't.
Yeah, I'm not gonna do that.
Then don't,
but there's a reason
Lawyers who take whistle-blower
cases don't work here,
And it's because corporations
Don't appreciate
shakedown artists.
And what if
this isn't a shakedown?
And how do you know it isn't?
What I know is that
innocent people died...
Mothers and fathers
and sons and daughters...
And if somebody's covering up
why that happened
And I can stop it,
then I'm going to.
And I said you're not.
Well, but you also said
that Professor Gerard
Didn't know my secret.
Harvey, I know,
I know he'll never tell anyone,
But someday, someone's
gonna find out who will,
And I'll be done.
Mike, he's not...
Harvey, I got
into this whole thing
So that I could try
to help people,
And I don't know
how much time I have left,
So please,
Let me try
and help these people.
Then you better make damn sure
This whistle-blower
isn't full of shit.
♪ see the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Bonjour, madame.
Oh, I'm so glad you started
with that French bullshit,
Because that's what
I want to talk to you about.
I know.
Never thought I'd have
someone ask my permission
To take you to Paris.
You know damn well
that's not what Jeff did.
Jessica, what exactly
do you want to talk about?
I want to know
why you cleared my schedule.
Because Jeff asked me to,
And I can't remember the last
time you took a vacation.
When's the last time
you took a vacation?
I'm not the one
in a serious relationship.
Oh, so you're playing matchmaker
for me now?
Oh, I'm not playing anything,
And you were the one
who said you had to choose
Between hiring him
and continuing to see him.
And then I changed my mind.
And I don't want you
to make the same mistake I did.
What are you talking about?
I should have taken
some time with scottie.
Jeff and I are not
you and scottie.
Jessica, take a vacation.
Don't take a vacation.
The man came in here,
Asking me for help because
he wants to go away with you,
And I said yes because I'm not
gonna be the reason he can't.
Pearson specter,
how may I direct your call?
- Louis, do you have a minute?
- No, I don't.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Pearson specter,
how may I direct your call?
You hear...
Pearson specter,
how may I direct your call?
Hello?
Pearson specter...
You hear that?
Where's the litt?
Every call is like a slap
in the face.
Louis, it's standard practice
for a law firm
To shorten their name
on the phone.
So blatant disrespect
is standard practice now?
It's not disrespect.
It's just...
You're telling me
that your father doesn't
Have them answer the phone,
"rand, kaldore, Zane"?
Actually, no, he doesn't,
And I think you'd agree
that people respect my father.
Unless you want to go back
to telling me
That he's a shady lawyer.
Come on, Rachel,
that was when I was mad at you.
Which is actually why I wanted
to come and talk to you.
I want to thank you
for forgiving Mike.
It... it means a lot to me.
Now, can you stop
obsessing over the phone
Long enough to hear that?
I'm sorry, Rachel,
But I can't,
And now I have to go rip
that receptionist a new ass...
Louis, if one of your first acts
as name partner
Is to rip the receptionist
to shreds,
You'll regret that
for the rest of your life.
Just let it go.
Let it go.
Things will run their course.
You know what, Rachel?
You're right.
And by the way, I'm glad
that we're friends again.
Pearson specter...
Harvey, what are you doing
at 3:30 this afternoon?
Why?
I have some news, and I don't
want you to overreact.
What is it?
Jeffrey bender
wants to meet with you.
He heard we're taking
a whistle-blower case,
And he wants us to drop it.
Relax, I'll take care
of Jeffrey bender.
Wait a second,
you're not gonna try
To cut Mike's legs
out from under him
- Before he even gets started?
- What's the point?
He'd just bother me
until I agreed not to anyway.
I can't believe it.
You have no idea what to say.
What's the date today?
I want to write this down.
You know what?
It's the seventh
of kiss my ass,
And tomorrow is the eighth of
set your own goddamn meetings.
Is that the Mayan calendar?
Nope,
that's the Donna calendar.
I got you.
For the record, I got you.
All right, take me
through it one more time.
It's simple.
There are axles on all the cars
in all the trains,
And those axles have sensors to
make sure they don't overheat.
So you're saying
that the train crashed
Because the heat sensors
failed.
I'm saying
that all the heat sensors
On the entire fleet were faulty,
And they knew about it.
Then why didn't you
come forward with this before?
You mean before they fired me
for coming forward with it?
Which brings me
to my next question.
You've had four different jobs
in the last six years.
What are you getting at?
I want to know why.
I move around.
It's not uncommon
in my business.
Move around or keep failing?
I got fired
for blowing the whistle,
Not for messing up on the job.
That's not what your last
performance review says.
I don't give a shit
what it says.
They used that as an excuse
to fire me,
And my reviews
before I came forward
Passed with flying colors.
I'm a solid worker.
How the hell do you think
I got this?
I know your reviews
are stellar.
What I need to know is
if there's anything out there
That we don't have, because
they are gonna come at us
Any way they can,
and when they do,
It's not gonna
be about heat sensors.
It's gonna be about you.
Yeah, I don't care if
I'm the worst guy in the world.
I know I'm not the only guy
in that company
That knows
those sensors are faulty.
What are you talking about?
what do you mean,
there's a report?
Done after the crash
that showed a defective part
Was the real cause,
not engineer error.
Says the whistle-blower.
Says these.
That's a memo
ordering the report
And another email
acknowledging its existence.
We got 'em.
- We do.
- Set a meeting.
Let them do the talking,
then drop the hammer,
And stick a settlement
down their throat
Before they know what hit them.
I appreciate the advice,
Harvey,
But this time I'm going in
with the hammer in my hand,
And I am coming out swinging.
Okay, big talker,
how much you asking for?
40 million.
Are you kidding me?
They'll pay ten times that
without even trying.
Not when I tell them
they're gonna have to admit
What they did.
- Are you nuts?
- No, I am not.
We are not sealing
this settlement,
And before you say another word,
this is my case.
I don't care whose case it is.
They're never going to admit
what they did.
Pick a higher number
and let them seal it.
Harvey, you told me to prove
this wasn't a shakedown.
Now you want me to take money
to cover things up?
You know what that is?
A shakedown!
A shakedown is when
your case has no merit.
This is the way things work.
Not to mention,
if we quietly settle,
We don't have to worry
about scaring away our clients.
That's why
it's the way things work.
Harvey, people died
in this crash!
And they're not coming back, no
matter what liberty rail admits.
You are such a cold,
heartless son of a bitch.
And this isn't
about your parents,
So back them
into whatever corner you want,
But when they refuse
to admit what they did,
You are not going to trial.
Stay out of my case.
Something smells delicious.
I'm making us dinner, but it
won't be ready for a while.
Good, that means we have time
To go over
my proposed itinerary.
I don't recall saying yes.
I thought that we would start
With a private tour
of the rodin.
Oh, the rodin.
God, I must have visited that
sculpture garden a dozen times.
Then I'm so glad that I arranged
for us to have a picnic
While we're there,
And during that picnic,
We can reminisce
about the week before,
Where we danced the night away
in the Latin quarter.
We did?
Mm, or we'll talk
about how we'll end the trip
In the loire valley,
Where we will sip wine
along the seine.
Jeff, this trip is perfect.
How did you know?
I know you've always
loved Paris, so I started there.
And then I called your sister.
You did that for me?
I did.
So what do you say?
I say,
If you knew what I was cooking,
You'd already know my answer.
- Looks French.
- Mm-hmm.
So you let me go through
all that even though
You knew you were gonna
say yes the entire time?
Mm-hmm.
Aren't you glad I did?
Yes, Jessica.
Yes, I am.
Donna, what are you doing here?
I'm here
because I can't take it anymore.
What?
This place has no life,
and I can't take it anymore.
And that's gonna add life?
If I gave you
something too needy,
It would intimidate you,
and you would let it die.
You expect me to believe
that's why you're really here?
Of course not.
I'm here to stop you from doing
What you're gonna do
in an hour:
Crash Mike's meeting.
Donna, I can't have him
risking our other business.
It was one client,
and you covered it.
And if he drags this to trial,
It will be every client.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
Then trust him
to accept that on his own.
Donna...
Harvey, when are you gonna
let him be his own man?
His own man?
He's out of control.
He's identifying these people
with his parents.
And you're out of control
because you can't
Separate yourself from him.
Okay, you need
to stay out of it.
And I will, but you said
you made a mistake
Not trusting Mike
with gillie industries.
I'm telling you,
don't make that mistake again.
Pearson specter,
how may I direct your call?
Uh...
rand, kaldore, Zane.
son of a bitch!
Hello, liar.
- Excuse me?
- Rand, kaldore, Zane.
You know what that is?
That's how they answer the phone
at rand, kaldore, Zane.
- Louis, I'm sorry.
- Oh, save your sorrys.
Do you know the receptionist
at the front desk?
Yes, her name is elise.
Good, you can use her name
when you fire her.
I don't have the authority
to fire people,
But I did just talk to her.
- You did?
- Mm-hmm.
To set her straight.
That's good.
No, not good.
She came to see me.
She said that
you've been harassing her.
What happened?
She said that you called and
hung up on her over 50 times.
What?
How did she even know it was me?
Because you called
from your office.
Well, it wasn't harassment
because it wasn't sexual.
Well, she also said that
you were leering at her
When you stepped
off the elevator.
I wasn't leering!
I was mad about
how she answered the phone.
Louis, it doesn't matter
why you did it.
She felt violated.
Well, you know what,
you tell her it's not like that,
And then you violate her ass
out the door.
Louis, is this really the kind
of name partner you want to be?
No, I want to be
the kind of name partner
That has his name
said on the goddamn phone.
Okay, well,
in order to fire her
Without getting sued
for harassment,
You'd have to fire
the entire support staff,
And you and I both know that
that's never going to happen.
We are not firing
all of our support staff.
Well, it's easy for you to say,
being that your name is first.
What are you talking...
Jessica, I am talking
about respect.
R-e-s-p-e-c-t,
find out what it means to me.
But I guess
I'll just find my own way
To be treated how I deserve.
I know I'm gonna regret
asking this.
Louis, tell me specifically
what it is you're talking about.
They are answering the phones,
"Pearson specter,"
Not "Pearson specter litt."
Louis...
You don't believe me?
Check it yourself.
I'm not harassing
our support staff.
It's not harassment,
God damn it!
Louis!
Jessica, it's like they've
been specifically instructed
To leave my name off.
Now you're just being paranoid.
I am not paranoid.
They're in lockstep.
I'm telling you,
someone paid them off.
Louis, that's insane,
But if you want them
to say your name,
I will get them
to say your name.
Jessica, what can I do for you?
You can explain to me
why you paid our reception staff
Not to say Louis' name
when they answer the phone.
- Who says I did that?
- They do.
God damn it.
I paid them good money
to keep Louis
From finding out
for at least a month.
He hasn't found out.
It wasn't him who got them
to crack, it was me.
Even still,
I'm asking for a refund.
Jeff, I'm serious about this.
I know you're pissed about
how he got his name on the door,
But I need you
to bury the hatchet.
- Well, I'm not gonna do that.
- Why not?
Because every single time
I see his rat face,
I think about him
blackmailing you,
And it makes me want
to walk over to him
And rip his arms off his body,
And that little phone prank
was just my way
Of keeping myself
from doing something like that.
I understand,
And I do appreciate it,
But I'm not asking you
to do it for him.
I'm asking you to do it for me.
Mr. Ross.
All I can say about your filing
is that I think
You might have a career
writing fiction.
And if you don't hand over
that report we're requesting,
You're gonna
have a career behind bars.
You're not here
for that report.
You're here to strong arm
my client into a big, fat check.
I'm sorry to be the one
to tell you this,
But a big, fat check
isn't gonna get you out of this.
- Is that a fact?
- Sure as hell is,
Because we both know
that report
Says you're responsible
for this accident,
And we're not settling anything
without you admitting it.
And we're not admitting
something we didn't do.
What the hell is this?
Well, you wanted the report.
Here it is.
Your client wasn't lying
about its existence.
He was just lying
about everything else.
We ran repeated tests
on our heat sensors,
And they passed every one.
This is bullshit.
The only thing that's bullshit
Is Joe Henderson.
He doesn't care
about the accident.
All he's trying to do
is shake us down,
Exactly like he did
at his last four jobs.
What the hell is that?
His last four lawsuits.
Did you think we wouldn't
find out about them
Just because the records
were sealed?
Mr. Ross,
your client's been playing
The whistle-blower lottery
for years.
He's never won before.
He's not going to win today.
Ch,
you tried to blow the whistle
At every job you've ever had,
and now they know it!
Keep your voice down.
You...
no, I'll keep my voice down
When you stop bullshitting me.
Those claims were
supposed to be sealed.
I don't care what they were
supposed to be.
They found them, and you were
supposed to tell me about them.
And what would you
have done if I did?
I would've said what they said,
That you don't give a shit
about what they did!
You're just looking
to get rich.
You think I would've
risked my job
And everything that I have
for nothing?
Excuse me?
I said, I don't see you
Working out of the goodness
of your heart
In your $1,000 suit.
You have no idea
who I am or why I do things.
And I told you, you don't have
to be concerned about my history
Because what
I'm telling you is true.
Not according to this.
That's the report that you said
gave us all the leverage
And they say
proves them innocent.
That report is bullshit,
Because I'm telling you,
those sensors didn't work,
And that was the cause
of that accident.
Well, I might have
a leg to stand on
If you had
any credibility at all.
How the hell am I supposed
to get a jury to believe you
When I'm not even sure I do?
What are you doing here?
I'm here to tell you
to call the front desk.
Oh, let me guess.
Jessica told you
they won't say my name
And you thought
it was hilarious.
You're right, I did.
Why don't you get the hell
out of my office
And go laugh somewhere else?
Oh, you want to hit me now?
Yeah, well, why don't you go
ask Mike Ross about my headlock?
'Cause it's a goddamn vice.
Pearson specter litt,
How may I direct your call?
It was you.
Yes, it was me,
But I fixed it, so...
You can stop worrying
if everybody at the firm
Respects you, because they do.
Everyone except you.
No, Louis, including me.
Listen, I may not like how
you got your name on the wall,
But that doesn't mean
it shouldn't be up there.
Congratulations, Louis.
Thanks, Jeff.
Hey, maybe we can even
get drinks this week.
- Name partner buys.
- Deal.
Done.
You can leave the coffee,
but I'm not getting up.
Mike, you've been working
for seven hours straight.
You need a break.
I've been working for seven
hours because if I tell Harvey
What's going on
before I have a fix,
He is gonna pull the plug.
Well, then maybe the plug
needs to be pulled.
Rachel, just because
Joe Henderson is
A bullshit plaintiff
doesn't mean
They didn't cover things up.
It doesn't mean that they did.
Okay, fine.
Why would he ask
for that report
If he knew
it would hurt our case?
- I don't know.
- I don't know either,
Which is why I need more time.
Well, then you need to convince
Harvey to let you keep going,
Because if you don't
and he finds out...
He is not gonna find out.
Mike, he's not gonna
find out from me,
But if I've learned one thing
in the last six months
Of working here, it's that if
he finds out from somebody else,
You're gonna regret it.
You come here to tell me
you're taking that vacation?
I came by to ask
when Mike Ross started taking
Whistle-blower cases.
Jessica...
I want you
to put the brakes on him
Before this gets
out of control.
Well, I'm not gonna do that.
- Harvey.
- Jessica, it's one case.
He asked me to trust him,
and I'm gonna do it,
And if you're ever gonna
be able to enjoy a vacation,
You're gonna have to trust me.
All right.
Good night.
Bon voyage.
You do know
that doesn't mean "good night."
Of course I do.
Do you know how to say
"good night" in French?
What, do you think
I'm some kind of neanderthal?
You don't know one word
of French, do you?
Ménage à trois.
You're an idiot.
Ménage à quatre.
Ménage à cinq.
Can I come in?
What's going on?
We have a problem.
I'm listening.
Liberty rail's report
directly contradicts our claim.
That's a big damn problem.
I believe my client, Harvey.
Based on what, your gut?
No, I found the guy
who wrote the report.
He's on indefinite leave
in Australia,
Where we can't subpoena him.
So it's our word
against theirs.
Which is why I'm here.
Joe Henderson made four other
claims in the last six years.
- You're shitting me.
- Harvey...
That's it.
I'm pulling the plug.
I knew it.
I knew you would bail on me
the second this thing
Hit the smallest bump.
Bail on you?
I backed you because you told me
you had a case.
I do have a case.
I told you they got to this guy.
And you got no proof of that.
And if this were your case,
You would be begging me
for help to get it.
It's not my case.
It's yours.
And now you're asking a jury
To believe these guys
fabricated a report
Based on the word
of a career whistle-blower.
No, I'm asking you
to believe it.
It doesn't matter
what I believe.
This guy is
a goddamn shakedown artist,
And I'm pulling the plug.
I don't care what he is.
I'm not
a goddamn shakedown artist!
Mike...
Harvey, you told me that
those people weren't my parents,
But they are
somebody's parents.
Please.
You got 24 hours.
You know it's against the law
to litter, don't you?
What do you want, Donna?
I know you went to see Harvey.
You know that
he wants me to fail.
That's not true.
I don't have anything,
and he only gave me a day.
And if he wanted you to fail,
He wouldn't have given you
another second.
You know he thinks
this is about my parents, right?
Is it?
Maybe it is,
But what these people did
is a million times worse
Because they knew
it could happen.
Wait a second...
they knew this could happen,
And they didn't fix it before?
Yeah, Donna, and then they...
they rolled the dice.
Well, what about now?
Are those trains
still messed up?
Because that would
make them monsters.
They are monsters, but that
would also make them idiots,
And they're not idiots.
Well, what are you
talking about?
Well, they must have
fixed the sensors by now;
Otherwise if it happened again,
they'd all go to jail.
Well, if they fixed the sensors,
then there has to be
- A paper trail.
- Of course there is.
Then all you have to do
is get it.
What do you think I've been
trying to figure out all night?
What's to figure out?
Subpoena it.
Yeah, there's only one problem.
Harvey only gave me 24 hours.
But now that
you've come up with this,
Maybe Harvey
will change his mind.
Donna, I have a theory that
I can't prove and an opposition
That's shown they're willing
to alter evidence.
He's not gonna change his mind,
and you know it.
There's got to be another way.
Donna, look, I appreciate
what you're doing,
But unless you have this other
way in your pocket, please,
Just leave me alone
and let me try
And think this thing through.
no! I don't care what he says.
It's an active
goddamn investigation,
And I'm not gonna
stand around...
You can't talk on that here.
Hang on a second, Charlie.
I'm sorry, we got off
on the wrong foot.
Is your name Danielle?
That's what it says
on the plate, isn't it?
Well, Danielle, I'm here
to pick up the documents
I ordered an hour ago,
and if you don't give them to me
In the next 15 seconds,
Today's gonna be your last day.
You didn't talk to me.
I said hold on, damn it.
Look, I don't have time
to play "who spoke to who."
I am up from do because,
as it is, these documents
Weren't sent
when they were promised.
I'm sorry.
What is it you need again?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
All the maintenance work orders
from the past six months.
I can't let you have that
without authorization.
Well, then by all means,
let's call your supervisor,
And we can tell him
how you'd rather play farmville
Than cooperate with me.
Who did you say
you're with again?
Have you heard of the national
transportation safety board?
They'll give you
what you need in the back.
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
Don't give me that.
This makes my entire case,
But I can't use it if
I don't know where it came from.
Oh, that looks like
it came from liberty rail.
Oh, oh, yeah,
it just happened to walk itself
Over from their secure facility.
Well, it's possible that
somebody went over there
And released it
from their secure facility.
Donna, if I go to Harvey
with this and tell him
What I know happened, he...
You don't know.
You think.
Don't lawyer me.
He'll never let me use it.
Well, then don't tell him
what you think happened,
Because if you do,
he'll make you drop the case.
Okay, right now,
I don't care about the case.
I care about you.
Mike, I didn't steal anything.
I talked my way in,
and that's what happened.
Did you tell them
this was discovery
For a case against them?
No.
Then it's not admissible
in court.
Well, then you
have to figure out a way
To use it not in court,
But don't ask me
for my help on that.
I have done enough.
Hey.
Heard you wanted to see me.
I take it you patched things up
with Louis litt.
How do you know?
Oh, he wanted to know
if you were a sports bar guy
Or a wine bar guy.
Did you tell him I'm more
of a strip club kind of guy?
You really want to go
to a strip club with Louis litt?
I don't really want to go
to a strip club with anyone,
But I do have a meeting
in 10 minutes,
And it's 15 minutes away.
Oh, I just wanted to tell you
That I appreciate you
patching things up with him.
There's no need to thank me.
I would do anything
for the woman that I love...
Even get a drink
with Louis litt.
You here to talk
about anderton software?
Because your 24-hour
liberty rail pass is up.
Then I guess it's a good thing
That just came
in the mail for me.
What is it?
Maintenance records showing
They replaced the heat sensors
on all of their trains
Within six weeks
after the derailment.
Now, why would they do that if
they never failed a safety test?
They wouldn't.
Which means Joe Henderson
was telling the truth.
I can think
of three different ways
They'll explain this away.
Not if we can get them on record
before they know we have it.
And why don't they know
we have it?
The same way I didn't know
they got
Joe Henderson's sealed records.
Which means you did
something sketchy.
Harvey, do you want to spend
all night asking me exactly
What I did or did not do,
Or do you want
to help me right a wrong?
Donna?
Set a deposition
with liberty rail,
And tell them this time
it won't just be Mike.
I'm on it.
who the hell is that?
That's the ceo of liberty rail.
Yeah, I know who he is.
Who is she?
That's their lawyer.
Why didn't you tell me
she was hot?
Because it's not relevant.
- It is to me.
- Why?
Because she's hot.
You must be
the infamous Harvey specter.
- You must be...
- Evan Smith.
Have to admit,
when I saw your name was Evan,
I thought you were a man.
And I have to admit,
when I saw your name was Harvey,
I thought you were a man.
- I think I'm in love.
- I think you are too.
Okay, can we
get this over with?
We sure can.
I don't even know how you
have any questions at all,
Given our last meeting.
We just have a few.
Mr. Mcintyre,
before the derailment,
Liberty rail conducted tests on
the heat sensors on its trains.
Is that correct?
- Of course we did.
- And why was that?
We run tests
on all our systems.
It's routine.
And the finding of that report
Is that there were no problems
with the heat sensors.
Are you going to just
ask questions
That you already
know the answers to?
It's routine.
There weren't any problems
with the sensors.
And do you routinely
replace the heat sensors?
Yes.
We replace them
every five years
As part of our regularly
scheduled maintenance.
And when was the last
regularly scheduled maintenance?
That would be two years ago.
And you wouldn't fix something
that wasn't broken, right?
Of course not.
I'm not in the business
of wasting money, gentlemen.
I'm a bit confused.
If you're not in the business
of wasting money
And there was nothing wrong
with those sensors,
Then why did you just
replace all of them?
They didn't replace
all of them.
I think we'd like your client
to answer that question.
You're in a bit
of a pickle, Richard.
You don't know whether to say
you did or you didn't.
Of course, you could roll
the dice with your own life
Just like you did
with other people's.
The truth is,
it doesn't matter,
Because you already
said on camera
You didn't replace
those sensors.
And we have these.
Where'd you get these?
I'll tell you
what I told Joe Henderson.
It doesn't matter
where they came from.
It just matters
that they're here.
I need to talk to my client.
That's a good idea.
You should discuss
how many zeros
You're gonna write
on that check.
And one more thing.
You're not only gonna
write a check.
You're gonna
write a public admission
Because people died
in that crash.
That's not how this works.
It's how it works today.
you're really gonna force
them to make a public admission?
Damn right, I am.
- Who are you, mahatma Gandhi?
- Somebody has to be.
You were too busy
demanding a bunch of zeros.
Well, I was just
looking out for you.
Those suits don't pay
for themselves.
No, they don't.
Mike, great job.
You really stepped it up.
Thanks, Harvey.
I think you might be starting
to come into your own too.
really?
Every single game?
No, just the playoffs.
- Two sips?
- Two sips.
- No more, no less.
- Any beer?
Oh, no, not any beer.
Miller lite.
Miller lite?
What?
But she's a queen.
What can I tell you?
She got it from her dad.
Look, if the giants
are in the playoffs
And Jessica doesn't take
two sips of Miller lite
After every single first down,
She thinks they're gonna lose,
And there's no talking her
out of it.
And those happen a lot, right?
First downs?
They sure do.
So what is she like
when she's drunk?
Well, that's a conversation
for another time.
Ooh.
I so feel you, bro.
You know, I got to say, Louis,
I almost feel bad
about pulling that prank on you.
Don't feel bad.
It was a pretty good prank.
Okay.
One more?
Only if you tell me more about
what Jessica's like at home.
No, screw that,
I want you to tell me
What she was like back
when it was Pearson hardman.
Done.
- Hey.
You're heading out
for the night?
- In a few minutes.
- Want to grab a drink?
Celebrate?
- I can't.
- Why not?
Not that it's
any of your concern,
But I'm having drinks
with Evan Smith.
What?
You got her number?
No, she called me.
Oh, she asked for your number?
No, she didn't have to.
You gave it to her.
It was on that subpoena.
I know what's gonna
be on your subpoena.
- What does that even mean?
- You know what it means.
Sure as hell do.
- You wanted to see me?
- I did.
I take it you heard
about liberty rail.
- I did.
- See?
No harm, no foul,
no mass exodus of clients.
I'm glad.
What's on your mind, Jessica?
You don't seem...
I know you told scottie
about Mike Ross.
How'd you know?
I didn't till just now.
- Jessica...
- I'm not mad.
I just want to know
what made you want to tell her.
What difference does that make?
Because I want to tell Jeff
the truth about Mike Ross too.
What changed between now
And when you fed him
that Louis bullshit?
Nothing's changed.
I just don't want
to lie to him anymore.
He told you he loved you,
didn't he?
When the hell did you start
figuring shit like that out?
I didn't till just now.
Then answer my question.
What made you decide
to tell scottie?
That's not what
you really want to know.
What you want to know
is if I wish I told her sooner.
Do you?
Yes, I do.
Hey.
Hey, Rachel,
what can I do for you?
I just wanted to come by
and say thank you.
- For what?
- Oh, come on, Donna.
Mike told me you saved the day.
Oh, well, you know,
After I saved those kids
from that burning building,
I had a little extra time, so...
Well, then maybe you should
take the rest of the night off.
And why is that?
Because that's what
superheroes do.
Macallan 18.
You got great taste.
Surprised I called?
Like I said, you got great
taste, but let me be clear.
You want to talk settlement,
I can't do it
without Mike Ross.
I'm definitely not here
to talk settlement.
Good, because there are things
I can do without him,
Exceptionally.
I want to show you
a little video.
What, did you dig up footage
From my high school
championship?
Because that'll make this
too easy.
Afraid not.
That's your secretary
unlawfully gathering evidence,
Which means there will be
no settlement of any kind.
And tomorrow, I'm sending this
to the district attorney.
Enjoy your drink, handsome.
Jessica.
Jeff, there's something
I need to tell you.
There's something
I need to tell you too.
What's going on?
What's going on is
I just had drinks with Louis,
You know, as a favor to you.
Turns out he's not so great
at holding his liquor.
- What did he do?
- No, he didn't do anything.
- You did.
- I don't...
You see, we were
actually bonding
When I suddenly remembered
what he had done to you,
And I...
well, I wanted to make sure
That no one
ever did that to you again.
So I asked him how he found out
About Daniel hardman's
embezzlement,
And he started with the words,
"it was two years ago."
Jeff, I can explain.
You can always explain,
But that just means
your whole story
About how Louis got his name
on the door is bullshit.
And I came here
to tell you the truth.
More bullshit!
Then let me tell you now.
Don't you get it?
We're past that now.
- I don't want to know!
- Jeff...
In fact, I never really
wanted to know, I just...
I just wanted you to tell me.
But now, no matter
what you tell me,
I won't ever believe
it's the truth.
Jeff, let me in.
It's over, Jessica.
It's done.
We're done.
www.tvsubtitles.net