- I'm leaving you, Harvey.
- You can't just quit.
I'm not quitting.
I'm going to work for Louis.
Your sleepless nights
aren't going to stop
until you accept the fact
that your secretary
isn't coming back.
And I told you
they'll stop when she does.
This is my formal notice,
but I have no intention
of leaving you high and dry,
so let's talk about
finding you someone
in the next two weeks.
Do you know
what's best for me?
- Ripping the Band-Aid off.
- Harvey--
So why don't you
clean out your desk
and walk yourself
over to Louis?
Hey, Harvey, if there are
any hard feelings with Donna--
No, Louis, no hard feelings.
Okay, but I just want to say
if there were--
I said there's
no hard feelings.
Jack Soloff has been
going around the firm
saying you're never gonna
save that company.
Since when do you care so much
about what Jack Soloff says?
Since he's a senior partner
with ambition.
I called your father today.
Rachel Elizabeth Zane,
will you marry me?
Yes.
How come I never get
to pick the places we eat?
Because I don't want
chicken nuggets for dinner,
and you could take a break
from them yourself.
I don't see
a little healthy heart
next to this
duck liver mousse.
Very funny.
I got Mike to try it.
I can't help it
if the man is whipped.
Speaking of which,
let me see that ring
your mother
keeps talking about.
Ooh.
Okay. I guess he knows
what he's doing.
Well, he's marrying me,
so obviously.
While we're on the topic...
- This is a prenup.
- Yeah. I had Tom draw it up.
It's actually
a standard boilerplate--
I don't wanna start
my marriage
planning how
it's going to end.
Rachel, that is not what
a prenup is for,
and you know that.
It's to isolate assets
in order to protect yourself.
I don't have assets
to protect.
Yes, you do.
Right.
You're talking
about your money.
I haven't taken a dime
from you
since the day I graduated
from college.
Yeah, maybe not,
but one day you're gonna get
everything I have.
Dad--
Rachel, marriages end
all the time,
and I just want to make sure
that you're taken care of,
if something goes wrong
between you and Mike.
If something goes wrong
between me and Mike,
I will be taken care of,
because Mike wouldn't--
- You don't know that.
- You don't know Mike.
You're right, I don't, which is
why I had that drawn up,
and the least you could do is
take it home and look it over.
Fine.
Now, can we enjoy the rest
of our dinner together?
We can try.
♪ ♪
Big Mike.
- It's been too long.
- Too long.
Guess we're just too busy
being kickass associates
at kickass law firms.
I don't know about you,
but some days I kick ass...
And some days...
You get your ass kicked.
Whoo!
Okay, Mike,
so what is this big news?
You the fastest person ever
to make it to junior partner?
- Better. I got engaged.
- No shit.
Yes shit.
Well, what country
is she from?
What are you talking about?
Well, I'm assuming
she's a mail-order bride.
Okay.
It's Rachel Zane.
- Damn.
- Mm-hmm.
Congratulations, bro.
Seriously, you hit the jackpot
with that one.
Thank you, Jimmy.
Uh, the--
Wait--wait a second,
does Harold know?
No, that's why I brought
you guys down here.
Okay. You do know he has
a huge crush on her, right?
- How huge?
- Mike, come on.
We're talking about Harold here.
What do you think?
- Oh, shit.
- Hey, bros, what's the haps?
- Hey.
I will tell you the haps,
Harold.
- Do you remember Rachel Zane?
- Uh, yeah, of course.
I still check her Facebook page,
like, ten times a day.
Why? Did something
bad happen to her?
Well, if I was her,
I would think it was bad.
In fact,
I'd think it really sucked.
Rachel and I got engaged.
Oh, that's amazing.
I am so happy for you, man.
Wow.
Really? 'Cause you
sure don't look happy.
Hey, Jimmy, why don't you
go get Harold a drink?
- Why don't I don't?
- Wait a second, Mike.
Do you remember that time
when I walked in on you
and Donna Paulsen
in the file room,
and she was on her knees?
Let's be honest, we all know
what was going on there.
Does Rachel know
about that?
Not only does she know,
she's totally fine with it.
Oh, my God.
You are the luckiest man
in the entire freaking world.
I know. I know.
Pissing me off.
I need my waitress.
- I need a Mai Tai.
- Yeah, go get her.
Mai Tai?
He needs some sex from a woman.
♪ ♪
I don't suppose
one of those would be for me.
I don't think you'd want it
if it was.
Louis likes six sugars.
Of course he does.
I hear you're interviewing
replacements this morning.
I am.
Jack Soloff.
What brings you to my neck
of the woods?
You do.
Oh, does this have anything
to do
with Jessica not being at
the partners meeting tomorrow?
It sure does.
Oh, well, then I'm way ahead
of you. She doesn't get it.
We need ventilation
in the men's bathroom.
I was in there after
Neil Sweetzer this morning,
and my eyes,
they nearly melted off my face.
That is a problem.
Not why I'm here.
I'd like to alter
the firm's compensation formula.
Okay, Jack, look,
I know that
you're the new head
of the compensation committee,
but I don't think
that's a good idea.
Salaries should be weighted
more towards billables
than contingent compensation.
What do you think
about that?
I think that affects Harvey's
salary more than anyone else's.
Would it?
- Hadn't realized.
- Bullshit.
You're using your position
to take on Harvey.
Hey, you don't make a name
for yourself taking on nobody.
Would you rather it be you?
You threatening me?
Why would I do that?
Louis, you're a name partner.
Got there by being a grinder.
It's only fair that
the grinders of this firm
got a bigger piece
of the pie.
On top of that,
Jessica's not gonna be
at the meeting tomorrow.
Timing couldn't be better.
You know what?
Bring it up.
Thank you, Louis.
What was that?
- What was what?
- That.
That was Jack Soloff wanting
to run his proposal by me.
Yeah. A bullshit proposal
designed to cut Harvey's salary.
You're picking
a fight with him.
No, I'm not.
I'm letting him
bring up his proposal
at the meeting,
so I can smack it down.
Why would you do that?
Because I saw the look
on Harvey's face.
He's jealous of us,
and I want the chance
to back him publicly.
Louis, Harvey
might be upset about us,
but encouraging people
to go after him
just so you can have his back
is a huge mistake.
You were at Millstein Swain
for seven years.
When Ellen Swain retired, I
decided it was time to move on.
Why not go to another partner
in the firm?
Because I didn't think
any of the other partners
were good enough.
I appreciate the honesty.
And I appreciate being
the first person you called in,
and if you're as good
at reading people as they say,
I'll also be the last.
- Is that a fact?
- Call anyone you want.
I'm the Deion Sanders
of legal secretaries.
- Deion Sanders?
- I'm quick on my feet.
I know how to
intercept a problem.
Yeah, but Deion Sanders?
If you prefer another era,
Dick Butkus.
Either way,
no one gets by me.
You don't look
like Dick Butkus.
No, I don't.
Well, thanks, Abigail.
I'll be in touch.
♪ ♪
You.
How long have you been
a legal secretary?
24 years this spring.
- You good at what you do?
- I'm great at what I do.
Then you start tomorrow.
♪ Suits 5x02 ♪
Denial
Original Air Date on July 1, 2015
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Well, what do you think?
- Size 12?
- You know it.
Then I think
they're awesome.
You didn't come
all the way down here
to give me your new shoe.
And I'm telling you
for the hundredth time,
Michael is not leaving Nike.
And for the first time,
I'm not here about Michael.
Adidas just made me an offer
for $100 million.
Adidas can go to hell.
That's 1/3
of what your company's worth.
- Harvey, I want to take it.
- What?
I'm not letting you do that.
I'm not asking
for your permission.
And I don't give a shit--
I'm not letting you sell
your company
for pennies on the dollar.
Where the hell
is this coming from?
It's coming from the fact that
life is short,
I'm burnt out,
and I'm ready to move on.
Life is short?
That's your reason
for not thinking this through?
I don't want
to think it through.
I might change my mind
and not do it at all.
Okay, Teddy,
you want to sell?
Sell, but we built this company
from the ground up.
Give me a week
to get you a better offer.
I'll give you the same thing
they're giving me.
48 hours.
Then I'll take it.
By the way,
where's Donna?
- She moved on.
- You see?
That's what
I'm talking about.
Life is short.
Donna moved on
to something better.
She didn't move on
What do you mean?
She's working for Louis.
Litt?
What the hell happened?
Nothing happened.
Just time for a change.
Ah.
If she's working for that
asshole, something happened.
Teddy, you say you know
when it's time to move on,
it's time to move on
from this topic right now.
Okay, Harvey.
All I'm saying is Mrs. Keebler
out there ain't no Donna.
Twice in two days?
People are gonna get
the wrong idea.
Well, they can think what
they're gonna think,
but it's not going to stop me
from giving my boy
an engagement gift.
- You're giving me a case?
- It's not just any case.
This is right up your alley.
Do-gooder lane.
- All right.
- Listen, Mike.
These people got the shaft
for one reason.
They're poor, and no one
gives a shit about 'em.
They need a hero,
and you're that guy.
Why aren't you that guy?
Oh, I am that guy,
but you're the one
getting married to Rachel Zane.
The same Rachel Zane
that I almost got fired,
and then you gave me
a second chance.
So this is your way
of making it up to me?
Listen, Mike,
talk to the plaintiffs,
listen to their stories,
and I promise you
it'll break
your little bleeding heart.
Thank you, Jimmy.
Yeah, you bet.
What if I can't get
Jessica to sign off?
Then I'll just
take the case back
and get you a decanter
or some shit.
So it's unanimous.
From now on,
all first-years are required
to bill 2,800 hours
and bring their own lunches.
Congratulations, Louis,
another generation
of associates
smacked into submission.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I think I'm done
with this meeting.
Harvey, please,
we still have new business.
Speaking of which,
I'd like to propose a change
to the current
compensation formula.
Excuse me?
Well, since taking over
the committee,
I've been evaluating
pay structures,
and I think it's high time
that this firm
put a larger emphasis
on billable hours.
Why don't you stick
to the 48th floor, Jack?
I take it you have a problem
with my proposal.
You're damn right I do.
I just took on the sale
of a man's company,
and my entire fee
is contingent-based.
Because you operate
as your own entity,
while the rest of us are members
of a team known as this firm.
No, because I bring in
a truckload of money
for this firm.
Well, like I said, special rules
for Harvey Specter.
You know what, Jack?
That's enough.
The current system
works fine,
and I don't appreciate
you speaking to Harvey
in such
a disrespectful manner.
- Are you shitting me?
- Harvey, I'm sorry.
Save your sorries, Louis.
This meeting's over.
Harvey, listen.
I'm on your side.
Yeah. I don't need you
on my side, okay?
- I have shit to do.
- Wait.
I haven't even brought up
my proposal yet
for the men's bathroom.
You want to finish
being king for a day?
Be my guest.
Enjoy your coffee
and your 50 sugars,
and go for it, but like I said,
I have shit to do.
Stanley was a good man.
Never missed a day of work,
provided for his family.
He didn't deserve
what happened to him.
What did happen?
Like I told
the other lawyer,
he went to the hospital
with chest pains.
They said it was nothing.
He kept complaining.
Stanley never complained.
Two days later
they released him.
Stanley went to sleep
in our bed that night.
And he never woke up.
No.
He didn't.
Are you sure the hospital
released him
because the insurance company
cut his stay?
He was sick, Mr. Ross,
and they just sent him home.
There are over 200
other people
who had the exact same thing
happen to them.
You think
that's a coincidence?
No, I don't,
which is why I'm considering
reopening this case.
So what's stopping you?
Well, for one thing,
I want to know
why your other lawyer
dropped out.
Because they worked that man
to the bone.
He almost lost
his entire practice,
but I was told that you're
with a big, powerful firm.
I am...
but I don't know
if I'm gonna be able
to get them
to sign off on this.
So what are we
supposed to do?
You're supposed
to sit tight.
- What the hell was that?
- What are you talking about?
You know exactly
what I'm talking about.
You stormed out
of the meeting
that we were supposed
to run together.
I didn't storm out,
I walked out
because you were doing
a shitty job running it.
What are you talking about?
I had your back.
After you let that clown
come after my salary.
I didn't let him
do anything.
I defended you,
and then you smack me down,
after which I had
to postpone a presentation
that I was
very passionate about.
It's a bathroom, Louis.
It smells sometimes.
So why don't you
just go in there,
do what people do in there,
and get out of my face?
You know what?
Donna was right.
I should have never tried
to make things right with you.
- Make things right with me?
- Yeah, Harvey.
I let Jack do that so that
I could put him in his place
and show you that I had
your back, but you can't see it
because you're too damn jealous
of me and Donna.
- What did you just say to me?
- You're jealous.
You know what, Louis,
if I was so upset
about the two of you,
why am I still paying
her salary?
Bullshit.
The firm pays her salary.
Not all of it.
You see, when I brought her
over here from the DA's office,
Jessica wouldn't hire her
because I was an associate,
so I paid her salary.
And then I made partner,
and I didn't think it
was enough, so I paid her more.
And again and again
and again.
So I've had enough
of you telling me I'm jealous.
Yeah, well, Donna
doesn't work for you anymore.
She works for me,
and the only person
who's gonna be taking care
of her salary--this guy.
- You got that?
- Fine by me.
But before you say that,
you better know what you're
getting yourself into.
Oh, yeah, I know what
I'm getting myself into,
because you can't put a price
tag on a woman like that.
I need to talk to you.
Let me guess.
You got into a pissing contest
with Harvey,
he told you he's been
covering Donna's salary,
you, out of pride, said that
you were going to take it on,
and now you're here to find out
how much you're on the hook for.
- Nothing like that.
- Oh, good.
- Then what is it?
- Everything you just said.
- Louis--
- Jessica, please.
- I just want to see the number.
- Okay, Louis.
You want to see the number?
Here's the number.
Thank y--
holy goddamn shit.
Are you sure you didn't
accidentally add a zero?
Yes, I'm sure.
Is there any way
the firm can--
The firm is not going
to pick this up.
Harvey knew that, and he chose
to pay her more anyway.
What the hell
am I supposed to do?
Well, it seems to me
you have two options:
You can tell Donna that Harvey's
been augmenting her salary,
and you don't want
to do it anymore.
- Negatory.
- Or you can pay it yourself.
- Not happening.
- There is a third option.
I can send her
back to Harvey.
How dare you?
What do you mean I'm not liquid?
Who told you
to only save 10% cash?
Well,
I don't care what I said.
Does my podiatrist
listen to me
when I tell him
I have hammertoe?
Is everything okay, Louis?
- Everything's wonderful.
- Okay.
Actually, it occurred to me
that we have not discussed
a very important subject.
What is it?
Donna, money's
a very sensitive issue.
Mm-hmm.
And I think you should be
fairly compensated.
I mean, I know how hard it was
for you to leave Harvey for me,
and I am forever grateful.
- It's just that I--
- Louis, shh.
I don't need a huge raise.
The standard 2%
is more than enough.
- 2%?
- Yes.
You have a huge heart,
but I already make more
than every other secretary
at the firm, so--
- 2% it is.
- Thanks, Louis.
Don't mention it.
Hey, do you have a second?
I need your legal advice
about something.
Yeah, of course.
What is it?
My fiancée left this prenup
in the kitchen.
I'm just wondering
if you think I should sign it.
Mike, it's not
what it looks like.
It looks like your father
had a prenup prepared
for you to make me sign.
Then it's exactly
what it looks like.
And I'm guessing
you don't want me to sign it?
No, I don't,
because he's been trying
to control me my entire life,
and I'm not gonna
let him do that with this.
Has it occurred to you
that maybe your father is only
doing this because he loves you?
I don't really care
why he's doing it.
Great marriages
don't start with contracts.
- I know that.
- Then why are you grilling me?
Hey.
Because there's a reason that
you didn't tell me about this,
and I need to know
what it is.
My dad said
he doesn't know the man
that I'm choosing to marry,
and I just--
I didn't want
to tell you that.
- Well, I found out anyway.
- Yeah.
Rachel, in the future,
I want you to feel comfortable
telling me this stuff
in the first place.
I will.
Mr. Specter, I wanted to--
You're still here?
I don't leave
until you leave.
Well, in that case, what time
is my meeting with Adidas?
11:15.
I moved your 11:00 to 3:00
and your 3:00 to 5:00.
- Did you line up--
- Buyers?
I did
but not for another week.
Nike and Puma are overseas,
and you said
Reebok didn't matter
if the other two can't be there.
God damn it.
- There's one more thing.
- What difference does it make?
I can't delay the sale
if I don't know
why my client is dumping
his company on a whim.
That's the one more thing.
Mr. Doyle's best friend died
a month ago
of pancreatic cancer.
He was 46.
How'd you know that?
Something he said to you
just before he started
talking shit about me
stuck in my head.
What exactly was that?
When people say "life is short"
two times in 30 seconds,
it's usually right
after somebody died.
I take it you were listening
to our conversation.
That's what
good secretaries do.
- Sorry about the Keebler thing.
- You didn't say it.
Besides, it doesn't take
Albert Einstein to figure out
why you hired somebody
that look like me
to replace somebody
that look like her.
Listen, Gretchen, I--
You don't have to worry
about that with me.
I prefer my men manly.
Am I not manly?
Well, if you have to ask...
Mike, how you doing?
Robert.
What can I do for you?
I heard you wanted me
to sign a prenup.
I did.
I hope
you didn't take it personally.
Of course not,
I'm happy to sign it,
but Rachel did say
that you don't know
what kind of guy I am,
so I thought I'd come here
to show you that this is
the kind of guy I am.
You're going
after Kelton Insurance?
It's not about
who I'm going after.
It's about
who I'm representing.
I'm putting my ass on the line
for 200 people
who have no one to fight
for them other than me,
so if you're worried that
I'd go after Rachel's money
if something went wrong--
You're not
that type of guy.
No, I'm not.
I respect that.
Thank you, sir.
But let me
tell you something.
I used to be one
of those people,
and I scratched and clawed
my way to where I am today,
which is why I know
when you come from nothing
and you make yourself
into something,
you're always waiting
for the day they're gonna
come and take it away.
I'm telling you
that I come from nothing,
and I would never do that.
I'm not saying
you're gonna take it.
I'm saying
you might do something
that makes
someone else take it.
What do you mean?
You're learning at the feet
of Harvey Specter
and Jessica Pearson,
and they know
something I know.
You're gonna be
a great lawyer.
You're gonna
crack some eggs,
and you never know
when someone's gonna come at you
to take what's yours
for something you did.
- Robert, I would never--
- Let me finish.
I'm telling you this
because you're gonna be family.
You might not have crossed
any lines yet, but you will.
I'm just trying
to protect my baby girl.
Jessica,
you wanted to see me?
Actually, Louis
wants to see both of us.
Then let's get it over with.
Okay.
I would like to propose
a revamping
of the pay structure
under the following guidelines.
We increase the percentage
of billables the partners get.
We decrease the percentage
of contingent fees
- by an offsetting amount.
- What?
That's what Jack Soloff
said yesterday.
No, this is different.
I've capped the amount
it affects any one partner.
You got to be shitting me.
I know you're wondering why
I'm proposing this.
It's crystal clear
why you're proposing it.
You get the exact amount
to cover Donna's salary,
and you take it
out of my paycheck.
Louis--
This has nothing to do
with that.
Jack had a great idea.
It just needed
some fine-tuning.
Fine-tuning?
You're the one that said
you only let him
bring it up
so that you can
smack it down.
Is that true?
Yes. Maybe, but I had
some time to think about it.
Jack put something
on the table,
and it's our duty
to follow through on it.
Oh, bullshit--you're only
following through on it
because you're a cheap
son of a bitch.
Harvey.
I don't want to hear it,
Jessica.
Yesterday, he accused me
of being jealous.
Today, he's coming
after my money.
- No, I'm not--
- Shut up.
We both know Donna
going to work for you
has nothing to do with you.
- You got lucky.
- Lucky?
Like a monkey
who won the lottery,
so the least you can do is
be a man, pay her yourself,
or suck it up
and tell her the truth.
All right. That's enough.
We're not doing this.
- I am a name partner.
- Louis.
No. He has no right to--
I will slap the taste
out of your mouth.
Thanks, Jessica.
I appreciate you being
on the same page.
Oh, we're not
What are you talking about?
I wanted the two of you
to run that meeting yesterday
to see if you were okay
with each other, but you're not.
He may be cheap,
but he's right.
You are taking your
Donna anger out on him,
and it needs to stop.
I don't have Donna anger.
Oh, like hell you don't.
And if you don't admit that
to yourself,
I'll slap the taste
out of your mouth too.
What you working on there,
Mike?
Um, nothing.
Just some cleanup.
What can I do
for you, Jessica?
You can tell me why
you reopened a case
against a major
insurance company
we were never a part of
to start with.
Um, I reopened it
because I looked at it
and it's a winner.
Well, I also looked at it,
and I say it's a loser.
Jessica, look--
You took a case
on contingency
where every plaintiff
is dirt poor,
which means, even if we win,
compensation for lost wages
is nothing.
You're leaving out
punitive damages,
and Harvey takes cases
on contingency all the time.
Yeah, he takes them
to make money,
not to save kittens
in trees.
And I just told you
this is going to make money.
And that's what you said
about Liberty Rail,
and instead of making money,
it almost ended
with Donna behind bars.
No one is going to jail
for this.
No, they're not, because it's
going to cost a fortune to fund,
and I'm not laying out that kind
of money on a long shot.
Jessica, look.
I promised myself that I--
I don't care
who you promised.
You took this case
without running it by me,
and you did it
because you knew I'd say no.
- Jessica--
- So that's enough.
Dump it, or I will.
I need to talk to you.
Really?
'Cause the last time
you talked to me,
you told me to open my mouth,
and you slammed it shut.
Because you wanted to go after
Harvey, but now I'm on board.
- Why should I believe you?
- Answer me this.
How many partners
do you have in your pocket,
if we put your proposal
to a vote?
I can get 45%.
Well, then the reason
you can believe me
is that I'm gonna get you
the difference.
How you gonna do that
if you don't have the courage
to back my plan
at your own meeting?
By showing everyone
at this firm exactly
what Harvey makes.
Now I know
you're bullshitting me.
You'd be fired
if you did that.
Not if I do it by accident.
Can you believe
that sneaker brings in
over a billion dollars
from China alone?
With earnings like that,
makes me wonder
why you're trying
to rip off my client.
Buying a man's company
for a fair price
is hardly ripping him off.
But it's not a fair price.
You gave my client 48 hours
to take your offer.
I'm gonna give you five minutes
to take mine.
Double your money,
or I walk out the door.
That's ridiculous.
What's ridiculous
is you preying on a man
who just lost
his lifelong friend.
I'm a businessman,
not a grief counselor.
Then let me counsel you
on this.
Because he's grieving,
I have the ability
to go to the board
and delay this sale.
But you're not going to,
because you know
it'll drive down
the price even more
when he eventually
wants to sell anyway.
You're right,
it will,
but I'll tell you what,
Mr. Polk,
it'll still be worth
more than your offer.
And after my client's grief
passes,
he may still want to sell,
but it sure as hell
won't be to you.
♪ ♪
I got to call you back.
How the hell
did you get in here?
I fired your assistant
ten minutes after I fired you.
Guess Amy still knows
how to get a person through.
Congratulations.
You made your way in.
You can make your way out.
Not before I give you
the chance to make $20 million.
Mm-hmm. What makes you think
I want to get in the business
of underwriting
class-action lawsuits?
Because you're in the business
of making money,
and before you say no,
I'm gonna give you
20% off the top.
It's the best deal
out there.
Well, that's not
good enough.
25%.
Are you authorized
to do that?
No, you're not.
Knowing you, you probably don't
even have the authorization
to come to me
in the first place.
I came to you because this is
our chance to make it right.
Bullshit.
You need money.
That's the only reason you're
standing here in front of me.
Jonathan,
I could have gone anywhere.
I came to you for the same
reason I went to Walter Gillis,
to make it right.
Pick up the phone
and ask him.
I'm not Walter Gillis.
Tell Amy I said "thank you"
for getting you past security,
'cause now I'm gonna call
every investment banker I know
and tell them to pass
on your offer
because Mike Ross
can't be trusted.
What the hell is this?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Yes, you do. This is Harvey's
last three income statements,
and I found them sitting
in the copy machine.
Donna, I need you to put that
back where you found it,
and I need you
to put it back now.
- I won't do it.
- That was not a request.
- That was an order.
- I don't care.
- I'm not gonna let you do this.
- See?
I knew that you would jump
at the first opportunity
you had to take his side
over mine.
This isn't me
taking Harvey's side.
This is me stopping you
from making a huge mistake.
And if he did the same thing,
you wouldn't be stopping him.
Harvey would never
do anything like this,
and if he did,
I sure as hell would.
- Oh, bullshit.
- No, Louis.
It's not bullshit.
You have no idea
how many times
I kept him from
going overboard with you.
- It was half my goddamn job.
- Well, you know what?
You didn't stop him
every time,
and you're not stopping me
this time.
Now, give me that thing.
Okay. Fine.
You don't want to put it back?
- I'll do it myself.
- Louis--
No. Donna, you know what?
You came to work for me.
You knew who I was
when you did,
so now it's time
for you to decide.
Are you with me or not?
While I'm not opposed to
unexpected gifts on my desk,
I do prefer
if they're made of chocolate.
Got it.
Next time I leave you
a signed prenup,
it will be made of chocolate.
Why did you sign it?
- I went to see your dad.
- You did what?
I wanted to show him
what kind of man
his daughter was marrying,
because I wanted him
to trust me.
Mike, he doesn't trust anybody,
which is exactly why
I'm not interested
in his marital advice.
But like you said,
I would appreciate it
if in the future,
you tell me if you're gonna
do something like that.
You're right, I should have told
you before I went over there,
but for the record, instead of
getting him to trust me,
I ended up trusting him.
- Mike--
- Rachel, listen to me.
I know you think that
he's doing this to control you,
but he thinks he's doing it
to protect you.
And the truth is
that I never had a father
who could do something
like that for me, so...
I think that you should try
and see where he's coming from.
What's that?
It's your new offer.
- It's twice the money.
- It's what I do.
And that's why
I pay you so much.
I didn't do it
for the money, Teddy.
I did it because you
were getting ripped off,
and I'm not gonna let
that happen to you,
no matter what
the circumstances.
You found out.
Why didn't you
tell me what happened?
Because I didn't want you
to try and stop me.
You still could have
come to me.
And tell you what?
That my best friend
from when we were seven died
out of the blue?
I hadn't spoken to him
in 20 years,
because we got into a fight
over some woman whose name
I can't even remember.
And now I don't give a shit
about the sneaker business.
Well,
I would have understood.
Would you have?
Look, Harvey,
I appreciate what
you did for me.
If I'm ever back in business,
you'll always be my lawyer.
I'll always be your friend.
- Louis, do you have a second?
- Oh, I don't know.
What animal are you gonna
call me now? An iguana?
I'm not gonna call
you anything.
I'm here because I want
to put everything behind us.
Well, aren't I lucky?
Louis, please.
You were right.
I was a dick in that meeting
and again in the bathroom
and again with Jessica.
I said some things
that I wish I could take back,
but we've been friends
with each other for a long time,
and I don't want
to throw that away.
You really mean that?
I do.
Come here.
Harvey, this is amazing.
I never thought
you would come to me and--
- Oh, shit.
- "Oh, shit" what?
I forgot. I have to put a bid
on an item on eBay.
- What?
- A Mongolian...
praying mantis piano ballet.
Good talk.
I have to go.
♪ ♪
What is that?
You shouldn't be reading that.
That's privileged information.
Where the hell did you--
♪ ♪
Oh, shit.
What's that for?
It's a retainer.
I am looking
for some legal advice.
I don't think
you can afford me.
It won't take long.
I just want you
to take a look at this.
You got Mike to sign this?
My dad did.
Then why are you
coming to me?
Because you once told me
that you have a father
just like mine.
Let me guess, you think Robert
is trying to control you?
He did manage
to construct a situation
where the two
most important men in my life
are making decisions
about me without me.
You know what I think?
I think this has nothing
to do with your dad,
and you know it.
Mike.
Yes. Mike.
That's the real reason
why you're coming to me,
even though
you told yourself it wasn't.
- It could protect me.
- It could.
It could also
do something else.
Undermine my relationship.
Believe me.
I learned that one
the hard way,
which means you need
to ask yourself,
how much do you
really love Mike?
I love him all the way.
Then don't sign it.
On the house.
And, Rachel,
as far as your father goes,
he and I don't always
see eye to eye,
but I do respect that man.
And if he is anything
like my father,
for all of his faults,
he would take a bullet
before he'd let anything
happen to his little girl.
Thank you.
Uh, okay.
Harold and I
ponied up last time
because it was
a special occasion,
but tonight drinks
are on you, my friend.
That's fair.
As much as I appreciate it,
Jimmy, I got to return the gift.
- What?
- Yeah.
- I can't take the case.
- No, no, no.
What do you mean
you can't take the case?
Jessica won't lay out
the money for the man hours.
Okay, then get somebody else
to lay out the money.
Mike, investment banks
are taking stakes
in shit like this now.
You, of all people,
should know that.
You think
I didn't try that?
It didn't work.
God damn it, Mike.
You always said
you gave a shit about people.
And you said that
I could return this case.
I don't care what I said.
Jimmy,
what the hell
is going on here?
Okay. One of the victims
was my uncle Keith,
but I didn't tell you about him
because my cousin came to me
and asked me
to make it right,
and I promised her
that I would.
It's just I don't have the juice
at my firm,
and I was--
I was too ashamed
to tell you.
- Jimmy--
- No, Mike, listen.
Look, I'm sorry
I didn't tell you straight up.
But, please,
these people need your help.
What can I do for you,
Jack?
You can explain to me
how the hell you justify
making this much money.
Where'd you get this?
Was left in the copy machine.
- By who?
- I don't know.
But now I do know
why you pissed
all over my idea
at the meeting.
This is confidential.
It was confidential.
Now, every senior partner's
seen it,
and people are furious.
I earn every penny I make.
We'll see about that.
What are you talking about?
I just called for a vote
tomorrow on my proposal,
and I hope you've been
saving your money,
because your gravy train's
about to leave the station.
So this is why you said,
"Oh, shit."
What's that?
Oh, you know what it is,
because you're the one
who left it
in the goddamn copier.
Oh, my God, Harvey,
I was making copies
of everyone's salaries for
my records, and I must have--
Bullshit, Louis.
You did this
to come after me,
and after I apologized,
you ran and tried to stop it.
Harvey, please,
what's done is done,
and like you said before,
we're friends.
We can move past this, and we
can fight the vote together.
There's no way I win the vote
after people see this.
You want to get past it?
Admit what you did.
That's automatic termination.
Then we'll fight that
together.
- Harvey, I can't.
- Louis!
Jessica tried
to fire me once.
I can't give her the chance
to do that again.
Well, you know what?
It's gonna happen again,
because I know what you did.
You know what?
That's enough.
And you come at me
flinging accusations,
well,
you better have proof.
You have proof, Harvey?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
Harvey, you don't get
to come to me
at all hours
of the night anymore.
I'm here
because your new boss--
- I know why you're here.
- Then you know what he did.
And I need you to admit it,
so I can block
their bullshit vote.
And get Louis fired?
He wouldn't be in this mess
if you'd have just stopped him
from doing this
in the first place.
Harvey, if I knew Louis was
gonna do something like this,
and I'm not saying I did,
then I would have
told him to his face not to.
But if he went ahead
and did it anyway,
then I'm not gonna
go behind his back to fix it.
Because you always said,
"Once you pick a side,
"if you're not loyal
to that side,
then who the hell are you?"
Then you should have
thought of that
before you picked someone who
would do something like this
in the first place.
You want to know
what kind of man Louis is?
This whole thing started
because he wanted to prove
to you that he had your back,
because he thought
you were jealous of us.
No, this whole thing started
because I told him that
I've been paying your salary
since we came to the firm,
and he was too cheap
to pay it himself and too weak
to tell you the truth.
And if you've kept that
from me for 12 years
and you're only just telling me
now, then maybe you are jealous.
Mike, how'd you get in?
Give you a key already?
No. Laura let me in.
She said you'd be back here.
I don't know why.
I'm trying
to find something tasty.
There's not one damn thing
that's bad for you
in this entire house.
Then I guess it's a good thing
I didn't tell her
that I brought you these.
Oh, chicken nuggets.
Rachel made them herself.
Deep-fried, not baked?
You're welcome.
She sign that prenup?
No, but she sent those
because she realized the prenup
was about love,
not control.
Then I respect her decision.
What changed her mind
about me?
You really want to know?
- Mm-hmm.
- Jessica.
Oh, shit.
What did she say?
I got to know that secret.
I don't know
what she said to Rachel,
but I know
what she said to me.
So that's why you're here.
You know those people that
I told you I was fighting for?
Jessica's not
gonna go for it.
I get it.
Too much money to lay out
for too little payoff.
But you said you came from
the same place as these people.
Robert, they need someone
like you to fight for them,
and I can't do it.
So I'm asking you to.
You think this case
is a winner?
I do.
Then what do you say
we do it together?
What are you doing here,
Louis?
I notice you didn't come
to the vote this morning.
No, I didn't. I was busy
closing a deal for my client.
Let me guess. You had 'em
backdate your sale to yesterday,
so it falls
under your old pay structure?
No, Louis,
that's something you would do,
because unlike you, I don't
actually care about the money.
You expect me
to believe that?
I don't care whether you
believe it or not.
My compensation package
was about recognizing what I do.
Money was just a consequence.
That's why I didn't mind
sharing it with Donna.
- Now, get out.
- No.
You did care about the money,
because it was the last thing
you had that separated you
from me.
- Excuse me?
- I got name partner.
I got Donna,
and that drove you nuts.
So you shit on me
at the meeting,
and then you pretended
to apologize.
I did apologize, Louis.
I came to you
like a man,
and then when I gave you
the chance to make it up to me,
you choked,
like you always do.
Well, how you like me now?
Because the only thing you
had left was that you made more.
And now you don't,
and I win.
You didn't win anything.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the fact
that no matter what you get,
you're always wanting more.
And the problem
with always wanting more is
that the second you get it,
it can always be taken away.
You're not reversing
that vote.
I'm not talking
about the vote.
I'm talking
about what you value most.
That's right.
Might not happen today
or tomorrow,
but it's gonna happen, because
I'm gonna make it happen.
One day, you're gonna walk
into your office,
and she's gonna be gone.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net