Will you marry me?
- Yes, I'll marry you.
- When we have kids,
world, watch out.
- Louis, I don't want kids.
- Sheila, I'm gonna be a father.
- You heard louis.
He already gave him the job.
- I want to know
why the hell you came back.
- What matters is
that I'm staying,
Because this is where I belong.
- This makes it look
like forstman's payment
Never went
to any offshore accounts,
And that you never took
a piece of it.
- That's forgery.
- Which is a less of a crime
than what you did.
- I had no choice!
- Bullsh--, you had no choice!
You could have said "no" at any
goddamn point along the way.
- One thing is for sure.
When all this is over, I'm
gonna fire the sh-- out of you.
- I wouldn't be back here
if it wasn't for louis.
- I'll take care of it.
- "Dear harvey and jessica,
"I put all of you in jeopardy
for my own personal gain.
"effective immediately,
I, louis litt,
"am resigning
from pearson specter.
Please take care of my home."
- One, two.
- Give me a second, gimme a sec.
Maybe we can get you
some trunks, go a few rounds.
- I think I've already
gone a few rounds.
I need your help.
- Anything.
What can I do for you?
- Clients.
I need clients.
- Louis, the by-laws say that--
- Come on, harvey. You think
I don't know what they say?
I wrote the by-laws.
- Yeah, and who'd you
write 'em for, huh?
Jessica, and she's not gonna
make an exception for you.
- Well, maybe she'll make one
for you?
I tried to get interviews
at six different firms
And every one of them
said the same thing:
It's a bloodbath out there.
Which means if I can't
bring business with me,
Because I'm never gonna
find a job in this city.
- Louis...
- Harvey.
I'm not askin' for the moon.
Just three companies that
I brought to the firm myself
When they were nothing.
- Let me talk to jessica.
- Thank you.
- Harvey, you don't look busy.
Would you like to attend
the international securities
Law symposium?
- That depends.
Is it in vegas, miami, or rio?
- Poughkeepsie.
- Send paul porter.
- What can I do for you?
- I just saw louis.
- No. He's not getting
any clients.
- He just wants three.
Letting them go won't break us.
- No, it won't,
but it will open the floodgates
That ever thought of leaving
and taking their clients.
And he's worked his fingers
to the bone for both of us,
And he's asking for a crumb.
- And I give him that crumb,
and next thing you know,
All the cookies
in the cabinet are gone.
- I do know that instead
of talking about giving
Louis' clients away,
You should be working
on keeping your own.
- Jessica, I'll find a way
to keep versalife,
But that has nothing
to do with louis.
We owe the man something.
- And I'm giving him something.
My phone rings and he gets
a glowing recommendation
Instead of me saying that he
left after committing a felony.
- No one's gonna call
if he can't get in the door.
- That's on him, not on me.
- Are you sure we
should be doing this?
In bankruptcy
picking through his stuff?
- It just doesn't feel okay
going through his things.
- Rachel, you haven't heard from
him. I haven't heard from him.
If we don't pack up his stuff,
who will?
- I guess you guys
had the same idea I did.
Yeah.
- He didn't take that either?
- No.
I just cleaned it.
It was smudged
And I didn't want to give it
back to him dirty.
- He must have been
in such a hurry.
- He was in a hurry 'cause
he was ashamed.
- I want to just
get this over with.
- Jessica, what--
- am I doing here?
I'm here to tell you
that I know you know the truth
About louis' resignation.
- I don't know--
- Yes, you do, and I'm guessing
you didn't like it.
- You're right.
Because I don't think
that he deserves to be fired.
- That's funny, because I think
you both deserve to be fired.
- What do you--
- you knew what he did,
And you said nothing.
- So that's why you're here.
To fire me.
- No. I'm here to give you
a second chance.
- Those don't look
like my case files.
- They're not,
but I didn't come empty-handed.
I got you somethin'.
- A job?
- General counsel
at procter & gamble.
- Procter & gamble?
What is that, a joke?
They're in cincinnati, which is
like, american for "siberia."
"number 31 on the fortune 500,"
And it's a chance
to make a fresh start.
- Whose idea was this chance?
Her majesty?
Oh, yeah,
I bet she loved that.
- Louis, it was my idea,
and you should take it.
- Well, would you take it?
No way on earth.
You know why?
Because this is rome,
You're a gladiator,
and so am I.
- Then be a gladiator.
Take this job and fight
your way back here.
- I don't have
to go to cincinnati
To fight my way back here.
I can goddamn fight jessica.
- ♪ see the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ all right ♪
♪ all that time
imagine this ♪
♪ the greenback boogie ♪
- I'm here to pick
the three clients that are mine.
- Those clients, like everyone
this firm represents,
Belong to me, and there's
nothing you can do about it.
- Oh yes there is,
'cause pursuant to the by-laws,
You're required
to inform clients
Of any attorney's departure.
If you fail to do so prior
to me giving you formal notice,
They're up for grabs.
- Well, you wrote the by-laws.
I'll take your word
that's what they say.
- Oh, I see. You don't think
I can take 'em from you, huh?
Well, I'm the one who brought
them in and answered their call
When all you did
was take your cut.
- Is that all I did?
- Yes, and that's
why I'm gonna win them,
Because I deserve them.
- And that's what it always
is with you, louis, isn't it?
What you deserve.
- You're goddamn right it is,
And you have some nerve
tellin' me no
After all I've done for you.
- What you've done
is break the law,
And I'm still willing to give
you a good recommendation.
- I don't need your
bullsh-- recommendation.
I need clients, and if
you're not gonna give 'em to me,
You better strap in,
because I'm gonna take 'em.
- Louis.
You haven't returned
any of my phone calls.
- I don't like contact
during transitional periods.
- But you didn't even
say goodbye.
- What is there to say, katrina?
- Well...
When you're ready,
I would love to take you out
for dinner.
- We can't do that.
You're on the other side now.
- What are you talking about?
- I gave jessica notice.
I'm going after three clients.
- Louis--
- no-no-no.
And I do not want to put you
in the position
To fraternize with the enemy.
- You're not the enemy, louis.
Jessica had me contact all
of your old clients in person.
- She what?
- You can't approach them.
It's over.
- I have to get going.
- Louis!
I am so sorry.
I didn't want to do it.
- Don't be.
If it had to be somebody,
I'm glad it was you.
- I'm in the middle of a merger.
What's so important
that I had to come down
To your sh--ty office?
- This used to be
your sh--ty office.
And after that,
it belonged to six other people,
Five of whom are now gone.
- That things can change
in the blink of an eye.
- Louis.
- Yes, louis.
Took all of ten seconds
to scrape his name off the wall.
How long do you think it's gonna
take jessica to scrape off mine?
- Harvey, jessica
sees me as a huge problem.
The solution is just
to get rid of me.
I don't want that to happen, so
I need to solve
an even bigger problem.
- And you want me
to give you a bigger problem.
- I just got back.
I need you to give me
The biggest problem you've got.
- Fine.
Sterling pharmaceuticals
is merging with pfizer.
Come on, smart guy.
You want to solve the problem?
You better be able
to identify it.
- There is no problem.
They merge.
They only make up 26%
of the market.
That's--that's not
over the limit for 10b-6.
- But?
- Sh--.
Versalife puts us
over the limit.
- Unless we figure out a way
around 10b-6.
Like I told jessica I would.
Harvey, no one has ever
been able to do that.
- Listen to me.
You want to make a splash?
Part the red sea.
Oh, no.
- "oh, no," what?
I don't feel like having.
- You know what, harvey?
I just came in here to see
if you needed anything.
- I don't.
- Okay, fine.
Listen, I know that
this whole thing with louis
Is upsetting you.
- No. What's upsetting me,
is you saying
- I'm worried about him.
He's in a really bad place.
- You think I don't know that?
That's why I tried to help him.
I got him a job
on a silver platter
And he threw it in my face.
- And he shouldn't
have done that.
- Yeah. Then why are you here?
- Because I still think
we can help.
You did a good thing
by getting him that job.
It was the right instinct,
but it was the wrong city.
- Yeah, I can't get him anything
in new york.
- I'm not talking
about new york.
- Then what the hell
are you talking about?
- Nice grouping.
- How'd you know I'd be here?
- Because you go mudding
when you're happy,
And you come here when you're
looking to blow off steam.
- Well, I am blowing off steam,
donna,
And I'm not finished, so
unless you can handle a pistol,
Do me a favor please
and just leave me alone.
- Connecticut junior
pistol championship finalist.
Three years in a row.
- Ask me that again
and I will use this on you.
- Is there anything
that you can't do?
- No, there isn't.
Including talking harvey
into getting you another job.
- So where is it this time?
Cincinnati? Minneapolis?
Anchorage, alaska?
- Boston.
- Sheila.
- Yes, sheila.
- I got him to give you his word
he will do it,
He's not gonna make the call
unless you say you're on board.
- I can't.
- What do you mean, you can't?
- Donna, sheila values strength.
She's gonna
see this as me coming to her
At a time of weakness.
- Louis, you go to boston
with the sole purpose
Of being with her, she's gonna
see that as a sign of love.
- Tell him to make the call.
- Okay, kyle, I think
the question you have to ask is,
"where do I see myself
in ten years,"
And unfortunately, the answer
is, "not as a harvard graduate."
Idiot.
Louis, what are you doing here?
- I'm here to take you back.
- I-I don't understand,
the way we lef--
- I don't care how we left it.
Not a day has gone by that
I haven't thought of you,
And I can't hold
it back anymore.
Sheila, I love you,
And I want us to be together.
- Louis, this is wonderful,
but it's--it's--
It's just a lot to take in.
To believe that
you're really ready to commit.
- Well, how's this for ready?
I'm taking a job in boston.
- What?
- I quit pearson specter.
- Oh, my g--
I can't believe it.
You did all that for me?
- Yes.
- Well, I--
- Well, what?
- I got a job in boston for you.
- Louis, did you
make that decision
Before or after you
quit your old job?
- What difference does it make?
- It makes a huge difference.
You don't call for six months,
and then...
And suddenly I'm supposed
to fill the hole in your life?
- No-no-no-no-no,
it's not like that.
- Okay, then what is it?
- I mean, do you know
How hard it was
for me to not call you?
I was tryin' to move on.
- Then why didn't you move on?
- Because I realized
that I don't need new york.
I need you.
- Louis, geography was
the least of our problems.
And--and I want you to know
that I've come around on that.
- You don't "come around"
on children.
I don't want them, and I'm not
going to change my mind.
- You don't have to,
because I've changed mine.
- Okay, and I believe
that you believe that, it's--
- Well, then if you b--
I'm just sensing
that you don't know where I'm--
- Louis, when I asked
if you'd quit first,
I was asking because if--
If I believed that you
were really ready
To give up children,
I would run
Into your arms
and never let go,
But if you're doing this
because you're down and out--
Do you understand that
I was going to change
My entire work schedule
weeks ago for you?
Before all this.
- You were going to.
But you didn't.
- Sheila, please.
- It was good
to see you, louis.
Please go.
- You see me getting
my ass kicked by ftc rule 10b-6.
- And?
- Harvey needs and update
and I don't have sh--.
- And if you were harvey
and he was jessica,
You'd say you're all over it.
- I can make that happen.
- Donna, send a bottle
of johnnie walker blue
To jonathan palmer,
and get him tickets
To the next sox game,
And then find out
when his wife's birthday is,
His kid's birthday,
his dog's birthday.
- How am I supposed to--
- I don't care how you do it.
Figure it the hell out.
- Harvey, this is
a thank you to him.
- It's not a thank you,
it's an apology for you
Talking me into getting him
to give louis a job.
- What did he--
- He didn't show up
to the interview,
And what's happening
with our versalife problem?
- I'm all over it.
- Yeah, "all over it" means
you don't have dick.
Next time I see you,
have something.
- Jonathan palmer's in boston.
Harvey got louis a job there
because of sheila, didn't he?
- Yes.
- Donna, if he didn't show up
For the interview, it means
it didn't work with sheila.
- Sh--.
He's gonna be devastated.
- You bring him his box
of stuff yet?
- No, but I'm going
to right now.
- Let me do it.
- Listen to me.
Harvey's pissed at you
because you don't have anything
And louis needs me.
- Donna, I am here
because that man
He gave up going
after sheila for me.
For all I know, that's why it
didn't work out for him up there
And it's...
The least I can do,
is comfort him when he's down.
- Go.
- Come in, come in.
What are you doin' here?
- Stuff has been sitting
on your desk for days.
I wanted you to have it.
- Okay. I'll need it
for my new office.
- You got a job?
- Not yet, but I will.
- Oh.
Order of the coif.
Yeah, look who
graduated magna cum laude.
- Summa, actually,
for all the good it'll do me.
- I know there's got to be
a story behind this key. Yeah?
From one of your
first cases or...
- Mike, do me a favor, please.
Just stop it, will you?
- Stop what?
- Stop asking questions that
you already know the answers to
Just to stay here longer.
- Louis, I'm not--
- you're not what?
You're just making small talk
while you look around the room
To see if there are any
sharp objects in the vicinity.
- That is not why I came here.
- Well, it wasn't to deliver
a box of my sh--.
- Look, when I was drowning,
you threw me a lifeline, okay?
- Okay, well,
that's nice of you to say,
And I appreciate you
bringing over my things,
But they're not exactly
a lifeline.
- I heard about boston.
- What'd you hear?
- That harvey got you a job
and you didn't even show up.
- Well, why would I
when the love of my life
Rips out my heart
and then stomps on it?
- Louis, I'm just trying
to help.
- Well, you can't!
I don't have sheila.
I don't have a job.
And right now I'd just
prefer to be alone.
- No.
Well, I don't care
what he says.
15% of bullsh--
is still bullsh--.
Dick.
- I can see you're busy, sir, so
I'll just jump right to it and--
If this is your asking me
for rachel's hand in marriage,
You know, you're goin'
about it the wrong way.
- Sir, I think if I were gonna
do that, I'd have the foresight
To ask your wife
how to approach you first.
- Good answer.
I'm actually here
about louis litt.
- Yeah, I heard he resigned.
- He did, and he's looking
for a job.
- A fellow like that
should have his pick.
- Well, the partnership
agreement prohibits him
From taking clients.
- Ooh, sh--.
- Yeah.
- Ah, jessica doesn't
play around, does she?
- Look, I know it's bad
out there, but--
- Bad? It's the apocalypse.
And I'm not runnin'
a soup kitchen.
If a partner
can't bring me clients...
- These are louis' billables
for the last 15 years.
- Mm.
This guy ever sleep?
- And he doesn't just bill.
He trains the associates,
he publishes.
He will give his life to you.
- And you want me to do this
because you're with my daughter?
- I want you to do this
because I've never asked you
For a thing, and
the first time I am,
It's a favor for someone else.
That's the kind of man
that your daughter is with.
- So it's because you're
with my daughter?
- You're gonna see it
how you're gonna see it,
But the real question is:
What are you gonna
do about louis litt?
- I'll meet with him.
But there's no guarantee.
- Well, that's all I can ask.
- You tell my daughter to give
her old man a call sometime.
- Yes, sir.
Hey.
- You look happy.
- I am happy, because today
I did a good thing.
- You're going to let me paint
the bedroom robin's egg blue?
- I said I did a good thing.
I didn't say
I did a ridiculous thing.
- I got louis a job interview
in new york.
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
- That's amazing!
- Yeah.
- Oh, I love you.
- Well, you should fix
one for yourself too,
Because I couldn't have
done it without you.
- What do you mean?
- I mean the interview's
with your dad.
- What?
- I went to your dad for louis.
What?
- It's really sweet.
- But...
- Let's just say
there's a reason
That I didn't go to my dad
to pay for law school.
- I thought you said it was
because you wanted
- It is, but other people
don't have a problem
Because they don't have to wait
for the other shoe to drop.
- What are you talking about?
- So you mean after this, he's
gonna want something from me?
- I don't know, but he's gonna
want something from someone.
- If it gets louis a fresh
start, I really don't care.
Really?
- Yeah.
- You got to be kiddin' me.
- No.
- You went there too?
- Every Tuesday
for the last five years.
- Oh. Wednesday.
Chicken parm day.
- More like christmas to me.
- Oh, I believe it.
- Oh, louis.
But it's time that we got
down to the crux of the matter.
- You want to know
why I resigned.
- Well, I did call jessica,
And she gave you
a glowing recommendation,
And we both know
that's bullsh--.
- You want to know the truth.
- Did I say anything
about the truth?
I'm just makin' sure you know
I know that it's bullsh--.
But my truth is,
I don't care why you left.
All I care about
is what you're gonna take.
- What?
- You take one client,
I could give a sh--
How big it is, and I'll make you
a senior partner on the spot.
- Wait a second.
Mike ross said
That I was not required
to bring business.
- This isn't about business.
This is about balls.
I don't need another grinder,
I need a lawyer
who can kick a door in,
And the door in question
is pearson specter's.
- You want to see if I can break
my partnership agreement?
Because if you can't do that,
then what the hell good are you?
You're no different
than jessica.
I'll take that
as a compliment.
Sylvia will validate you
on the way out.
Robert, this is new york.
I take a cab.
- See, that's my way
of saying "get the hell out."
- Well, how long
is a little while?
- Do you have any--
- Louis!
- Excuse me.
Katrina, what are
you doing here?
- You know what I'm doing here.
This isn't your client anymore.
You're prohibited
from contacting them.
- I-I'm not here to see--
- neubacher capital?
Yes, you are.
Just like you're going
to go see carver tech
And blackthorne simons.
- How do you know that?
- Because they called me.
- What are they saying?
- Doesn't matter
what they're saying.
It's plain as day
you're trying to poach them.
- Does jessica know?
- Not yet.
But if you keep doing this,
she's gonna find out.
- Yeah, well, let her sue me,
'cause I don't have
any other choice.
- Robert zane offered me
senior partner
If I can break
the partnership agreement.
That is a major law firm
in new york.
I'm not gonna get
a better chance than that.
- Look, tell jessica
if you have to.
I don't want to get you
in trouble, okay?
But I just lost my job.
And I just lost the woman
I love for the second time,
All in one week.
Now I have this chance
to turn my life around...
With this one client.
I'm gonna take it.
- Louis.
You want one client,
I'll give you one client.
- What? Wait, no--
- When you agreed to take me on,
I swore that
I would be loyal to you,
And if I'm not loyal now,
then I never was.
- Katrina, if you do this
and jessica figures it out,
She will fire you,
And I cannot live with that.
- That won't matter
if you get the job
And you take me with you.
- Give me the goddamn name.
- What?
- I'm gonna tell you something,
And I don't want
you to overreact.
- From the look on your face,
I'm not makin' any promises.
- I just got an email
from louis.
He's going after versalife.
- Get me ray.
- What are you gonna do?
- Get me ray!
- Harvey, it was just
a notification email.
You don't even know where he is!
- Yes, I do.
- That notification is required
by the bylaws.
He's doing it
at the last second.
I guarantee you he's walking
in versalife's door right now.
- Hell do you think
you're doing?
- Not doing, did.
I just signed versalife.
- You have no right.
- Please, I have every right.
Because when I quit, jessica
only notified my clients,
Not yours,
because she didn't think
I had enough balls
to go after you head-on.
Because I didn't think
you would stoop this low.
- Oh, too bad. You exposed
your flank, now you're too late.
- Yeah, and you can see
the fear in my eyes.
Excuse me.
- I told you, you're too late.
- To tell them
an unemployed clown
Just sold them
a pile of bullsh--?
- You mean the bullsh-- that you
have to drop them as a client?
The pfizer merger.
Ftc rule 10b-6.
They were not pleased
that you kept them in the dark.
- You are a son of a bitch.
- Who's the clown now?
You're a son of a bitch.
I'm only taking one client
The least you could do
is be a gentleman about it.
- A gentleman?
I got you two jobs!
- Two jobs in siberia!
Out of pity.
- I got you those jobs
out of compassion,
Just like when
I fought for jessica
To not fire you
in the first place.
But when I take versalife back,
It's gonna be without
any feeling for you at all.
- What happened?
- I lost them,
but I'm gonna get 'em back.
- What I want to know is
how the hell did louis find out
That we had to drop them?
- I don't know.
People know sh--.
- People don't know sh--.
People get told sh--.
- Jessica, I know I wanted
to throw him a bone,
But I did not tell him.
- I wasn't talkin' about you.
I was talking about mike ross.
- Tell me you didn't have him
working on versalife.
- That doesn't mean--
- I knew it.
He was working on versalife.
He owes louis
for bringing him back here.
That is motive and opportunity.
- You just want him gone
by any means necessary.
- Oh, I think I have been
more than clear about that.
- Yeah, well,
try another theory,
Because mike
would never do this.
- Oh, there are a lot of things
You never thought
mike ross would do.
Sell out an old man's company.
Get in bed with a billionaire.
Cut his boss out of a deal.
- Jessica--
- people change, harvey.
Louis is taking versalife
to robert zane.
Mike ross' future father-in-law.
Why don't you think about that?
- Mike, I need to know
what you have on versalife.
- It was me.
- What was you?
- Louis going after them
is my fault.
- What did you--
- I went to robert zane
And I asked him
to give louis a job.
- That's it?
You didn't tell him
about versalife?
- Of course not, wh--
you think I would do that?
You went to one
of our biggest competitors
And put 'em together
with a desperate louis.
- I did it because louis
was desperate, all right?
I went to see him the other day
to bring him his stuff,
You're telling me when you
were supposed to be helping us
You were busy giving them
to louis on a silver platter?
- I was, but I also figured out
how to get them back.
- Why didn't you tell me then?
- 'cause I was trying to think
- What the hell's
wrong with this option?
- It involves going
to walter gillis.
- Well, look
who decided to drop by.
The man who lost me my company
And his partner
who tore it to shreds.
- Walter, I understand
how you must feel.
- So, why are you here?
- Because we have a proposition
for you.
- Does it involve an apology?
- It is an apology.
- You want me to buy versalife?
- We want you to buy
a division of versalife.
- They've been working on
anti-addiction meds for years.
- Look at the results.
This one works.
- But it's a money-loser
and it's gonna take years.
They don't have
the capital, the patience,
Or the will.
- But you do.
- And let me guess, you two are
here out of the goodness
Of your hearts.
- You want the truth?
He'd be here whether this was
for his own good or not.
For me, I'm here
because it gets me out of a jam.
- So you can stick it to us
if you want to,
But if you do that...
You're gonna miss the chance
to save a lot of other people
Just like phillip.
- Don't ever talk to me
about phillip again.
This is how all this started,
with you using my son.
- No, I'm the one
who used your son.
I used him to get control
of your company,
But everything mike did
from the second he met you
Was to save your company,
Because when it comes
to caring about people,
He's twice the man that I am,
And by the way,
he never gave up on you,
And he never sold you out.
- Bullsh--.
- You're right, it is.
- Mike, no.
- The truth is,
is that I gave you my word.
I told you I would never sell
you out and then I got into bed
With someone
that I never should have trusted
And I lost you your company.
- Yes, you did.
- And that company
was your family.
It gave you purpose,
but you still have money,
And this is a purpose.
Walter, if you don't want
to do this, I get it.
But I need you to understand
that the only reason
I even thought to come to you
in the first place
Is that I'm gonna regret
what I did to you
For the rest of my life.
I hope you're not
furious with me.
- I'm not mad.
- You're not?
- No.
- Well, good.
I wanted to...
Thank you
For setting up that meeting
with robert zane.
I just hope you understand
that if I had a choice,
I never would have gone
after versalife,
But I had no choice.
- Louis, we took them back.
- What?
But you had to drop them.
- Not anymore.
We convinced them to sell
their trial drug division.
- Of course. You drop a drain
on their earnings,
Stock price
goes right through the roof.
- And their market share
falls below the threshold.
- But who the hell
would buy it?
- Walter gillis.
- Of course, walter gillis.
- Louis, listen--
- mike.
You won.
You're a brilliant lawyer.
- You are a brilliant lawyer.
- Yeah, I'm a brilliant lawyer
who's never gonna work again.
- Hey, stop.
That is not true.
Look--look--look
at everything that you have.
A harvard law diploma,
summa cum laude,
Those are the credentials
of a supreme court justice.
- Nah, that and 2 bucks will
get me a seat on the subway,
But thank you
for having the decency
To tell me in person.
- Louis, come on.
Let me--let me--
Let me stick around for a while.
You--you can tell me the story
about that key.
- Mike, I know
what you're tryin' to do.
Now's not the time.
Please go.
- Come in.
You're not louis litt.
- No, I'm not. But if you're
expecting him to show up,
It's gonna be a long wait.
- You here to take his spot?
I'll give you senior partner
right now.
- I'm here to tell you
you're not getting versalife.
- I'm sorry,
I don't know who that is.
- It's the company
you tried to poach from me.
- You seem upset.
- I'm not upset.
I just wanted to remind you
you once told me
I was a piece of sh-- for using
your daughter against you,
But now you turn around
and use louis against me?
- No, that's not the same.
- It is to me.
I may fight with him,
but he's still my family.
- Then why did he leave?
- That's between me and louis.
- I wanted versalife, but it's
not worth gloating over.
So why are you really here,
harvey?
- I'm here to ask you
to take louis anyway.
- And why would I do that?
- 'cause you're a smart man.
If you do it, I'll owe you one.
- I don't need you owin' me one.
- Why don't you take the night
to think about it?
You can never have
too many favors in the bank.
- You wanted to see me?
- I heard about versalife.
Good work.
It wasn't you.
- No, it wasn't.
- You know I thought it was you.
- Harvey didn't tell me,
But I didn't just
fall off the turnip truck.
- No, you didn't.
- What?
- Every damn time I think
there's no upside to having you,
You do some sh--
to make me think
It's actually nice
to have you around.
- We're good after you
bill a few more hours tonight.
- Well, that's gonna
have to wait until later,
Because I am definitely
going out to celebrate.
- You've earned it.
- Jessica.
She did what harvey
would have done for you.
- Jessica.
- Katrina.
- Is this about the--
- I can either fire you...
Or you can resign.
The choice is yours.
- You know?
- I know.
- Then why are you being
so nice about it?
- Because letting you go
is enough.
- And you also don't want
to antagonize me,
Since I'll be working
for robert zane.
- You haven't heard?
We got versalife back.
Louis won't be going to zane,
And neither will you.
I wish you luck.
- You'll have my letter
of resignation on your desk
In the morning.
- Well, if I were, I'd say you'd
gone three times in an hour.
- Yes,
and this is our third drink.
- You know they have medicine
for that, right?
- You saying I'm old?
- Yes, but I'm also saying
I know you haven't been goin'
to the bathroom.
- All right, you want the truth?
I've been calling donna.
- Oh my god, that is so great.
You guys finally
decided to take the plunge.
- I wanted to know
if robert zane called me back.
- I asked him to hire louis
anyway.
- You're kidding.
- I'm not.
I even told him
if he did I'd owe him one.
- Hmm.
- What?
- Oh, I'm just tryin'
to figure out at what point
In the last week
you decided to become a pussy.
- Oh, so doing something nice
for someone makes you a pussy?
- I didn't say that exactly.
- Yes, you did.
You've done for people.
- Okay, you know what, harvey?
I am nice, and if that makes me
a pussy, then so be it.
- Then it's settled:
You're a nice pussy.
Miss, can I get a cosmo
here for my friend?
- Go ahead, order another drink.
Be in the bathroom
in another five minutes.
- You going back
to the prostate again?
- What, like you've never
repeated jokes before?
- I have no idea what--
- what I'm talking about?
Let's see uh, "you see,
That's funny,
because blah-blah-blah,"
Or "by blah-blah-blah,
I mean blah-blah-blah."
- Okay, I get it.
- Oh, I'm just getting started.
I could do this all night.
- Hey, you know what?
Now I have to go
to the bathroom.
- Go for it.
Take your time, no rush.
If it hurts, call someone.
- Louis, what
are you doing here?
- I'm waiting for harvey.
- Harvey's not here.
- Then you'll have to do.
- Look, louis,
I know you've been
through a lot,
But harvey's gonna--
- I don't give a sh--
what harvey's gonna do.
- Okay, you're scaring me.
- You know what an oscar
looks like?
- What?
- Academy award. Bald guy.
I mean, of course
we all know what it looks like,
But especially you,
you're an actress.
I mean, of course you don't need
to be told what it is.
- What are you talking about?
- The highest academic honor
In harvard law is
the order of the coif.
You don't get a trophy.
You get three things.
You get a parchment
to hang on your wall,
A medal to wear at graduation,
And this.
Now, this key
doesn't say "order of the coif."
It doesn't say anything.
It's just a symbol.
- What does that have
to do with harvey?
- It doesn't.
It has to do with mike.
- You know what, louis?
It's been a long day, can--
- It's about to get longer.
See, mike asked me about this.
And I thought he was--
I thought he was trying to get
my mind off of my problems,
But then he did it again.
And it got me to thinking:
Mike graduated magna cum laude.
He's in order of the coif.
But he didn't recognize this.
- So he forgot a stupid key.
- Mike ross doesn't forget
anything.
See, the reason
he didn't recognize this
Was because he never got one,
because...
He didn't go to harvard.
- Louis, we've been
down this road before.
Mike is the harvard database.
- But he's not in the yearbook,
His address during his law
school years was in new york.
He even paid rent the first
of the month in person.
- Well, I'm sure there's an--
- sit down!
Last year, you told me not to
tell sheila about mike's file.
You acted like you cared
about me.
You didn't give a sh-- about me.
You cared about you!
And harvey!
- No.
- And mike!
- And jessica!
- Louis, that's not true!
- Well, let's call sheila
right now.
I know all of the numbers
by heart.
I mean, she may not
be interested in me anymore,
But she will definitely be
interested in a fraud claiming
That he went to harvard.
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
You've been lying to me
since the day mike ross arrived.
I knew harvey and jessica
never really accepted me,
But I thought
you were different.
I thought you were my friend.
- I am your friend, louis.
- No, you're not.
And don't you ever
say that to me again.
- Where are you going?
- To see your friend jessica.
Louis knows.
- Louis.
- I know you're a stickler
for the rules,
So I figured I'd just
come by to return my I.D.
- I want to see you
perp walked through the bullpen
With your pretty little jacket
draped over your handcuffs.
But until then, yeah,
I'll take an explanation.
- When I found out the truth
about mike ross,
It had already been done.
- By harvey?
Right after he
made senior partner over me?
That's when he hired the fraud?
That's the correct timeline,
right?
- Yes.
- So instead of turning him in,
You cover it up.
- Louis--
- And the one time
that I do something...
You don't cover it up at all.
You throw me to the wolves.
- I saved you from the wolves.
- Then I ask you
for the smallest gesture,
Just to allow my career
to continue with dignity,
And you couldn't muster
the tiniest shred of compassion.
- What do you want me to say?
- I want you to tell me
you're a liar!
And a hypocrite!
I want you to say you're sorry.
- I am a liar.
And I am a hypocrite.
But I will not say I'm sorry,
Because I did what I did
to protect this firm.
- Well, looks like the captain's
about to go down with her ship.
- Bullsh--.
You want something.
- Oh, I told you.
I want to see you in--
- In handcuffs?
If that were true, the police
would be here instead of you.
No, you wanted to see me squirm
Before asking me
for what you really want.
I'm not gonna
give you the satisfaction,
So you might as well
spit it out.
- You asked me what I wanted
once before, and I told you,
And then you told me
that I couldn't have it.
But now I can.
Pearson...
Specter...
Litt.
www.tvsubtitles.net