Previously on "Suits"...
I don't owe Harvey shit.
He may have gotten me out,
but he done came and put me
in there in the first place.
You're right,
you don't owe Harvey,
but you do owe me
because I didn't have anything
to do with putting you in there,
but I broke the law
to get you out.
I came here to compliment you
on getting rid of Sheila's ass.
If she's not back
by the start of trial,
I'm gonna assume you want
to be brought up on charges.
I just stopped by to give you
this restraining order
preventing you
from contacting Louis Litt.
You're done driving a wedge
between me and my people.
If I represent myself,
every second I'm up there
they're gonna see me
as a lawyer.
And if she rattles you
for one of those
goddamn seconds,
they're gonna see you as a fraud
and they're never gonna see you
as anything else.
Did Mike Ross go
to Harvard Law School or not?
I'd like to assert
my Fifth Amendment right.
If I was on that jury,
I'd find you guilty.
They're not gonna
let me change my goddamn lawyer
in the middle of a trial.
We need to figure out
a way to make them,
'cause if we don't,
we're gonna lose.
You have one last chance
to save yourself.
Call me before it's too late.
Okay, so we have
a plan for you
to start representing yourself.
We just need a way to rattle
Gibbs when we execute it.
I have a way, but...
you're not gonna like it.
I'm gonna call Clifford Danner
to the stand.
No way, it's too risky.
- Harvey, listen to me...
- He's angry and volatile
and in case you forgot,
he's one of the people
you were dumb enough
to tell your secret to.
I know all of that,
but you said it yourself,
we need sympathy,
and no one is gonna
get us more sympathy
than the innocent guy
we got out of prison.
Harvey, you said
I needed to do this.
Well, this is how I do it.
Do you have faith in me or not?
♪♪
Mrs. Gloria Danner?
- Yes.
- Hi, my name is Mike Ross.
I'm a lawyer at Pearson Specter
Litt and I was hoping...
I know who you are,
and I know
what you're doing here.
You've come to get Clifford
to testify for you,
but I'm afraid
he's not going to.
Please, ma'am, I promise you,
the DA cannot reopen his case...
I'm not talking
about the district attorney.
My son's dead, Mr. Ross.
♪♪
- What?
- Clifford was shot and killed
three weeks ago, so...
I'm sorry, he can't help you.
♪♪
- Hello?
- Are you in the office?
It's Thursday night.
I'm watching my show.
Well, then goddamn Tivo it
because I need your help.
It better be important if
you're taking that tone with me.
And if this is about
that mah-jongg game...
I don't give a shit
if it's mah-jongg
or kung pao or Chinese checkers.
This is the most important thing
that I'm ever gonna ask you
to do in your entire life.
Give me an order.
I need you to pull
whatever strings you have
to get me a transcript
of Mike's trial
and I need you
to keep it to yourself.
Mind if I ask
what you need it for?
Because I need to know if we
have a snowball's chance in hell
of winning this thing.
Is defense ready
to call its first witness?
- I am, Your Honor.
- What?
I'm calling my witness.
Does prosecution have a problem
with that?
Objection, this is outrageous,
Your Honor.
They can't switch attorneys
in the middle of a trial.
And that would be true
except for the fact
that I've been co-counsel
on this case from day one.
Co-counsel?
What planer are you living on?
The one where Pearson Specter
Litt is my attorney of record.
I have the employee directory
right here.
My name is in it.
It's been there
since the beginning
of this trial,
and if you wanted
to object to me,
you would have had
to have done it
at the beginning of this trial.
Then I want them waiving
all rights to a mistrial
and I want it in the record.
Your Honor,
I'm not gonna be punished just
because she didn't understand
that I've been representing
myself this whole time.
He's got a point, Ms. Gibbs.
Then I want them waiving
all rights to a mistrial
based on
him representing himself.
My pleasure, Your Honor,
'cause I don't expect
we'll be needing a mistrial
at all.
Then call your first witness.
Defense would like to call
Gloria Danner to the stand.
Please state your name
for the jury.
Gloria Danner.
Mrs. Danner,
a number of years ago,
your son Clifford
was convicted of murder
and sentenced to prison,
is that right?
Yes.
For a crime he didn't commit.
How do you know
he didn't commit it
if he was convicted of it?
Because you proved he didn't.
Mrs. Danner,
can you tell the jury
why it is that you're here today
testifying
and not your son Clifford?
He was working late
at the diner.
It was the only place he could
get a job when he got out.
Two men came in
to rob the place,
and when Clifford tried
to stop them,
he was shot and killed.
I'm so sorry.
I worked my whole life
to put him through school
and he ends up dying
in the back of that
shit restaurant
in that shit part of town.
Can you tell the jury
why you agreed
to come share your story
for me today?
♪♪
Prison
ruined Clifford's life...
♪♪
And if you had been our lawyer
from day one,
he never would have been
convicted in the first place.
♪♪
Thank you, Gloria.
No more questions, Your Honor.
♪♪
Mrs. Danner,
I happen to be familiar
with your son's case.
and I understand
that in order to reopen it,
Mr. Ross risked
increasing his sentence to life.
That's correct.
Well, I'd like to know
how you'd have felt
if he lost that gamble.
I'd have been devastated.
And if that happened,
how would you have felt
if you then found out that
Mr. Ross wasn't even a lawyer
after all?
Objection, Your Honor, how
many hypotheticals can she ask?
That's okay.
I think everybody
in this courtroom knows
how they would feel.
No more questions, Your Honor.
I wouldn't have cared what
a piece of paper had to say,
because Mr. Ross is
the only lawyer I ever ran into
that ever gave a damn
about my son.
♪♪
Mr. Ross, would you care
to call your next witness?
♪♪
I can't imagine anyone
being more eloquent than that,
Your Honor.
♪♪
Defense rests.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 5x15 ♪
Tick Tock
Original Air Date on February 24, 2016
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Having trouble
with your closing?
No, it's just
part of the process.
Would it make you feel better
if I told you
that I have never felt more
proud of my future husband
than I did watching you
up there today?
Yes, it would.
Good.
Because I want to talk to you
about your closing.
Ugh.
Don't tell me you want me
to go with jury nullification.
There is nothing wrong
with getting a jury
to sympathize with you,
and, Mike, your parents died
in a car accident.
Who isn't gonna feel
for a person like that?
Rachel, the only problem
with me saying,
"Let me off because
tragedy struck me as a child"
is I've pretty much admitted
that I'm guilty.
No, the difference is that
that accident is the reason
that you wanted to become
a lawyer in the first place.
And they won't just understand
it, they will love you for it.
How can you know that?
Because I love you for it.
Tell them your story
and I am telling you,
they'll let you go.
♪♪
Louis, you wanted to see me?
Yeah, that was hours ago.
We need to talk.
We need to talk right now.
- About what?
- About the fact that
Mike Ross is all of a sudden
representing himself.
And why exactly do we need
to talk about that?
Because it means Harvey thinks
he's gonna lose.
You wanna walk me
through that logic?
Harvey's never given up
control of a case in his life,
and if he's doing that now,
it means he wants that loss
on Mike's record.
Louis, at a time like this,
Harvey doesn't care
about records.
Bullshit.
I read the transcript
backwards and forwards.
He thinks he's gonna lose.
Louis, what's really
going on here?
I'll tell you what's going on.
If Harvey thinks
we're gonna lose,
then we'll lose,
and if that happens,
you know who Gibbs
is coming after next.
Louis, we will deal with that
when and if she does,
but I am telling you,
Harvey letting Mike take
the reins is not him giving up.
It's him growing up
and realizing he is not
the one to bring this home.
♪♪
Do you want to talk about it?
Talk about what?
Oh, I don't know,
maybe the fact
that Mike is working
on a closing
to keep himself out of jail
and you're not working on it
with him.
There's nothing for me to do,
Donna.
It's in his hands.
In his hands?
Harvey,
that was a trial maneuver.
It doesn't mean you can't
help him when he needs you.
- He doesn't need me.
- He needs you more than ever.
No, he doesn't,
and it's time for him
to put the clipboard down
and get in the game.
- Harvey...
- Donna, this wasn't just
some move to slip testimony in.
This is Mike's life.
It's his story and he needs
to be the one to tell it.
Everything he's done up until
now has prepared him for this,
and I'm telling you,
he's ready for it.
Is defense ready
for closing statements?
♪♪
Mike?
You okay?
Mr. Ross?
Oh, uh, yes, Your Honor.
♪♪
Um, ladies and gentleman
of the jury,
I think most of us...
You guys heard evidence earlier
in the trial
that I have
a photographic memory,
and I do, but the way it works...
I don't just take
a snapshot of something.
See, I read it
and then I understand it,
and once I understand it,
then I never forget it,
but I've been trying
to memorize my speech,
but I can't
because it's bullshit,
because I...
I am bullshit.
You see, the truth is, is that
I am guilty of being a fraud.
My whole life I have wanted
to be a lawyer
so that I could help people
like Clifford Danner.
People who have no one else
to fight for them.
No one who believes in them,
but instead, all I've done
as a lawyer
is work night and day
to put money into the hands
of rich people.
I was given a gift
and I wasted it,
and I'm ashamed of myself.
Andand as a final insult,
I paraded this mourning woman
out in front of you
just as a way
to get you to admire me.
♪♪
I am so sorry, Gloria.
And all I can say is
that I promise you,
whether these people
find me innocent or not,
I am gonna spend
the rest of my life
fighting for the
Clifford Danners of this world.
I will not waste
that gift again.
♪♪
You could believe it or not,
but I am a lawyer,
and I always will be.
♪♪
Thank you.
Well, it's an interesting
thing, really,
how criminals can play
with our emotions.
Mike Ross is articulate
and persuasive and passionate
and listening
to his closing argument,
I almost want
to let him go myself,
except for one thing:
He's a liar.
He didn't commute to Harvard
one day a week
as he so laughably claims.
He didn't go to college.
There is no paper record
of his enrollment,
no applications to law school,
no picture in the yearbook,
no class rankings,
no one at all
who even remembers him.
Except for that
one indebted friend
with a lot to lose,
and if you believe
his testimony,
I got a bridge over Brooklyn
I'd like to sell you.
And whether he says it or not,
he's banking on the fact
that you are gonna think
this is a victimless crime,
but if you acquit him,
you are giving permission
to everyone to say...
"Hey, I'm gonna pretend
"to be a lawyer.
"I think I'm gonna say
I'm a doctor.
"Hell, you know what?
Today,
I'm gonna pose as a pilot."
Imagine if one day you woke up
on the operating table
to discover the man who was
about to crack open your chest
is not really a doctor.
Guilty.
Make no mistake about it,
Mike Ross thinks
he's better than you.
He thinks he doesn't have
to play by the same rules,
but we know he does
because, ladies and gentleman
of the jury,
Mike Ross...
Is a fraud.
♪♪
Mike...
Mike.
She was good, Harvey.
- Yeah, so were you.
- You were great.
She was better.
Everything she said was true
and the jury knows it.
No they don't.
Look, ever since
the day I met you,
you have always seen
the good in people,
and we only need one person
on the jury
to feel that way about you.
- And what if they don't?
- It doesn't matter
because we can't do anything
about it anyways.
So, let's get out of here.
- I can't.
- What do you mean you can't?
I mean, I can't leave
until that jury comes back.
Mike, they might not come back
for days.
I don't know what to tell you,
Harvey, but I can't leave here.
It's okay, Harvey.
♪♪
Look,
Mike, if we really
don't have time,
I don't want to waste it here.
Rachel, if I leave,
all I'm gonna be thinking about
is what's happening
in that jury room.
Then I am going to go
and get us some food
and we're gonna have
a bite to eat
because I'm not gonna
let this time go to waste.
Okay.
♪♪
- What?
- What do you mean what?
I want to know what you think.
I think I saw
a heavyweight fight
that's gonna come down
to the goddamn cards.
You see it any different?
What I see is my fate
in the hands of a jury,
and I don't like it.
Why the hell do you think
I cut so many deals
instead of going to trial?
Well, the only deal
that Gibbs is going to cut
is the one that
hangs us out to dry.
And I don't know about you,
but I don't feel like
just sitting by
while this thing goes
to verdict.
You think I do?
Look, there's no other w...
Hold on a second.
We could go get us a mistrial.
What good would that do?
A mistrial's just gonna
kick the can down the road
till Mike gets tried again.
Listen to me.
When Mike wanted to
represent himself,
Gibbs jumped out of her chair
saying that we were trying
to get a mistrial.
Then she demanded we waive
our rights to one completely.
And the only reason
she'd do that
is because she doesn't
have authorization
to try this case again.
Which means,
a mistrial isn't just
kicking the can down the road.
No, it's blowing it
to kingdom come.
♪♪
The only problem is,
we don't have grounds
for a mistrial.
Well, then you better go out
and find some.
And you better do it
before that jury comes back.
♪♪
That's what I'm trying
to tell you.
My lawyer's not here.
That's not my problem.
Then why did he tell me that
if I told you
he couldn't make it,
you'd give me a continuance
or something?
I'll tell you what I'll do,
Mr. Diaz.
Since Perkins isn't here,
I'll help you out.
Instead of going to trial
and winding up
with a five year sentence,
I'll let you cop
to three and a half right here.
Five years?
We stole some TVs.
For the third time,
and that's five years.
I was only driving the car,
man.
Then you can drive yourself
to prison, man,
but I'm not giving you
a continuance.
Hey, I'm sorry to interrupt,
but he doesn't give you
a continuance, the judge does.
And you're entitled
to one automatically
if this is the first time
your attorney didn't show.
- And who the hell are you?
-That's not your concern.
And this is not your concern.
Yeah, well,
I'm making it my concern
since I don't like
watching prosecutors
take advantage
of unrepresented defendants.
All I'm doing is
offering the man a deal.
I'm not taking advantage.
That is bullshit.
You know full well
his lawyer didn't tell him
to ask you for a continuance.
He told him
to ask the judge for one.
Now you're gonna try and bully
him into three and a half years
for what sounds to me like
a simple misdemeanor theft.
You don't know shit
about this case.
Well, I'm about to.
Hand over the case file.
I don't have
to give you anything.
You're not his attorney.
Mr. Diaz,
my name is Mike Ross.
Now, do you want me
to represent you
or do you want to stick
with this asshole Perkins
who didn't even show up
to your hearing?
He's my lawyer.
Donna, I need your help
and I need it right now.
What's going on?
Is the jury back?
No, I need to know
if Stephanie Liston still works
at the U .S. Attorney's Office.
She does, why?
I need the names
of the jurors.
Harvey, if you're even
thinking about tampering...
No, I'm not thinking
of tampering with the jury.
I just need to find grounds
for a mistrial.
A mistrial?
You told Mike he killed it.
Was that a lie?
- No, it wasn't.
- Then why are you
so suddenly having doubts?
It's called hedging.
No, it is called
breaking the law
and I don't want any part of it.
Goddamn it, Donna.
I'm trying to protect Mike.
Then maybe you should be
getting a mistrial legally
instead of having me do
what you're asking.
- We don't have time.
- I don't care!
What the hell's wrong
with you?
- Me?
- Yes, you.
Whose side are you on?
Oh, don't you dare
ask me that.
You know damn well
that I would break the law
for you and Mike,
but you are asking me
to have my friend do it,
and I am not going to. Donna...
Harvey,
even if I did ask Stephanie
and she said yes,
which she never would,
you would have
to drag innocent people
through the mud
to get this done.
And the Harvey I know
isn't that kind of person.
♪♪
Donna, what is going on?
Why are you so upset?
I'm not upset.
When you say, "I'm not upset,"
is that you acting?
Because it sucks.
What do you want
from me, Louis?
I want you to cut the bullshit
and tell me what's wrong.
I just saw you
leave Harvey's office
and five seconds later,
I saw him do the same thing.
Okay, Louis, what's wrong is
Harvey wants me
to get the names of the jurors
from my friend
in the U.S. Attorney's Office.
- He's trying to tamper?
- He's trying to get a mistrial.
Well, then why the hell
aren't you helping him do it?
- What?
- You heard me.
Why aren't you doing
whatever you can do help him?
I can't believe
you just said that to me.
Donna, listen to me,
if Harvey's doing this,
it means he thinks
he's going to lose.
And if he thinks
he's gonna lose,
it means he is gonna lose.
And if Mike goes down,
everybody goes down with him.
Don't you care
about that at all?
I'm getting a little tired
of people asking me
whether I care or not.
Because I do,
but not enough to push
women and children aside
to get on a lifeboat.
So, if that's all you came
in here to ask me,
why don't you be on your way?
♪♪
Okay, I got us some bread,
cheese, a little bit of wine,
and a picnic blanket.
So, I feel like we should
just go outside...
- I can't.
- What do you mean you can't?
Did the jury come back?
No, I, uh, I met a defendant.
He got caught in the act
of some petty larceny,
and, uh, they're trying
to railroad him, so I...
So, you're taking a case?
Rachel, he tried
to sell a couple of TVs
out of the back of a truck.
Now he's facing five years.
And somewhere in this building
there are 12 people
deciding whether or not
you're a fraud
and you're sitting here doing
the exact thing
that they're accusing you of.
They were right
in front of me.
His lawyer didn't show up...
- What is wrong with you?
- Whoa, Rachel, hey...
Don't you understand
that I am scared,
and that I am trying
to be supportive
and to keep a brave face,
but that I could lose you, Mike?
So, I understand
you wanting to be here,
but I don't understand you
not wanting to be with me.
♪♪
Come here.
Look, I'm scared too.
That's why I can't go home.
And I don't know
how I got into this, but...
I know that I need to do this,
Rachel.
♪♪
You really meant what you said
to the jury, didn't you?
Yeah.
And you said that
you fell in love with me
because of me wanting
to help other people.
Well, this guy needs my help.
And it may be the last time
I can do something like this.
Well, then let's figure out
a way to help him together.
♪♪
What's for lunch, David?
Quinoa salad.
Well, enjoy it,
because it's gonna be
your last meal
as a U.S. Attorney.
Mike Ross promised me
that if I gave him
those phone records,
he wouldn't say anything
to anyone.
I'm not Mike Ross,
and the way I see it,
there's no reason
for me not to tell Gibbs
about your shady past
unless you give me a reason.
And how am I supposed
to do that?
You pack up your lunch,
you take it down the street
to the courthouse cafe,
and you share a table
with whatever juror shows up
when they break for coffee
in about two hours.
What's this for?
For when you buy juror number
whatever a cup of coffee.
Jesus Christ, you want me
to give you a mistrial?
I do that, I could lose my job.
You're gonna lose your freedom
in two hours if you don't.
This is blackmail.
I call it atonement,
and today's the day
you face the music.
♪♪
- You were right.
- About what?
I shouldn't have been willing
to hurt innocent people
to get done
what I needed to get done.
Well, it sounds like
you got it done anyway.
I did, and you're gonna get
a call from Vanessa
as soon as she gets me
some pictures I need.
Harvey, you just said that you
shouldn't have been willing
to hurt innocent people, and...
I didn't hurt
any innocent people, Donna.
I found a guilty one.
Well, then I will
go tell Jessica
and I will let you know
the second Vanessa calls.
Donna.
What, Harvey?
Thanks.
I can't believe we found that.
I can't believe you did.
Rachel, this might give us
the leverage
to make sure Diaz doesn't do
any jail time at all.
- Do you really think so?
- Yeah, I do.
And it doesn't surprise me
'cause I also think that you're
gonna make a great lawyer.
Well, then spending our time
doing this
wasn't such a bad idea
after all.
Mr. Diaz, are you ready
to enter a plea?
Before we do, Your Honor,
I'd like to enter a motion
to invalidate the search
of Mr. Diaz's vehicle.
- What?
- The warrant was obtained
because of a phone call between
my client and his cousin,
and there's no evidence that
Mr. Alexander had authorization
to tap that call.
Your Honor,
we had other sources
for our search warrant.
- And what exactly were they?
- Mr. Alexander?
Objection, Your Honor.
Ms. Gibbs, this case isn't
under the Justice Department's
jurisdiction,
so, what exactly
are you objecting to?
I'm objecting to the fact
that this man is not a lawyer.
Your Honor, that is a lie.
And as we speak,
a jury is finding him guilty.
And until they do,
my bar number is active.
This is ridiculous,
Your Honor.
He is making a mockery
of this entire courtroom,
and I urge you
to at least delay this case
until his jury comes back.
Your Honor, the only reason
I'm representing Mr. Diaz,
is because his court-appointed
lawyer didn't show up,
and then that man attempted
to railroad him
into an outrageous plea deal.
Ms. Gibbs, he may be a fraud
in your court,
but since he hasn't been
convicted of anything,
he isn't one in mine.
And unless Mr. Alexander here
magically finds his voice,
Mr. Ross's motion
to exclude the search
of his clients vehicle passes.
Is it true
what that woman was saying?
Yes, they're deliberating
on his fate right now.
I don't give a shit
if they're deliberating.
Is he a fake or not?
You saw what he just did,
and he's about to cut you a deal
from four years behind bars
to maybe a few months.
So what do you think?
♪♪
What'd he say?
He's too pissed off
to make a deal right now,
but trust me, he'll calm down,
and then he will.
Mike, where are you going?
I'm gonna go try
and make a deal of my own.
♪♪
You ran out of there so fast
I didn't get a chance
to talk to you.
What exactly do you want,
Mr. Ross?
I want to make a deal.
You finally ready
to turn on Mr. Specter?
Nope, but I am ready
to plead guilty
and never practice law again
if you agree
to not go after any of
the partners at Person Specter.
That's the same bullshit
your boss said to me
when I first met him.
You're done practicing,
so I should just let you
get away with it?
Why would I listen to you now
if I didn't listen to him then?
Because you've got it written
all over your face.
Seeing me be a lawyer
makes you sick.
Right?
And if I win,
I'm gonna keep being a lawyer,
and it's gonna make you sick
for the rest of your life.
No deal.
It's not a good enough reason.
Okay, then let's try this one.
You've been at the same level
at the U.S. Attorney's Office
for a long time.
Now, a person
who can't get a conviction
against a man that
everyone thinks is a fraud,
well, that's a person
who's going nowhere.
This is a chance
for you to save face.
I don't need to save face
because they're gonna
find you guilty.
Are you sure about that?
'Cause you couldn't convince one
judge to make me stand down,
so what makes you think
you're gonna convince 12 jurors?
You know what, Mike?
The truth is,
you would have made
a good lawyer,
but you're not one,
and I'm gonna put you away.
♪♪
- What can I do for you, Donna?
- Harvey wanted me
to let you know
that as long as they don't
reach a verdict
in the next few hours,
you'll have a mistrial.
I'll have a mistrial?
What's on your mind, Donna?
Nothing.
I guess I just never thought
I'd see the day
when you thought
Harvey was gonna lose.
And who says
I think Harvey's going to lose?
- A mistrial says it.
- No,
it says I'm not willing
to take a chance
on 12 complete strangers.
It says you don't have faith
in him.
Donna, you don't know
what you're saying.
Don't I?
I know I'm not a lawyer,
but isn't it true that
if Mike gets found innocent,
there's no double jeopardy,
but if a mistrial happens,
they might come after him again
one day?
Yes, Donna, that is true,
but Harvey and I are banking
that never happens.
- And what if it does?
- Then I'm sorry,
but the truth is,
Mike Ross is the reason
why we're in this mess
in the first place,
and if it's a choice
between his peace of mind
down the road
and mine today,
I'm choosing mine.
Now, is that all?
♪♪
Louis Litt,
what a coincidence,
I was just about to call your
office, say I was your cousin,
and ask if you'd decided
to take me up on my offer.
Before I give you an answer,
I want to know,
if I give you proof
that Harvey knew about Mike,
will you give me immunity?
Well, that depends.
What do you have?
What do you mean,
what do I have?
I have me.
Well, that's not good enough.
Well, then what the hell
did you come to me for?
Because I was expecting
something more
than the testimony of a man
who's saving his own ass,
which gets me nothing.
Nothing?
I'd be giving you my word.
And I don't need your word.
I need proof.
Well, goddamn it,
I don't have any proof.
Well, then you're no good
to me.
And now I'm in the position of
having to work that much harder
to get both you
and your partners,
so, if you'll excuse me,
I need to get back to it, Louis.
♪♪
Donna, I need you
to start prepping a motion
for Mike to ask for a mistrial,
and we're gonna need to do it
first thing in the morning.
Harvey, I don't think
there's gonna be a mistrial.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I just got off the phone
with Vanessa.
David Green never showed.
♪♪
Whatever it is, Louis,
I don't have the time.
Well, you better find the time
because Anita Gibbs
just offered me a deal.
And I assume you told her
to shove it up her ass.
I did, but what I really
wanted to say was,
"Where do I sign?"
What the hell
did you just say to me?
Did you ever think
for one second,
what's gonna happen
if Mike gets convicted?
Mike is not gonna
get convicted.
- How could you be so sure?
- Because I'm gonna go get us
a goddamn mistrial.
That's not good enough.
I want to know
how you're gonna do that.
- None of your business.
- It is my business.
If you're gonna go
and break some more laws
like you did when you hired
the fraud in the first place.
What the hell do you want,
Louis?
You want me to give you
permission to cut a deal?
I want you
to give yourself up.
- Are you out of your mind?
- No, I am in my mind.
You can't get a mistrial,
that verdict comes back
the wrong way,
everyone in this entire firm
goes to jail
because of what you did.
- Go home, Louis.
- No, no, no,
I want you to say it.
You went out on your own,
you hired a fraud,
and this whole firm's
paying for it.
- Shut the hell up.
- You and you alone
are responsible for the carnage
of what's to come.
- Louis...
- Just say it!
You listen to me.
I may have hired a fraud,
but you're the one who had
the chance to turn him in
and you used his secret
to get what you always wanted.
So, don't come here
at the 11th hour
trying to blame me for having
to sleep in the bed
that you made.
I don't want to go to prison,
Harvey.
Then get out of my way,
and let me do what I do.
♪♪
What are you doing here?
I came to talk.
I gotta hand it to you,
you would have made
a good lawyer,
but you're even better
than I gave you credit for.
You got in my head.
You came here
to take my offer?
I came to make an offer
of my own.
You said you were giving me
a chance to save face,
but I let you get off
with no punishment.
As far as my career goes,
I might as well have
let them find you innocent.
What do you want?
You plead guilty,
do two years in prison,
and I won't go after
any of your friends.
There's no way
I agree to prison time
for a crime I didn't commit.
We're not in the courtroom
right now, Mike,
so let's cut the bullshit.
We both know you did this.
So if you don't want to pay,
then you take me up
on my original offer.
You do no time,
and all I need in return is
one name partner at your firm.
And I told you
that's never gonna happen.
Well, maybe you want
to talk to your fiancé
because the look
on her face says
she'd rather throw one of them
to the wolves
then see you in prison.
So it's up to you.
You take either one of my deals,
or you take your chances
with the jury.
Just remember,
tick tock.
♪♪
What did she mean,
"either deal"?
♪♪
She countered my offer.
- How long?
- Rachel...
How long would you have
to be away for?
- Two years.
- No, Mike.
No, you can't.
Do you know
how much time I'm facing
if I'm found guilty?
You're not gonna be
found guilty.
Seven years.
You're not gonna be
found guilty.
I saw you up there.
You were amazing.
You were that same empathetic,
brilliant man
that I fell in love with.
There's no way
the jury didn't see that.
Rachel, the jury is not
in love with me.
What if all they saw
when they looked at me
was the same fraud
that I've been
since the first day
I took that job?
Is that why you're thinking
about going to prison?
Because what?
You want to punish yourself
and that's your only way
to stop feeling guilty?
Yes, maybe that's
a part of it.
Okay, well it sounds like
it's all of it.
All I know,
is it's the only sure way
to put this to bed
and make sure that
the only person
who is hurt by it is me.
What about me?
Because all I did was love you!
♪♪
And if you take some deal
that sends you to prison...
Rachel, we can survive this...
Goddamn it, Mike,
they were in on it too!
♪♪
I'm not gonna rat them out.
And I'm not asking you to.
I'm just asking you
to have faith in yourself.
Okay, I will.
♪♪
Where the hell were you?
You mean why I wasn't
at the cafe?
I was just coming
to the conclusion
that you could take that threat
and shove it up your ass.
You think I'm bluffing you?
I don't give a shit whether
you're bluffing or not.
It made me sick to let Mike Ross
back into a court.
I'm not letting that
happen again.
I don't think you understand
what's gonna happen to you
when I call Anita Gibbs
tomorrow morning.
You never made a mistake?
You never did something
you regret?
What do you think I'm trying
to fix right now?
Look, if you don't help me,
making sure you never
practice law again
isn't gonna be
on my list of regrets.
You know, I've heard
a lot of people talk
about the great Harvey Specter,
completely unbeatable.
From what I'm seeing,
you're just a bully
who uses other people's fears
to get what he wants.
Well, it's not
gonna happen tonight,
because Mike Ross is
about to go to prison
and I'm not going to stop him.
♪♪
Harvey,
it's the middle of the night.
What are you doing here?
I had to see you.
I know you said
I couldn't do this anymore,
but I need to talk to you.
- Talk about what?
- About what I have to do.
You're gonna turn yourself in,
aren't you?
♪♪
Louis,
the jury didn't come back,
and since they went home,
I'm going home.
So, whatever it is, it's gonna
have to wait until tomorrow.
Tomorrow could be too late.
Too late for what?
This is all his fault.
You didn't start it.
I didn't start it.
He started it.
I'm not having
this conversation
behind Harvey's back.
That's okay.
I already had it to his face.
Tried to get him
to do the right thing
and turn himself in,
but he wouldn't.
I'm not going
to convince him to do that.
I know, because he'll never
be convinced.
Which is why we need
to go to Gibbs together...
- Louis...
- Goddamn it, Jessica,
we don't have any time!
Did it ever occur to you
that if Mike gets found guilty,
the first thing
Harvey is going to do
is walk in there and take
the bullet for me and you?
- No, it didn't.
- Well, it occurred to me.
We turn on him now,
we're not better
than Daniel Hardman
or Charles Forstman
or any of those other people
you despise.
Don't you see?
We could protect each other.
You don't want us to protect
each other, Louis.
You want someone to tell you
that what you're thinking
is okay,
and I'm not going to do that.
Jessica, please.
Good night, Louis.
♪♪
So you want to
turn yourself in
because some cheater
called you a bully?
No, Donna,
I want to turn myself in
because he was right.
I'm not unbeatable.
No, Harvey, I think
he made you feel guilty,
and now you're not
seeing clearly.
Donna...
Harvey, if it were anybody
other than Mike on trial
and you saw his closing,
do you think that
the jury would convict him?
I don't know, Donna,
but I can't afford
to be wrong about this.
Then let me as you a question:
Why aren't you talking
to Dr. Agard about this?
- How do you know about her?
- Because I do.
And I also know that
the last time you had
a huge decision to make,
you went to her and not me.
Because that was
about business
and this is personal.
No, Harvey,
you didn't go to her
because you know she won't try
to talk you out of this,
but I will.
- Donna...
- Don't do it.
Don't fall
on your sword again.
- I have to...
- No, you don't.
We might not win.
You don't always have
to be the hero.
I'm not doing it
Then why the hell
are you doing it?
Because
it's my goddamn fault.
No, Harvey, it's not.
It's Mike's fault
just as much as it is yours.
Then why should I be the one
to throw him under the bus?
Don't you get it?
I am not asking you
to throw him under the bus.
I am asking you
to believe that the two of you
are worthy
of being found innocent.
And what if I can't do that?
Then you can march yourself
down to Gibbs's office
in the morning
and turn yourself in.
♪♪
But I don't want you to do that.
Why not?
Because I think
you're worthy.
♪♪
And I don't want to lose you.
Harvey,
go to the courthouse
in the morning,
sit with Mike
until that verdict comes in,
and show him
that you have faith in him.
♪♪
Like I have faith in you.
Hello?
Yeah, this is him.
Yeah, yeah, I'll be right there.
How's the jury back so early?
Oh, it's not the jury.
It's the prosecutor
from the Diaz case.
He wants to talk.
♪♪
I may have hired a fraud,
but you're the one who had
the chance to turn him in,
and you used his secret to get
what you always wanted...
- Mr. Litt...
- So don't come in here...
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but your cousin Gertrude's
on the phone.
She said she needs to know
whether you found
that old mixed tape of hers.
Tell her I didn't.
Tell her it
must have gotten thrown out,
and to never ask me
about it again.
- Good.
- What do you mean "good"?
I been wanting to tell
Anita Gibbs to go to hell
since this whole thing started.
♪♪
Mr. Ross,
I'd like to make your client
an offer.
We're listening.
We don't want you, Mr. Diaz.
You said you were just driving
the truck and I believe you,
and we already have
the two gentleman
who committed the actual felony.
So, all you have to do
is testify against them,
and you walk.
What?
Holy shit.
No jail time?
- No jail time.
- Okay that's enough.
I need a moment with my client.
No, I don't need a moment.
I'll take it.
Mr. Diaz, listen to me.
Testifying against your friends
may not seem like a big deal
right now, but it's something
you are gonna have to live with
for the rest of your life.
I don't owe them anything,
and if I can get myself off,
that's what I'm gonna do.
He's only offering you this
because he doesn't have
a case against you.
He's a two-time loser.
I'll make a case against him.
Mr. Diaz...
Give me the pen.
You are making a huge mistake.
Yeah, well, I don't think so,
and if you were in my shoes,
you'd do the exact same thing.
I would never
send my friends to prison.
Yeah, well,
they find me guilty,
they're gonna send my friends
to prison anyways.
♪♪
Harvey, thank God.
The jury came back.
We have an hour.
- Where's Mike?
- I don't know.
What's the matter?
Harvey?
I have to go.
♪♪
- You know they're back, right?
- I don't care.
I'm ready to take your deal.
Which one?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net