You walked out of our session
because you didn't wants...
- To talk about your mother.
- You're insane.
And you're a self-serving
narcissist
Who will do or say anything
to get what he wants.
It's my sister's company.
I'll give you her business.
All you have to do
is handle her divorce.
All right, I'll do it.
Promise me you won't
sleep with Esther.
The last thing I want to do
is sleep with your sister.
Would you like to
take me home tonight?
I would.
Jack Soloff signed
Fletcher as a client
and now I have to let
McKernon go.
I'm sorry you're in
this position right now.
I'm not the one
who put you in it.
Jack Soloff is.
This is your last chance
to work with me.
Take it and you
have a future,
don't and you can go
ask Daniel Hardman for a job.
I'm ready to talk about
my mother.
Mom?
- Mom?
- Harvey.
What are you--
what are you doing here?
I got sent home
from school.
I threw up.
Oh, well,
let's get you to bed.
Hey, Lil,
I was thinking that--
- Who's that?
- Honey, you remember
our cousin--
my cousin Scott?
- Hey.
- No.
Course you do.
He's cousin Judy's brother.
I don't feel good.
Oh, yeah,
you're burning up.
Let's get you to bed.
And let's not tell Dad
about cousin Scott.
Okay? 'Cause they don't
get along.
Come on.
You poor thing.
"You poor thing."
That's what stuck with me.
She said "You poor thing,"
but she didn't give a shit
about me.
And did you know
what you saw?
No, I just knew
something was wrong.
And you didn't
tell your father?
She told me not to.
And you trusted her?
I did.
Harvey, I never thought
I'd be saying this to you,
but I'm proud.
It took an amazing amount
of courage to tell me that.
- We're not gonna hug, are we?
- No, we're not.
But it does feel good
to end a session
on a positive note
for once.
Peterson case, huh?
I remember when I used to
handle that asshole.
Funny, I don't remember
inviting you into my office.
Oh, yeah, that's right,
it must be because
it's something
that I would never do.
Listen, Mike, I know I pulled
some shit with you and Louis,
but I'm here to
make things right with you.
Not interested.
Just hear me out.
What the hell is this?
It's a case that's
tailor-made for someone
with a hedge fund
background.
New York Teacher's
Pension Fund
just lost 30% of their
annual income.
They put half their portfolio
in derivatives without hedging?
Not just derivatives.
Derivatives created
and marketed by Straussbank
to increase
their own revenue.
Sorry, Jack,
I don't work with people
that I don't trust
and I don't trust somebody
who comes to me saying
their trying
to make things right
without a good reason.
You want the reason?
Jessica told me to.
Yeah, well,
she didn't tell me.
And until she does...
you can get out
of my office.
The Simon brief
is on your desk
and I moved your Wednesday
noon meeting to five.
Why'd you do that?
Because Anthony Kimball's
most honest
with a drink in him.
And on top of that,
I wouldn't want you
to have to work too hard
- on your birthday.
- What? It's not my birthday.
Oh, come on,
you can tell me.
What is it? 48? 49?
- The big 6-0?
- A: I'm not the one pushing 60.
You better not be
talking to me.
B: If it were,
I'd be drinking with someone
a lot prettier
than Anthony Kimball.
Then why is Wednesday night
permanently blocked out
on your calendar?
- Donna.
- Harvey.
- You look busy.
- I look busy because I am busy.
Too busy to join me
at Del Posto on Wednesday night?
Harvey, we don't need
to do that anymore.
Then why did you leave it
permanently blocked off
on my calendar?
Because I did that
a long time ago
and when I left your desk
I forgot to undo it.
Then why don't we pretend
that you forgot
to undo it on purpose?
I don't work for you
anymore.
What would we
be celebrating?
Instead of celebrating
the day you came to my desk,
how about we celebrate...
two weeks of being
on decent terms?
It's only been
a week and a half.
Seriously, Donna?
I don't just want to be
on decent terms.
I want to get back
to being friends.
That's really nice,
Harvey.
See you Wednesday night.
♪ ♪
Thank you.
Jessica.
What a pleasant surprise.
I think we both know
that it isn't.
- Pleasant? Or a surprise?
- Either.
Because we also
both know that Jack Soloff
came to see you
before I did.
Is there a problem
with that?
There is if you're colluding
with one of my partners
to take over my firm.
Jack came to me
asking for advice about
how to land a new client.
He was so determined
I was suddenly reminded
- of Harvey's first client.
- McKernon Motors.
A client he cared so much
about he gave up a promotion
just to keep his word.
It's hard to forget
a move like that.
It's also hard to forget
your history
of worming your way
back into my firm.
So, if you're looking
for someone to mentor, Daniel,
go find yourself
an afterschool program.
But stay the hell
outta my house.
Jessica...
I have no interest
in your shitty firm
and I don't have to
enter your house to damage it.
You did that
all by yourself
the second you let
Fletcher Engines go.
Jack tell you that?
Fletcher Engines
told everyone that.
And you told your entire firm
that you care more about
Harvey Specter
than you do about them.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a meeting
in my new office.
It's so nice
to be back in the city.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 5x07 ♪
Hitting Home
Original Air Date on August 5, 2015
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Clean out your things and get
the hell out of my firm.
- What?
- I gave you one last chance
to play nice,
and you blew it.
- How did I blow it?
- Oh, you're going to deny
that you've been spreading
word around the office
that I told you to drop
Fletcher Engines?
Yes. I'm gonna deny it,
because I didn't do it.
Then how the hell
does everybody know?
Because I told them
when I signed Fletcher.
Which I wouldn't have done
if I'd known
you were gonna drop them
because it made me
look like shit.
Well, it didn't make me come
out smelling like a rose either.
And your mentor
seems to have known that.
He's not my mentor.
I went to him for advice,
and all it got me
was almost getting fired.
But you said you'd
give me one more chance,
and I've been trying
to take it.
Give me one good example
of that.
I approached Mike Ross
to work with me this morning.
And by the way,
he spat in my face.
Jessica...
you made your point
and I heard you.
If you're just gonna
fire me anyway,
why give me the chance
in the first place?
A joke?
Uh, do you hear me laughing?
10% is 11% more
than you deserve.
I--
What the hell?
This better be important.
I was just about
to close a deal.
I just heard a rumor
that Jack Soloff
signed Fletcher Engines.
That's ridiculous--everyone
knows we can't sign Fletcher
if we represent McKernon.
I'll tell you what
everyone knows, Louis.
Jack signed Fletcher.
Jessica forced him
to drop them,
and the only reason Jack
would have done that
in the first place is if
you were fired by McKernon.
Harvey, I can explain.
God damn it.
I knew it.
Just wait a minute.
Harvey, listen to me.
Jack set us up.
He acted as if he was
cooperating
when all along he was looking
to blow up the deal.
Why the hell didn't you
come to me when it happened?
Because we wanted
to fix it ourselves.
Wanting to fix it yourself
is the cause of every problem
you and I have ever had,
and now you're teaching
that bullshit to Mike?
You know what, Mike and I
worked on that deal together,
and we kicked ass.
I'm happy, Mike's happy,
Dominic's happy,
and I'll tell you why.
Because I'm a damn good
attorney, and you know it.
So if that's the only thing
you came in here for,
I would like to close
my deal now.
Mr. Specter,
Esther Litt just called.
She has an urgent matter.
Needs to see you right away.
Did she say
what it was about?
No. Just not to tell
her brother.
Oh, so this is where the little
people get their caffeine.
I'm guessing you're not here
to have a breakfast bar.
I've never had a breakfast bar
in my life.
I want to thank you
for taking on that pension case
- with Jack Soloff.
- I didn't take on
the pension case
with Jack Soloff.
- Yes, you did.
- Jessica, no.
You can't make me work
with that man.
I can make you work
with the goddamn window
washers if I want to.
And if you don't do this,
you might find yourself
dangling 50 stories
above the ground.
- Why?
- Because I asked Jack
to make peace,
and you're the one
he chose to reach out to,
so you're the one to do this.
I guess I meant
why don't you just fire him?
If I fired every
ambitious attorney
that ever took me on,
there'd be nobody left here
but me and Harold Gunderson.
Wait a second--you know
who Harold Gunderson is?
I know who everybody is.
And before you say
one more word,
if I ever start handing out
pink slips for troublemakers,
you'd be the first in line.
Right.
I came here as soon
as I got your message.
I don't do that
for most people.
So much for hard to get.
I think we're past that.
Did Jeffrey
get greedy again?
No. A man named
Kenneth Jackson
is claiming
my nut-free muffins
put him
in anaphylactic shock.
What happened?
Too much gluten?
- Not enough gluten?
- Harvey,
this isn't funny.
This is my company,
and my entire brand
is based on quality.
I'm sorry.
I'll take it seriously.
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
Thank Louis.
Because he's gonna
handle this case.
What?
This is a business matter,
not personal.
And I'm not stealing
Louis's client.
You're not stealing me.
You already handled my divorce.
Are you gonna tell me that Louis
is a better lawyer than you?
No. I'm gonna tell you
that he's a damn good lawyer,
and he'd do anything
to project you.
That's not the point.
I need this to go away
quietly,
and Louis doesn't do
anything quietly.
- Then tell him that.
- He never listens to me.
Then get him to listen
or get another law firm,
because I'm not
taking this case.
Harvey, I don't need
another firm.
I need you.
You know what I think?
I think you want to go
out with me again,
and you came to me with this
because you're afraid
to say it to me.
I don't believe you!
You think I concocted
a lawsuit against my own company
just to tell a man
I've already been with
that I like him?
Sure looks that way.
In that case,
I guess I do have
the wrong man for the job.
Thank you for taking the time.
♪ ♪
Please let him know
I'm here.
Esther.
What are you doing here?
I thought I was very clear
yesterday.
I'm not taking
your case.
You were clear.
I'm here to see Louis.
But it's nice to see
your ego's as strong as ever.
I'm sorry...and I didn't mean
to be such a dick yesterday.
It's okay, Harvey.
I know what you did.
You accused me of what
you accused me of,
so I will go to Louis.
So you're not mad at me?
It was actually sweet...
in a dick-ish sort of way.
That's my specialty.
Thanks, Harvey.
Hi, Esther,
I'm Donna Paulsen.
- I'm the--
- I know who you are.
You're the best thing
that's ever happened
to my brother.
Oh. Well, you don't know
the half of it.
Anyway, I hope I didn't
put you to too much trouble
- on short notice.
- Oh, nonsense.
Louis was thrilled when
he heard you were coming in.
What was so goddamn important
that I had to cancel
my entire morning?
I swear he was
happy to do it.
And you and I
are having lunch
the second whatever it is
you're here for is over.
- Want a sip?
- Is that a prunie?
No! I can't believe
you still drink that crap.
You know I've got
Grandma Gertie's spastic colon.
What he hell
are you doing here?
I'm being sued.
Holy shit.
Your shitty muffins really
did give someone salmonella.
It's not salmonella,
and Louis, this is serious.
- It's my company.
- All right, I'm sorry.
Well, does he have
a leg to stand on?
Of course not.
I do an audit of every
supplier every three months.
Are you sure?
Because if we're gonna
go after him with
everything we've got--
Louis, we're not going
after him at all.
I want to settle this
quickly and quietly.
Esther...
you settle,
you look guilty.
This is a shakedown,
pure and simple.
I know that,
but I don't care.
This is a business
decision.
And that's why I'm trying
to stop others
from doing the same thing.
I'm telling you,
- I know what I'm doing.
- I didn't say you don't.
No, you're just telling me
how to do my job.
Louis, I came to you
because you're my brother,
and I am telling you,
this is what I need.
All right, we'll settle.
Thank you, Louis.
No, thank you.
For what?
For not going to Harvey.
Once he handled
your divorce,
I would have thought you'd want
him to handle everything.
♪ ♪
Harvey,
make yourself comfortable.
Can I get you a mimosa?
No, thanks.
I just stopped by
to eat my morning bagel
and ask why Jack Soloff
tried to sign Fletcher Engines
and you didn't tell me.
I didn't tell you because
I was busy fixing it.
And did fixing it
involve figuring out
that he went
to Daniel Hardman?
As a matter of fact,
it did.
You saw Hardman.
I did,
and it didn't take long,
because he's back
in New York.
Let me guess.
He said he had nothing to do
with any of this.
Yep.
He said he was
just giving Jack
some helpful advice.
Well, I think it's time
we gave Jack
some helpful advice
of our own,
like get your ass
another job.
Now, Harvey,
I met with Jack.
He says he's done
confiding in Hardman,
and I've decided to consider
the matter closed.
You telling me you trust
that clown?
Now, I may look
damn good for my age,
but I wasn't born
yesterday.
You want to know how deep
it goes with him and Hardman,
- don't you?
- I sure as hell do.
Which is why I asked Mike
to work with Jack
and play nice,
and you better not
get in the way.
This doesn't look like
a "forgive me
for being a dick" card.
It's not.
It's a 28-page interrogatory
for Straussbank.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
You told me you don't
work with people
you don't trust.
Neither do I.
You don't have to trust me
to understand
that the shady shit
at Straussbank
starts at the top.
All the way to the top?
There's a 50-50 chance
that the CEO knows.
The CFO had to know.
All we have to do
is get their emails.
That's easy.
We agree not to pursue
criminal charges, they'll
hand emails over right now.
We can't give up the threat
of going to prison.
That's what gives us leverage.
We have to go to court.
Going to court
will take forever.
I just went through
the same thing with Robert Zane.
Why don't you pick up
the phone
and ask him
who turned out to be right?
You know,
I heard you were cocky,
but I had no idea.
You're the one who came
to me looking to make peace.
You wanna make peace
or not?
All right.
We'll try it your way.
Rachel, what can I do
for you?
I heard about Esther,
and I was hoping
I could help.
I appreciate the offer,
but I'm gonna take care
of this one myself.
And I'm not trying
to interfere.
I just thought it would
be nice to learn
from the most talented,
diligent,
and respected partner
that we have here.
Yeah, you're just trying
to butter me up.
Is it working?
Handsome.
Listen to me.
She's my sister.
She's being sued.
Last time she had a problem,
she went to Harvey,
but this time
she's coming to me,
and I'm not gonna farm
any of it out.
Can you understand that?
The reason
I want on this case
is that I admire Esther
and her company,
and if someone's coming at her
with a frivolous lawsuit,
then...I don't care
how little I do.
I just want to help you.
Paperwork's right here.
Your Honor, as you can see,
there's been clear negligence
at best,
- deliberate deception at worst.
- Not to mention
a breach of fiduciary duty.
I'm inclined
to agree.
Your honor, the only
thing that's clear
is his clients chose
a risky investment.
That's not deception
on our part.
The deception is he created
those derivatives,
he knew how risky they were,
and he sold them to us anyway.
I have $2 billion
in investment funds.
You think I review
every investment?
I don't know, but you sure
as hell reviewed this one.
- And where's your proof?
- We don't have any...yet.
Which is why we're requesting
access to these emails.
This isn't about
getting their emails.
This is about determining
if trial's moving forward.
And it is.
I'll set the email
discovery hearing
- for three weeks.
- Three weeks?
Uh, your Honor,
my wife has surgery
in three weeks.
I'd like to request
an additional month.
Bullshit she has surgery.
Scheduled C-section
at Columbia Presbyterian.
Then put someone else
on the case.
- That's not how it works.
- If I may...
If we agree not to pursue
criminal charges in this matter,
will you give us the emails
within the week?
You agree to that
right here,
I'll give 'em to you
tomorrow.
Then we have a deal.
Wanna tell me what kind of
kickback you're getting?
- Excuse me?
- You went behind my back.
I didn't do anything
behind your back.
I did it in front of
your face.
You know what I mean--
you gave up on leverage
by handing him a get out
of jail free card,
which means you're either
in their pocket
or you're using this case
so you can sign them
once it's over.
- What did you just say to me?
- You heard me.
You shook that guy's hand like
you were his goddamn cousin.
You listen to me.
If they wanted to be my client,
I'd take them.
But I didn't do that
to kiss his ass.
I did it to
get what we needed.
We already had
what we needed.
No, we didn't.
We had a hearing on it
in seven weeks,
and that C-section bullshit
was just the tip of the iceberg.
Between now and then,
they'd have figured out a way
to put it off
for another two years.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
I said I would try it your way,
and it didn't work.
Well, now those emails
are coming.
Are you gonna help me
or not?
Louis, I need to talk
to you--we have a problem.
- What's wrong?
- What's wrong
is Kenneth Jackson's
lawyer.
Her name's Lisbeth Wexler,
and this isn't her first
frivolous suit.
Well, it never is
with these people.
That doesn't mean
we can't settle.
Okay.
You don't understand.
I went through dozens
of her cases.
Every time she gets
an offer,
she threatens
to go public with it.
- Shit.
- What?
That's exactly
what I was afraid of.
Okay, well, then you know
it's not a big deal.
We can handle it, but we
can't give them an offer.
No, you don't understand.
I tried to tell Esther
this might happen,
but then she made me promise
that I would make this thing
go away without any trouble.
Okay, well, if we don't do
something other than settle,
she's in for a hell
of a lot more trouble.
He didn't really say that.
Oh, not only did he say it,
but I had to transcribe it
word for word
off his Dictaphone.
- What?
- No, I just realized
I haven't thought about
Jack Soloff
and his bullshit
for two hours.
Glad we did this, Harvey.
Me, too.
We should do it more often.
Well, I'm not sure how Mitchell
would feel about that.
Who's Mitchell?
He's the man
that I've been seeing
for the last six weeks.
He's...
he's smart
and he's funny and...
best of all, he has nothing
to do with the practice of law.
I'm happy for you,
Donna.
Thanks.
And the reason I told you
is so that you'll know
that I'm not jealous
when I say...
you need to tell Louis
you've been
sleeping with Esther.
- What?
- Oh, please.
It took me all of two seconds
to put it together
after I saw you two mooning over
each other this morning.
It's not what you think.
We bonded together
during her divorce proceedings.
Harvey, you said
you wanted to be friends.
This is me
being your friend.
Friends don't accuse
each other of things.
I'm not accusing you.
I'm looking out for you.
How is that
looking out for me?
Because, like I said,
you need to tell him.
Well, you know what?
I don't need to do that
because, for once,
your radar is off.
We haven't been
sleeping together.
We slept together one time.
What difference does
that make?
You promised him
you wouldn't do it at all.
Donna, Louis isn't rational
on his best days
with issues that don't
involve his sister,
Now, how is he going to take it
if I do what you're asking?
And how do you think
he's gonna react
when he finds out
you kept this from him?
- He's not gonna find out.
- Yes, he is.
Because I didn't have
to be me to see the way
you two looked at each other.
And someday Louis is gonna
see that, too.
Donna, I appreciate you
telling me this as a friend.
Now, as a friend,
I'm telling you
to mind your own business.
I was right.
You cut them some side deal.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I went through
all their emails
and I found them nothing
tying them to anything.
Which means you knew
they would leave some emails out
and you let it go
to get something out of it.
I didn't know they would
leave anything out,
but I thought they might
and I am gonna get
something out of it,
but it's not
what you think.
- What are you talking about?
- Your idea
of threatening prison
was right,
but nobody
ever went to jail
for selling
shitty securities.
They go to jail
for destroying evidence.
So, instead of proving
to some jury
that doesn't understand
securities law
that these guys knew the risks
of their investments--
All we have to do is prove
they deleted some emails.
I'm sorry.
Take a seat.
You know that's
the second time in two days
that you jumped right to me
being the bad guy?
Well, you have to admit,
my experience
with how
you treated me and Louis
was you being the bad guy.
Fair enough.
But were you there
when Louis lied to my face
about backing me in a meeting?
Or when he told Jessica
that I did something awful
that he, in fact, did?
No, I wasn't.
But you do know him
and what he's capable of.
And you're somehow
on good terms with him.
I'm on good terms with him
because I've seen
other sides of him.
Well, I have
other sides, too.
I may have done
some office backstabbing,
but I have never done
anything to indicate to you
that I would
do something illegal.
Which is what you
came in here accusing me of.
Okay, Jack.
You can have a chance
to show me another side
of yourself, too.
I told you
to settle this thing!
And I'm trying to.
Then why did I just
get a notice that the FDA
is investigating my company?
- What?
- What did you do?
I was gonna settle,
but then Rachel found out
their lawyer has history
of blackmailing companies
so our only option
was to counter-sue.
You filed a counter-suit against
my explicit instructions?
You know what, Esther?
You came to me for help,
and I don't tell you
how to bake your muffins.
Because you don't know the
first thing about my business.
And you don't know
the first thing about mine.
I don't have to.
I know you.
And you've got a chip
on your shoulder
the size of Montana
and when it comes out,
- you make everything worse.
- You know what, Esther?
I was right to do
what I did.
And, for once,
I'm not gonna let you
treat me like
I'm less than you.
Less than me?
Yes, less than you!
I'm always your
buffoon brother.
- Well, not this time.
- You had no right to do this
- without asking me!
- I didn't ask you because
- you wouldn't have listened.
- No, you never listen!
Which is why I wanted to go to
Harvey in the first place!
- What?
- You heard me.
How could you
betray me like that?
I wasn't betraying you.
I was looking out
for myself.
If you were looking out
for yourself,
then why did you lie to me
about going to him?
Because you're
always jealous
whenever I ask anyone else
to do anything.
You're my brother, Louis,
not my boyfriend.
If you wanted Harvey so much,
why don't you go to him
right now?
I can't.
Because when I went to him,
he told me
I should trust you.
- He really said that?
- He didn't just say that.
He said you were
a damn good lawyer.
I am a damn good lawyer.
But I should have
told you.
Well...
What are we
gonna do now?
That depends on if you
think you can trust me or not.
I can.
- Morning, Louis.
- Good morning.
Where the hell were you?
I text you like 18 times.
Yes, and if it had been
an emergency,
- I would have called you back.
- It was an emergency.
Louis, running out of
paper clips is not an emergency.
I know,
it's just that I...
needed you,
and I couldn't reach you,
and that's never
happened before.
I was having dinner
with Harvey.
- Harvey?
- Yes.
We're trying
to stay friends.
- Friends?
- Yes, friends.
I'm not going back
to him, Louis.
What?
I know that.
How'd it go?
It was fine.
He didn't happen
to bring up Esther, did he?
What?
Why would he do that?
Because apparently,
she went to him
before she came to me.
Well, he did handle
her divorce.
I know, it's just...
you don't think it's possible
that anything happened
between them, do you?
I don't know, Louis,
I mean...
Look, I do know
that we talked about
a lot of things
last night,
and Esther
wasn't one of them.
You're right.
Harvey would never
make a promise like that to me
and then break it.
I'm glad you had
a nice dinner, Donna.
♪ ♪
What the hell is this?
It's a stack of emails
they left out.
- How did you get them?
- Doesn't matter
how I got them.
It matters that I got them.
It does matter, because
if you got them illegally,
then we can't use them,
and you know it.
I didn't get them
illegally.
Then why won't you
tell me where you got them?
Because there are
some things
I like to keep
to myself.
And didn't you give me
a speech
about getting to know
different sides of you?
Well, this is
a different side of me.
Are you gonna trust it
or not?
Gentlemen, I'm so glad
you could see us
on such short notice.
Well, you scratched
our backs.
I think we can
scratch yours.
What kind of settlement
are you looking for?
We're not looking for
a settlement.
We're looking for you
to give up your CEO.
- What?
- He's not giving anyone up.
You've waived your rights
to criminal charges
in this matter.
Yeah, we're not talking
about this matter.
We're talking about
conspiracy to hide evidence.
That's 200 emails
from your analyst
laughing about the suckers
that you all ripped off.
Shit.
Relax. There's no way
he got those legally.
- You're right, we didn't.
- What?
God damn it,
you told me--
I know what I told you,
Jack,
but you wouldn't have
let me come here
if I told you the truth.
And the truth...
is that we also got
this one illegally.
That's your CEO saying
that if push comes to shove,
he's gonna throw you
under the bus.
And you really want to
take a chance
that we won't figure out a way
to find these others legally?
You've got 200 people
in your firm?
We're gonna offer every
single one of them immunity
- to admit they exist.
- And when they do,
either your CEO
is going down,
or you are.
♪ ♪
Glad you came
to your senses
- and called us to settle.
- Well, clearly, Mr. Jackson
has suffered
great physical harm.
I just don't want
anyone else to be hurt.
Yeah, that'd be a shame.
Then who would you have to sue?
- Excuse me?
- Sit down.
Now, we're here
because my sister
wanted to give you $50,000
to make this thing go away,
but I didn't listen to her.
So I'm gonna throw in
an extra $50,000 of my own.
It doesn't matter.
Because if you think
we're gonna settle for $100,000,
you're wasting our time.
The $100,000
isn't to settle this.
It's to have your client admit
that you approached him
after he had a public episode
and then instructed him to say
that it was within five minutes
of eating one of our muffins.
- You have no proof of that.
- No, we don't.
But he's on record
for making a false statement
to a federal agency,
which means
when we do have proof,
you're gonna be in prison
for a very, very long time.
- $100,000?
- Kenneth,
you'll get
20 times that when we win.
Maybe this'll help you
decide, Kenneth.
- What's that?
- It's a list
of all the other people
you've done this with.
- What?
- Oh, did you think
you were her first?
You were not.
Whoever rolls over first
gets the money,
then the rest get to line up
for orange jump suits.
That's enough.
We're leaving.
What do I have to do?
Esther, what are you
doing here?
I came to
give you this.
This is a $100,000 check.
It's for Kenneth Jackson.
- We're splitting this.
- No, we're not.
You were right.
I never should have
tried to settle with him
in the first place.
You saved me
more than that.
I don't know what to say.
Say you'll forgive me.
I don't think
you're a buffoon, Louis,
and I never have.
But I didn't realize
how good a lawyer you were
until I saw it myself.
I appreciate that.
But I know how hard
you worked
to make your business
happen,
and I know
what you gave up,
and there wasn't
a snowball's chance in hell
that I was gonna let
someone take advantage of you.
Thanks, Louis.
Thank you.
Hey.
Do you wanna
get dinner tonight?
I can't tonight.
How about tomorrow night?
Tomorrow night is perfect.
What do you say
we also invite Donna?
That'd be really nice.
Come by just to tell me
how impressive I was today?
I came by to ask you
why you still don't trust me.
Who says I don't trust you?
You didn't tell me
that evidence
was obtained illegally.
Jack...I told you
the truth.
Those emails weren't
obtained illegally because...
they weren't even real.
What?
I know how traders talk.
I know exactly
what they'd say, so...
I just wrote them myself.
Are you shitting me?
Take a look.
I lied to you
because to get them to believe
they were illegal
I had to get them
to believe they were real.
And you needed me to be
pissed to help you do that.
Told you to trust me.
You know what?
I do.
So to tell you
the truth,
when we started
this thing,
I was just doing it
to kiss your ass
so Jessica
would forgive me.
But...
you're the real deal.
I see what Harvey
sees in you.
Thanks, Jack.
Maybe now you can give
Harvey a second chance too.
It's just everything
comes so easy to him.
Jessica plucks him
from the mailroom.
Youngest senior partner ever.
Well...
I been busting my ass
for 20 years.
Nobody ever does anything
like that for me.
Well, I'll tell you
something, Jack.
He's got his own problems
just like everyone else.
And if you want to
get along with me,
you better figure out
a way to get along with him.
Gretchen, were we at
with the Cabrillo claim?
- I have to go.
- I'm not Gretchen.
And that's too bad
for you,
because she's still
in the habit
of covering for you.
Covering for me for what?
I told you Louis was gonna
find out about Esther.
And I told you
it's none of your business.
Well, it became my business
when Louis asked me
about it yesterday,
and I had to lie to his face
just to get him
to leave it alone.
I didn't ask you
to do that.
Yes, you did,
and you know it.
Donna, I don't have
time for this.
- I have an appointment--
- What appointment?
I checked with Gretchen
so you couldn't get out
of this with some made-up thing.
- Your calendar's empty.
- You know what, Donna?
One thing I learned
the hard way
is not to tell your
secretary everything.
Be careful, Harvey.
Because you're about to learn
the hard way
that I may have lied
to Louis about this once,
but I am never,
never gonna do it again.
Harvey?
Harvey, where have you been
for the last 40 minutes?
What are you talking about?
I mean, you scheduled a session
so that we could
explore your mother,
and you've been telling me
some meaningless story
about when you got stung
by a bee.
I got in a fight
with Donna.
Fight about what?
She wants me to tell Louis
that I slept with
his sister.
Why, exactly, does she
want you to do that?
Because I promised Louis
that I wouldn't,
and she thinks
he's gonna find out.
Why would you make
a promise like that to Louis
if you had no intention
of keeping it?
I had every intention
of keeping it.
It's Louis's sister.
But then I met her, and...
it happened.
Well, why don't you
just tell him that?
Because he's like
a four-year-old,
and on top of that,
he doesn't own her.
- She's his sister.
- But this isn't about
his relationship
with his sister.
It's about his relationship
with you.
You made him a promise.
Yeah, and as long as he doesn't
find out I broke it,
- it doesn't matter.
- And in light of the story
you told me the other day,
that's probably what someone
you know very well
said to herself.
Are you shitting me?
You're comparing me to her?
I most certainly am.
Right down to you putting
Donna in a position
- not to say anything.
- Donna is not
an eight-year-old boy,
and I'm not cheating on my wife.
No, but you're putting
two people you care about
in positions
to feel betrayed.
- Betrayed?
- Yes.
Like when someone has an affair
with someone else.
Okay--you don't get
to say that to me.
It's my job to say
things like that to you.
Then you don't know
what you're talking about,
because I've lived
my whole life
- not to be her.
- And when people do that,
they very often become that very
thing in a different way.
Well, I'm not goddamn her!
Well, then, you better
take a look in the mirror.
Because you made a promise,
snuck behind someone's back
to break it, and when
confronted with that fact,
you're denying
all responsibility.
That sounds like
an affair to me.
You wanted to see me?
Do you know how hard I worked to
get a view like this?
Full scholarship to Vassar.
Three years Harvard Law,
and one year
as the first black woman
to clerk in the Third Circuit.
And I'm not going to waste
all that hard work
just to let someone
take everything away.
Jessica,
as far as I can tell,
Jack Soloff is holding up
his end of the bargain.
He's doing more than that.
He just sent out an email
nominating you
for Junior Partner.
And you're gonna figure out
a way to turn it down.
- What?
- Go ahead, take a minute.
Congratulations.
You've earned it.
You are the best associate
I have ever seen.
Now,
these are your options.
Medical issues.
Family emergency.
You're just not ready.
Whatever it is,
you simply cannot accept
a junior partnership
at this time.
Jessica,
no one turns down partner.
Well, they do now.
Because I'm not sending out
a press release
announcing Mike Ross
of Harvard just got promoted.
- Then don't send one out.
- You're not hearing me.
No, you're not hearing me.
What do you think
is gonna happen
when word gets out
that I was offered the one thing
that every associate dreams of,
and I turned it down?
Nothing's going to happen.
Because you're going to
put your mind
to finding a good reason
with as much enthusiasm
as you did bullshitting your way
into this job
in the first place.
♪ ♪
- What is this?
- You know what it is.
Portfolio of business
I want you to take
to Pearson Specter for me.
I'm not doing it.
This is an opportunity
for you, Jack.
No, Daniel,
it's an opportunity for you,
and I'm not interested
in carrying your water.
Am I mistaken, or did we
not have this discussion?
We discussed it...once.
I remember.
It was during that same
conversation we had
when you came to me
for advice on the best way
to stab Harvey
in the back.
I get it.
You did me a favor.
But I'm finished.
I don't want your advice
or your shortcuts anymore,
because all it did
was almost get me fired.
So please...
just take this.
Ah, you've always
been a grinder, Jack.
What's that
supposed to mean?
I admire it.
But you're not just
a grinder.
You have a chip
on your shoulder.
And the thing I've noticed
about people with chips
on their shoulder
is that somewhere
along the way
they went to great
lengths to get 'em off.
I got the chip off
my shoulder.
I got Jessica's respect.
She doesn't respect you.
And that's not
the chip I'm talking about.
Don't call me again.
♪ ♪
Esther,
what are you doing here?
I'm actually going out
to dinner with Louis and Donna.
Well, thanks for
the invitation,
but that's the last thing in the
world I want to do right now.
That's not why I'm here.
I was thinking about
what you said
about why
I called you first
and then about
how you handled it.
And I thought...
maybe you might want to
take me out this weekend.
Esther, what do you
think's going on between us?
- I don't know, I just--
- You don't know?
Well, I'll tell you.
We had a moment.
It was nice, but I'm not
interested in sneaking around.
Who said anything
about sneaking around?
I did.
And you just got divorced.
And you're a mother of two,
and I'm not gonna
be the reason that--
- That what?
- That nothing.
Why don't you just
go out to your dinner?
Harvey, tell me
what's going on.
What's going on is,
you asked me out and I said no,
so please
just leave me alone.
Harvey--
I said leave me alone.
♪ ♪
Did you make the reservation
at Sarabeth's?
For the seventh time, yes.
And why was it so important
that it be there anyway?
Because their muffins are ten
times better than Esther's,
and I just
want her to know it.
I thought you two
made progress.
She's still my sister.
And I can't let her think that
she's the best at something.
- Okay.
- Hey.
Wait--what's wrong?
You look upset.
Nothing's wrong.
I'm just not feeling very well.
It looks like tonight's
not a good night after all.
No, no, no, you're upset.
It's not that, Louis.
I just don't feel well.
Please,
let's just reschedule.
I'm gonna just call
the restaurant and--
Wait a second, wait a second,
wait a second.
She came all the way down here
just to cancel?
I don't know, Louis,
I mean, maybe she was
already on her way
over here and--
Did she just come
from Harvey's office?
Because that's the direction
she came from,
not the elevators.
I don't know, Louis.
What do you want me to say?
"I don't know"
is exactly what you said
when I asked you
if you thought
there was anything going on
between Harvey and Esther,
and now you're saying it
again.
But you're Donna,
and you know everything.
I'm sorry, Louis.
I do know.
- What are you gonna do?
- None of your business.
Stay out of it.
You've done enough.
♪ ♪
You and I are gonna
have a talk right now.
Hey, whatever it is...
it can wait.
I need to tell you
something.
Does it have something to do
with why my sister
just left here too upset
to go out to dinner?
You piece of shit.
I knew it.
What'd you do to her now?
I didn't do anything
to her, Louis.
And when I say now,
I mean as opposed to before
when you slept with her.
That's right--Donna, the one
you tried to steal from me
at dinner the other night
told me--
Calm down, I didn't try
to steal any--
You made a promise
to me!
And even after
I told you
about when Esther and I
were kids
and the boys used me
to get to her,
you still went ahead
and betrayed me.
Louis, it had already
happened,
and I was just now
about to tell you.
Bullshit!
You were never gonna tell me.
You were gonna keep it
to yourself
- till the day you died.
- Louis, you have to believe me.
I swear I was
just about to tell you.
What you're about to do
is get your ass kicked.
All right, watch yourself.
Don't threaten something
you can't handle.
You don't think
I can handle you?
You also thought I was
too stupid to find out,
but I did find out.
I found out that you're nothing
but a lying, cheating--
I didn't cheat with Esther.
It was two grown people
making a goddamn decision
for themselves.
Well, that decision ended
with her walking out of here
near tears
because she didn't have
all the facts,
like the fact that
you're a serial womanizer
who can't stand when
anyone else
- has anything.
- Shut the hell up!
So he takes whatever
woman's in sight...
- I'm telling you.
- Because he's so messed up
from whatever goddamn
thing happened to him
- in his pathetic childhood...
- Shut the hell up!
He can't--
♪ ♪
Harvey.
Get away from me.
You get the hell out of here.
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net