I got up early,
so I could figure out
if there's anything around here
that I could stand living with.
- You want to move in together?
- If the offer still stands.
Are you kidding me?
You slept with Quentin
while he was married to me.
I asked you back then
if anything had started
before we were separated.
You said it hadn't.
'Cause I didn't want
to hurt you.
Here's
to your new partnership.
I fronted your buy-in.
How could you do that?
I did it
as a romantic gesture.
Yeah, well,Pretty Woman
may have been a romantic movie,
but Julia Roberts
was still a hooker.
How long have you known
Quentin had A.L.S.?
From the beginning.
And how long have you known
Quentin falsified
trial results to get
the drug on the market?
- He didn't lie.
- But you did.
I love him.
So what else could I do?
I am in this, Scottie.
Okay.
So am I.
I think Mike Ross
went to a subpar law school
and has been lying about it
the whole time.
Just call up Harvard
and ask for a copy
of his transcript.
Professor Gerard's
legal ethics class,
did you ever hear of anybody
ever getting an A-plus?
No, he's famous for never
giving higher than an "A."
Well, what are you
so happy about?
I made bubble-wrap slippers
this morning
while you were in the shower.
I specifically told you
the bubble wrap
is for the dishes.
I also made a hat.
Okay, I'm moving in
with a ten-year-old.
And you love me.
I do.
Hey, I was thinking,
what are we going to do
about our bed?
We already have two.
I know,
but, yeah, we do.
But don't you think a new
beginning deserves a new bed?
That...is incredibly sweet.
Yeah, not bad
for a ten-year-old, huh?
What kind of bed
were you thinking?
Whichever one we pick out
after we test them tonight.
And did you have
any particular test in mind?
Well, now I do.
See, I don't think
the store is
gonna let us run
that kind of test.
Yeah.
No, you're right.
We should probably just test
ours before we go out tonight.
Oh.
What are you doing?
I think that Louis
might have just seen us.
Come on,
what's the difference?
We're moving in together.
I think it's time
we stopped keeping it a secret.
But keeping it a secret
is sort of fun.
- Mm-hmm.
- And sexy.
And I am pro sexy--
I mean, I did make
those bubble-wrap slippers
and hat after all,
which is funny, 'cause...
That's not sexy,
it's just fun.
- It's something.
- Something.
- I made you some too.
Hey, Harvey, she won't be back
for another week,
so I don't think you need
to start drinking just yet.
You want to make fun,
or you want to help me
figure out
where to put this?
A bottle of scotch?
You couldn't get her
anything more personal?
- She likes scotch.
- You like scotch.
She likes me.
Therefore...
Why don't you just attach
a card that says,
"Welcome,
generic senior partner"?
This is a $12,000 bottle
of scotch,
and this is one of three
left in the world.
That doesn't say generic,
that says--
You're one
of three very expensive things
I recently purchased.
We worked it out
about the buy-in.
And this is gonna
un-work it out.
You know, it's funny.
First it was too generic.
Now it's special.
What are you saying?
I don't think you have a
problem with my choice of gift.
I think you have a problem
with my choice of recipient.
Do you think Scottie
would even be here
if it wasn't for me?
No, I don't.
Harvey, I want this for you.
I want it to work,
and I'm just trying to--
Make sure
I don't screw it up.
Well, we both know
you're gonna screw it up.
I'm just trying to delay that
as long as possible.
You sure about this?
That bottle is the reason
I buy my own present
for secretary's day.
- There's a secretary's day?
- There is.
And you're very generous.
How you doing, Mike?
Are you excited or what?
Excited about what?
Didn't you get my email?
Oh, there it is.
Why don't you read it?
Oh, actually, you know what,
never mind.
I'll just let you know
what it says.
It's so great.
You're gonna love it.
It says
I invited Henry Gerard here
to give a lecture
this Friday.
That's great.
You don't even know
who he is, do you?
Professor Henry Gerard,
author of the definitive text
in legal ethics
and chair of the department
for the last 20 years.
Yeah, I know who he is.
And do you also remember
what you got in his class?
It's pretty hard to forget
an A-plus.
Yeah, it's pretty hard
to forget a grade
that never happened.
No one gets an A-plus
in Gerard's class.
Yeah, well, no one can recite
an entire chapter
of his book from memory.
But I can and did.
Bullshit-.
You never got an A-plus because
you never took his class.
It's a required class, Louis.
Of course I took it.
Not if you never went
to Harvard.
Louis, that is insane.
I have a transcript
from Harvard.
I have a degree from Harvard.
That's because I--
Wait, let me guess.
'Cause you went to Harvard?
See, Mike,
here's the situation.
I don't believe you.
And I don't want to call
Gerard up and ask him
'cause I don't want
the world laughing at my firm.
But if he doesn't walk up
to you on Friday
and say, "Mike Ross,
my beloved student
"who I remember,
because he's the only one
I ever gave an A-plus to,"
well, then, I'm gonna know
you're lying.
And if you still
don't come clean,
I'm gonna launch
a formal investigation,
whether it makes my firm
look bad or not.
This is crazy.
There is nothing to investigate.
Well, I'd rather risk looking
crazy to root out an impostor
than to risk letting
that impostor poison everything
that I stand for.
It's over, Mike.
I'm on to you,
and I'm gonna expose you
for the lying piece of filth
that you are.
Don't forget to rinse
your mouth out
after you're done
throwing up.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ Suits 3x12 ♪
Yesterday's Gone
Original Air Date on March 13, 2014
♪ all that time
imagine this ♪
♪ the greenback boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Do you remember when you said
if Louis knew, we'd know?
He knows.
What did he do?
He's bringing
in Henry Gerard
to give a lecture.
So what?
It'll only be the first time
you've had to suffer through it.
He's bringing him in
because he saw
I got an A-plus
in his class.
What? No one gets an A-plus
in Gerard's class.
- Welcome to the problem.
- God damn it.
Donna, get in here.
Why are you calling Donna?
Because she's the one
who found out that Louis knows
you don't have a file
in the Harvard file room.
How do you know that?
Because Louis's new girlfriend
is the queen
of that file room,
and she left him alone
in there.
You guys didn't think
to mention this?
I thought I handled it.
She did handle it.
She sent him to sniff out
your transcript.
Only she didn't realize
you gave yourself
an A-plus in legal ethics.
I didn't give it to myself.
Lola Jensen did.
I don't give a shit
who gave it to you,
unless it was Professor Gerard,
which it wasn't.
How many people take
the class?
I mean, maybe Mike will just be
another face in the crowd.
Louis is bringing him here
to see if he embraces
his star student.
The worst thing I can do is just
be another face in the crowd.
We need to make it
so that he doesn't come.
It's not gonna happen.
The man doesn't back out
of commitments.
His favorite quote is
"for the law to work,
there must be honor
in one's word."
- Who's he quoting?
- Himself.
Pompous prick.
Guy never practiced a day
in his life,
thinks he can write the book
on real-world ethics.
Okay.
I'm not panicking,
but what are we gonna do?
Right now,
you're gonna sit tight.
And what are you going to do?
I think it's time
to tell Jessica.
We need to talk.
- We do.
- You know?
No, but whatever it is,
it can wait.
This isn't something
that can wait.
Quentin died.
I'm sorry.
I knew A.L.S.
wasn't gonna be a picnic.
And I knew this was coming,
but it doesn't--
Look, if you need some time,
I can manage things here.
The truth is, Harvey,
I'd take it.
But Lisa's on her way in
to discuss Quentin's will
with us.
Us?
Quentin named you and I
co-executors of his estate.
You're her husband's ex-wife.
I doubt Lisa sees this
as just business.
No, I can't imagine
she does.
Can you see this
as just business?
You don't like her,
you don't trust her, and you
have good reason for both.
Quentin asked me
to do this.
Maybe he gave you
a co-executor for a reason.
You're saying
he was giving me an out?
No, I'm just saying
that I'm here,
and you don't have
to do this.
Harvey, he asked me,
and I'm not going
to let him down.
Mike, you can't just wait
for the ax to fall.
I didn't just wait.
I armed myself.
I learned everything there is to
know about Gerard and his class.
Harvey is right.
This guy is a prick.
He makes everybody read
his books
and then doesn't even test
on them.
Okay, but arming yourself
isn't enough.
We need
to actually do something.
Harvey told me
to sit tight.
That's exactly
what I'm gonna do.
Right, that's because
Harvey's life isn't on the line.
Ours is.
Ours?
Mike, I am not moving in
with you
because I need
a new place to live.
Okay, so what do you think
we should do?
What's gonna make him believe
that you went to Harvard?
Well, if my transcript,
diploma,
and the job you can only get
by having attended Harvard
aren't enough,
I'm not really sure what is.
Well, there's got to be
something you can say.
Look, Rachel,
you know Louis.
The more I try and deny it,
the more
he's gonna come after me.
I can't believe this.
He is not gonna be happy
until he has
a signed full confession
proving he was right.
You're right.
And that's exactly
what I'm gonna give him.
Come on.
It's all
fairly straightforward.
The company
shouldn't be affected.
Tim can continue
with the day-to-day
while this works
its way through probate.
Well, the day-to-day's
going to change.
- How so?
- We have an offer from Pryzen.
You want to sell
the company?
I want to accept an offer.
Well, that was fast.
Excuse me?
What Jessica is saying is
Pryzen didn't waste
any time swooping in.
No, what I'm saying is,
before we authorize anything,
we need to evaluate
if this is even a good idea.
I don't see why.
Our general counsel thinks
it's a good idea, and I agree.
And I'm the one who's inheriting
the majority of the company,
so it's my decision.
Actually, it isn't.
What are you talking about?
My job is to see that
Quentin's wishes are fulfilled.
Are you implying
that you know his wishes
better than I do?
I'm implying
he's not dead a week,
and you want to strip his name
off the door and into oblivion.
What I want to do
is put the drug
that he dedicated
his life to
in the hands of a company
with the resources to finish it.
And I was there when he worked
for companies like this.
And he hated them, which is why
he went out on his own.
You were there?
Well, that's not how I heard
the story.
All right,
we're not doing this.
You want to sell your shares?
No one's saying you can't.
But we have a responsibility
to evaluate it.
Remember when you said
you'd try to be conciliatory?
I never said that.
Well, you should have,
'cause you sure couldn't
keep the personal out of it.
I didn't think
they were gonna come at me
with all that stuff.
They weren't coming at you.
They were coming
with a proposal.
Do you really think
that offer came out of thin air?
I think it's possible
they waited to pounce.
It's also possible
that Lisa and Tim
put this in motion
while Quentin was lying
in his hospital bed.
And what if they did?
Is that really our business?
Jessica, I understand
how hard this is for you,
but his legacy is this drug.
It's not about whose name
is on the company that makes it.
You're saying
you agree with Lisa.
I'm saying to you now
what I tried to tell you before.
This is personal for you.
It's not personal for me.
So before we take another step,
let me evaluate this offer.
You're right.
I lied to you.
I lied to everyone.
I cheated to get here,
and if you put me in front
of Henry Gerard,
he's not gonna
remember me.
'Cause you never took
his class.
Because I never went
to his class.
'Cause you never went
to Harvard.
- That's not true.
- Bullshit.
Louis, please, look, I know
you have every right to be angry
with me.
I'm not angry.
Angry is just a flash
in the pan.
My outrage is here to stay,
and I will obliterate any
infection threatening my firm.
I'm not the infection
you think I am.
The only thing that's bullshit
is that A -plus!
What?
Louis, I went to Harvard.
I...
I just changed my grade.
You expect me
to believe that?
I have always been
the smartest kid
at every school
that I went to.
High school, college,
the first two years of Harvard,
I'd get "A"s
without studying.
I'd ace every test
without going to class, but--
but that third year...
You had to take Gerard.
I could memorize his books,
but his tests weren't
about his books.
Yeah,
they're about his lectures.
The final exam--
I failed it.
I went to his office to beg
for a second chance.
He doesn't give
second chances.
- I had to try.
- He wouldn't do it.
He wasn't there.
I got to his office.
It was empty.
His computer was
just sitting there,
logged in
to the main system.
He was about to submit
his grades.
I only had a few seconds
before he came back, so...
I decided to save myself.
No, you decided
to give yourself an A-plus.
No, Louis.
You might not be able
to believe me
about anything else
ever again.
Believe this.
You have no idea how much
I wish I could do it over again,
because this time,
I would do it right.
I would go to every class, and I
would attend every lecture,
and I would feast
on what that place has to offer
like no one ever has.
But you didn't do it right
the first time.
You cheated,
and now you're looking at me
to help you get away with it.
No, Louis-
Get out of my sight.
What a surprise.
Louis, please,
I just want to--
I know what you want to do--
you want to lobby me
on behalf of someone
who had the audacity--
I love him.
What?
We're moving in together,
and we're starting
a life together.
Rachel-
and I'm telling you this
because I know what he did
and I still love him.
Okay, here's the problem.
I don't.
- Louis.
- Rachel...
I respect you.
I care about you.
But this isn't about you.
This is about Mike
and what he did to me.
You know,
he came to me the night
that you asked him
to be your associate.
I told him to go with you.
Why?
Because he said he had
a connection with you
that he's never had
with Harvey.
- He said that?
- Yes.
Your shared love of the law.
- Yeah, I told him that.
- I know.
And I have
the same connection with you.
Rachel, you're asking me to--
Louis, he didn't do this
to you.
He did it so that
he can practice the thing
that we all love.
And if you don't let it go,
he's never gonna be able
to practice it again.
Thank you for coming alone.
I'm happy to help,
but Jessica and I are a team,
and asking to see me alone
doesn't change that.
I'm not gonna cut her out
of the process.
Isn't that what
she's doing to me?
She's trying to kill
the sale.
That's not
what this letter says.
I'm not a lawyer,
but I'm not stupid.
It says all communication
goes through Pearson Specter.
- This doesn't kill the deal.
- It tells them that
they've been negotiating with
people with no power at all.
No, it tells them
they have
to negotiate with two entities
instead of just one.
It gives us more firepower.
What do you want, Lisa?
I want to know why your
signature isn't on that letter.
Because we came
to a consensus,
and she signed it
on both our behalves.
- I don't believe you.
- I don't care.
And if you can't handle us
notifying the buyer
that we're evaluating
this sale,
then it makes me question
whose judgment is
really clouded.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm done meeting
behind my partner's back.
What the hell happened
to letting me
evaluate this offer?
I am letting you
evaluate the offer.
You sent this letter
to kill the deal.
I sent that letter
to buy you time.
Jessica, you put my name
on a document you knew
I wouldn't support.
You are on Lisa's side.
You want to sell.
This isn't about Lisa,
and I don't give a shit
whether this company
is sold or not.
This is about you and me and how
we're going to run this firm.
Didn't we just have
a conversation about that?
Yeah, we sure did.
And when it had to do
with Scottie,
you gave me a big speech
about trust,
about how I had to trust
you had rational reasons
for what you were doing.
- This is different.
- Exactly.
This time
it's not personal for me.
It's personal for you.
And you're not playing
by your own rules.
This deal is wrong,
Harvey.
And like it or not,
I'm still the managing partner.
Not on this.
On this,
you're a co-executor,
and you're not putting
my name on any more letters.
So I suggest you get
your head on straight
and look at this deal
rationally.
And if you can't do that,
I suggest you step aside.
Jessica, you loved him.
I know you're hurting.
So is she.
Whatever your history
with her,
so is she.
You're here late.
The life of an associate,
right?
Ah, yeah, I remember.
I used to live in this room,
work piled all around me,
surviving on coffee,
delivery,
and no sleep.
And the whole time,
wondering,
"man, is it ever gonna get
any easier?"
- Does it?
- No.
But you still love it.
And so do you.
Or else you'd be home
with the woman
who loves you,
not spending your night here.
- You know.
- She came to see me.
I didn't think
I could forgive you.
But then somehow,
she...
Made me realize I could.
Louis, I don't know
how to thank you.
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't thank me yet.
I'm not the one
you did this to.
What are you saying?
I'm saying you did this
to Henry Gerard.
And it's not my place
to let it go for him,
which is why you're gonna have
to come clean to him.
You said it yourself.
Gerard doesn't give
second chances.
What he does or doesn't do
is up to him.
That's his right, Mike,
as the person that you wronged.
Yeah, but he doesn't have
to know that I wronged him.
Listen to me.
You said that if you had it
to do over, you'd do it right.
I'm giving you that chance.
Take it,
or I'm gonna have to take it
for you.
What are you here
to do now,
take my house away from me?
I'm here to talk.
Well, the last time we talked,
you pretty much said
I don't care about my husband
enough to honor his wishes.
The last time we talked,
I was an asshole.
Pardon my French.
I don't mind your French.
It's come to my attention
that I may have let
our history affect
how I'm handling this situation.
It's funny.
Harvey brought that same thing
to my attention.
So...
Tell me this.
Why do you want to sell?
Do you know why I lied
about those A.L.S. trials?
Because I was desperate
for the research to continue.
But it didn't matter.
Lisa.
He wasn't supposed to die.
He wasn't supposed to live
as long as he did.
We weren't trying
to prolong his life.
We were trying
to find a cure.
And we failed.
You never cared
about the money.
The only money
I cared about is
the money to find the cure,
and we don't have the resources.
Pryzen does.
But they already
have an A.L.S. drug.
- It's not as good as ours.
- In profit margin, it's better.
Which means there's nothing
to stop them
from buying your company,
burying your drug,
and making a fortune.
What are you saying?
I'm saying
you didn't fail him,
but I know how it feels
to think that you did.
And I have a way to make sure
that neither one of us
feels that way again.
So your great plan
backfired.
Harvey, I'm sorry.
I don't need you to say
I'm sorry.
But the next time
I tell you to sit tight,
I need you to say you will.
Okay.
Good, because the next time
I tell you to sit tight
is right now.
Wait, what are you gonna do?
I'm getting on a plane
to Boston.
And doing what?
I'll let you know
when I get back.
Why are you going to Boston?
I have to see Marcus.
He's in trouble.
Anything I can do?
No, I'll handle it myself.
Since you're leaving,
I'm going to need you to draft
some language for the Sainz
pharmaceutical sale.
So you're in favor
of it now?
Well, not exactly.
But I heard what you said,
and I went to see Lisa.
She and I
are on the same page.
Do you have time to hear
what the plan is?
I trust you.
So what do you need me
to draft?
I need you to draft
a provision that guarantees
Pryzen will finish developing
that drug.
Consider it done.
He's not seeing his brother,
is he?
No, he's not.
- Care to elaborate on that?
- Not particularly.
You're saying
I should trust him.
I'm saying I do.
I'd ask how you're holding up,
but I can see the answer.
Not well.
I can only imagine
what these last couple of days
have been like for you.
But I'm telling you,
it's gonna be okay.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
- But what if it's not?
- Well, then we're screwed.
But that's not gonna happen.
Look, Donna.
I am trying so hard
to be brave.
But what if Louis ends up
finding out
everything about Mike?
What if he ends up exposing him
and he actually gets arrested?
What if he actually--
God.
Rach,
Mike found out
that one of our partners
ordered multiple murders.
Harvey said he'd fix it.
Two days later,
that partner was in prison.
Stephen was a criminal.
This is an academic.
He hasn't done
anything wrong.
Well, what makes Harvey great
at his job is he knows
that everybody
has done something wrong.
Even the most esteemed
ethics professor in the country?
The cleaner they look,
the more dirt
they've swept under the rug.
I'm telling you,
Harvey's gonna walk in there,
he's gonna find the lump,
and Henry Gerard is not
gonna know what hit him.
Wednesday nights,
8:00 to 10:00,
it's like clockwork.
Consistency is nothing
to be feared.
I wasn't afraid of it.
I was counting on it.
Mr. Specter.
Professor Gerard.
Looks the same
as the last time I was here.
Can't say you look the same
as the last time you were here.
Yes, you can.
I see
you're as humble as ever.
We'll see who's humble
in a few minutes.
And for the record,
you were wrong
about how I'd turn out.
I know how you turned out.
More settlements than
any other lawyer in New York.
More closings than
And settling is what it takes
to get the job done
in the real world.
I know what it takes for you
to do what you do,
and compromising your way
through life
is no way to go
about the law.
I see
you're as pompous as ever.
What did you come here for,
Mr. Specter?
- I came to ask for a favor.
- The answer is no.
You don't even know
what it is.
I know you're the one
who's asking.
I figured you'd say that,
which is why I brought this.
I don't consider blackmail
a favor.
I doubt the trustees
will care about semantics
when they see that.
Well, I doubt the trustees
are gonna see anything at all.
Because that envelope is full
of blank paper
or your dry cleaning receipts.
You think I'm bluffing?
I know you are.
If you think that envelope
is meaningless.
Why don't you go ahead
and open it?
Your poker face
has gotten much better,
I'll give you that.
A lot of practice,
you know,
compromising my way
through life.
- You know.
- I know.
And you talk a big game,
but you're just as human
as everyone else,
you smug son of a bitch.
What's your favor?
Find a reason to cancel
your trip on Friday.
And if Louis Litt ever tries
to contact you after that,
don't take his call.
- Seems easy enough.
- It is.
Have a good night,
Professor Gerard.
Here's the problem,
Mr. Specter.
I don't only talk a big game.
I walk it.
And ethics is not about
never doing anything wrong.
It's about making choices.
And I'm not going to let you
make my choice for me.
So go do
whatever you're gonna do,
but I'm not canceling
my trip.
- You didn't get it done.
- How'd you know?
Because I know you would call
to tell me if it's okay.
And you didn't call,
so it's not okay.
Then why are you so calm?
Because you've taught me
enough to know
that it's going to be okay.
- It's not.
- What?
It's not gonna be okay.
I don't see what we're gonna do.
What do you mean you don't see
what we're gonna do?
You're Harvey Specter.
What's that
supposed to mean?
It means there's a gun
pointed at our heads.
There's 146 things
that we can do.
We just have to put our heads
together and figure it out.
What the hell do you think
I've been doing
all goddamn night?
Louis has us,
he's not gonna let it go,
and there's nothing
we can do to stop it.
- There has to be something.
- There isn't.
Well, I refuse
to believe that.
I don't give a shit
what you believe.
Get it through your head.
I'm not superman.
I failed,
and I don't know what to do.
Mike.
Tim, I thought
I was meeting with Lisa.
And I thought
you were above board.
I see you've read
our amendment.
You drafted a provision
that if they didn't spend
$100 million
finishing that drug,
they'd have to pay us
an extra $100 million.
I drafted a provision
to see
if they'd put their money
where their mouth is.
What you did was
what you always wanted to do--
tank this deal.
- They pulled the offer.
- They yanked the offer.
Then the deal wasn't worth
anything to begin with.
What wasn't worth anything
was the document
you had Quentin sign
making you executor
instead of me.
I didn't have Quentin
sign anything.
Well, maybe you didn't
have him sign it,
but I know
when he signed it,
and it's not gonna hold up.
It'll hold up just fine.
We'll see.
This is a subpoena.
So the next time
we have this conversation,
you'll be under oath.
What exactly
is he claiming?
He's saying Quentin
wasn't competent
when he made me executor.
So let him say it.
I don't see
where there's a problem.
Yes, you do.
No, I don't.
Just get up on the stand
and testify that Tim
doesn't know
what he's talking about.
But he does.
Quentin knew
what he wanted.
They're not going
to ask me that.
They're going to ask me
about his condition.
I saw him, Lisa.
I know what he was like.
Quentin knew
what he wanted.
He was also medicated,
could barely speak,
and he was
in a lot of pain.
But you don't have
to say those things.
I'm going to have to swear
to this under oath.
If making you executor
wasn't legally valid,
then why didn't you say so
when he did it?
Because I didn't think
it would be challenged.
And thinking something
might not hold up
and keeping that thought
to myself
is not the same
as lying about it under oath.
Well, those are
some fuzzy damn lines.
I didn't make them.
They came with the job.
You're gonna undo everything
he's ever worked for.
Maybe.
But just because you and I
want the same thing
doesn't mean that I'm willing
to perjure myself to get it.
Please.
You said you didn't want
to fail him again.
You didn't fail.
You don't need to make me
feel better.
I'm not trying
to make you feel better.
I'm just telling you
the truth.
You didn't fail because...
We were always playing
on borrowed time.
- Mike.
- Harvey.
I wouldn't have
any of this without you.
I think it's time
I cut your exposure.
You don't have to do that.
It's all gonna come
crashing down anyway.
I'm gonna go to Louis.
I'm going to resign,
and I'm gonna beg him
to let this whole thing go.
Then I'm going with you.
Harvey,
when Trevor went
to Jessica with my secret,
I felt betrayed.
I lost my closest friend
in the world.
And I know you don't like
to admit it,
but we're friends.
And I'm not gonna betray
my friend.
I used to hate
this kind of thing.
- What kind of thing?
- Guest lectures.
Hardman used to make us
sit through them.
Except he gave tests
afterwards.
Yeah, and if you didn't pass,
you got stuck on doc review.
Goddamn Hardman.
You remember
the Robinson case?
Sure do.
80,000 documents,
two years of prep,
and five months in court.
And the Friday
before trial started,
he assigned you and I
to proof everything.
You blew it off.
And you covered for me.
You did your half and mine,
then turned it in.
He would've fired you
on the spot.
Exactly, and I'm here
because you didn't sell out
a friend then,
but you're about to now.
- Mike.
- Me.
Friend?
Louis,
I may not ever say it,
but that's not
because we aren't.
We are.
You know it.
I know it.
I just don't like
to say it.
Last time I asked you,
you said, "don't push it."
You knew I meant yes.
I did.
So Mike told you.
He did.
What'd you say?
Doesn't matter.
Bottom line is I forgave him
because I don't care
what some stupid piece
of paper says.
And I want you
to forgive him too.
Oh, Harvey,
I did forgive him.
I just can't cover it up
for him.
You covered it up
with Hardman for me.
What you did that weekend
is not the same as what he did
to Professor Gerard.
What's the same is
Hardman wouldn't have let it go,
and Gerard won't let it go.
You make Mike confess,
you might as well throw his life
down the toilet.
Harvey,
he didn't just betray us.
He betrayed the law.
He did.
- That's not right.
- It isn't.
But forgiveness isn't
about right and wrong.
Louis, I know you value
the letter of the law,
but what about its spirit?
Because Mike embodies
that spirit
more than either one of us.
You said we're friends.
A friend would not ask me
to do this.
No, Louis.
A friend just won't hold it
against you if you don't.
Do you swear to tell
the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth,
so help you God?
I do.
But before we start,
I'd like to make a statement.
I am here to tell the truth,
but what I want you
to understand
is that truth is subjective.
The truth is the truth.
No.
The law is the law.
We can define
where a legal line is.
I'm talking about the truth.
The truth is
much more complicated.
By the letter of the law,
Quentin Sainz may
or may not have been competent.
I can't say what's true
with 100% certainty.
I just don't know.
But what I can say
with certainty
is that Quentin knew
what he was doing
when he trusted me to look
after his best interests.
How do you know that?
Because I knew him.
Just because someone
can't check off everything
on the list
that's required
to be competent
doesn't mean
they aren't better at whatever
they do than the rest of us.
And Quentin Sainz
was an amazing man
with an amazing mind.
And if he were here right now,
I'd still listen to him
on any subject
sooner than I'd listen
to anybody else.
That's all very touching,
but we're not here to talk
about the truth.
We're here to deal
with the letter of the law.
Have you never met someone
who by the letter of the law
shouldn't be able to do
what they do?
Who beat the odds?
Your honor-
We are talking
about a man's life.
about his legacy.
And I dispute that those things
are less important
than the letter of the law.
Your honor,
what has to happen today
is very clear.
You have to undo
this injustice.
Yes.
This is about justice.
But the issue isn't whether
Quentin Sainz was competent
when he made me executor,
but rather,
would it have been his intent
to do so if he were.
This man dedicated his life
to one thing,
and the circumstances
surrounding how he decided
to protect that thing
is not the question.
It's a question of law,
Ms. Pearson.
No, it is a question
of doing what is right.
Louis.
What the hell
are you doing here?
- I--
- I told you I needed
the Carell filings by lunch--
you didn't get that done,
so now you don't get to listen
to this lecture.
You do not get to listen to this
titan talk about legal ethics.
You know something,
you make me sick.
So do me a quick favor
and tell him you're sorry
and get the hell
out of here.
I'm sorry.
I accept your apology,
but I'm not
the aggrieved one here.
Louis is.
Louis...
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
It's not my pony.
Come on.
Motion to remove Jessica
Pearson as executor denied.
Well, you were right.
Quentin did know
what he was doing.
I know how hard
it must have been...
At the end.
I'm glad Quentin had you.
I'm glad he had you too.
He let it go.
I heard it all worked out.
Never a doubt.
I've got a present for you.
Tiffany.
"D.J.S."
This is a present
for Scottie.
Which makes it a present
for you.
- Let's put this in her office.
- Great.
We can put it next to your
overpriced bottle of scotch.
So it was a great gift.
Now it is.
For the record,
her middle name is Victoria.
No, it isn't.
What is it?
Please, she never told me.
Julie?
- Seriously?
- Jessie?
- Oh, my God.
- Joy?
- You're pathetic.
- Jenny?
Not telling.
I don't think
this is a good idea.
I don't care.
What are they gonna do,
fire us?
Mike, I haven't left
before 5:00
in the past six years.
All the more reason
to do it.
Now what do you want to do?
See a movie, grab dinner,
get a drink?
I just want to go home.
Yeah.
Let's go home.
People seem to keep coming
in here lately.
I needed to hear some music.
And drink some scotch.
How often do you really
do one without the other?
Move over.
Did you take care
of your Marcus problem?
For the time being.
Good.
It wasn't really
a Marcus problem.
I know.
You want to hear the truth?
Not tonight.
That's why I didn't tell you
in the first place.
I know.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net