Pursuant to section 28-B of the bylaws,
I am placing Harvey Specter
on immediate unpaid suspension.
That vote's not gonna
go well for you.
You need to do something
to humble yourself.
What is this?
Portfolio of business
I want you to take
to Pearson Specter
for me.
I'm not doing it.
Am I mistaken, or did we
not have this discussion?
Don't call me again.
Daniel Hardman's office.
I need to speak
to him right now.
He sent two packages.
Either move forward
on one of them or he'll
move forward on the other.
Rachel, you have to handle
this meeting by yourself.
What?
She knows that
I didn't go to law school.
I'm calling the DA's office
right now
if you don't tell me
what the hell's going on.
We're engaged.
So it is him.
Please,
I am begging you.
It's done.
- She bought it?
- She did.
You think I should stop
being a lawyer?
I'm saying if you really
love her, you won't marry her.
What are you doing?
Just looking at how beautiful
you are.
I already said yes,
so you don't have to--
What got into you
this morning?
Sometimes I just think about
how we got to be here together.
Then I wonder
if I deserve you.
And then I wish that we could
just stay here in this bed
for the rest of my life.
So do I.
Does--does this have
anything to do
with the close call
we had?
It does.
I just don't think I ever
thanked you enough for...
having my back.
Don't you know by now that
I will always have your back?
I do.
Mm.
♪ ♪
Harvey, no matter how this
goes, we don't show weakness,
we don't show division, and
we don't take it out on Louis.
Well, that's gonna be tough,
because we wouldn't even be here
if it wasn't for that
conniving son of a bitch.
Harvey, Louis came to me
last night,
said he was gonna
flip his vote.
So forgive him or not,
don't antagonize him.
There's still a chance
you could get out of this.
Good morning,
everyone.
Harvey, before we vote,
would you like to say something?
I would.
As far as the official purpose
of this vote,
I'm not gonna insult any of you
by lying to you.
I hit Louis, and I apologized
to him in private,
but what I haven't done is
apologize to all of you.
My compensation has always been
important to me.
Not for the money,
but for what it says
about my place
in the firm.
But this isn't a firm.
It's a partnership.
And my partners are
more important to me than money.
So, starting today,
I'm reducing my compensation
to the median amount,
with the rest going
to all my partners to share.
And I'm doing this regardless
of how you vote today.
Thank you for listening.
Louis, would you like to
present an opposing view?
Let's just get this
over with.
Okay.
We'll do this by secret ballot.
The final vote is eight
for suspension, eight against,
which means the motion
will not carry.
Therefore, Harvey will not
be suspended.
Now, if no one has
anything else,
I would like to get
back to business.
Actually, I would like
to propose
a new piece of business.
Daniel Hardman just signed
a billion-dollar client...
What?
And in exchange for sharing
that client with us,
he'd like to return to the firm
on a trial basis.
There is no way Daniel Hardman
is setting foot in this office.
Of course you'd think that,
because that would mean
more money
for the rest of us.
Are you kidding me?
I just showed everyone here
I don't care about money.
You just showed us
that you'll do anything
to get out of a suspension,
including bribing the partners.
Well, you may have fooled
half of us,
but the other half
didn't buy it.
That's enough.
Daniel Hardman will not return
to this firm
under any circumstance.
And of course
you back Harvey.
This is not about Harvey.
This is about my firm.
It's always about Harvey
and it's clear to everyone here,
whatever he does is
fine with you,
from hitting
another partner
to turning down millions
for this firm.
You two-faced
piece of shit.
Why don't we let
the partners decide?
I don't have to let
the partners decide,
because this is
my decision,
and my decision is, this
god damn meeting is adjourned!
♪ ♪
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 5x08 ♪
Uninvited Guests
Original Air Date on August 19, 2015
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
How the hell did you
get up here?
Carl downstairs and I
go back.
Well, you can take Carl back
where you came from
because you need an appointment
to be here.
I have something I need
to deliver to Harvey.
Then I suggest you leave it
with his secretary, Gretchen.
"His secretary, Gretchen."
Now, there's three words
I never thought
I'd hear you say.
Ooh.
How long has it been
since Harvey dumped you
onto Louis's desk?
How long has it been since I
slapped you in the face?
Because that is all I can
think about right now.
Promises, promises.
If you're here to take back
your old office, Daniel,
Don't break out
the measuring tape just yet,
because your plan
to worm your way in just failed.
So you can walk your ass out
the same way you walked in.
Louis, it's so fascinating
seeing you and Harvey
united like this after all
you must have been through.
What are you talking about?
Her.
I see you finally got
the better of him on something.
I didn't get the better of him
on anything.
There's no daylight between us.
Now get the hell
out of here.
And do it quick
before I have to call security
to tell them I'm beating
the shit out of you.
No need.
Since you're not interested
in what I have to say,
I'll go see Jessica.
And just between us chickens,
there's a chasm of daylight
between you two.
♪ ♪
Hey, how's Pearson Specter's
newest partner?
Are you talking about me
or Daniel Hardman?
News travels fast.
It does when it's news
about a lying sack of shit.
Mike, I would hope
that a partner with his eye
on the future
would be more forgiving.
You mean a partner.
You're not here about Daniel.
You're here about me.
You're goddamn right I am.
You promoted me just
to get Harvey to trust you
so you could set him up.
- No I didn't.
- Bullshit.
No, bullshit is
a gifted lawyer being held down
by partners to whom
he's pledged his loyalty.
Which brings me back to
what I just said a minute ago.
You think you bought
my loyalty.
Mike, you can pick
whatever side you want,
but when the dust settles,
and Harvey and Jessica are gone,
they'll be a place for you here
because I respect you.
Let me
tell you something, Jack.
When the dust settles,
you're gonna be the one
begging for a place,
and I'm gonna be the one
recommending they throw you out.
You really should try
one of those standing desks.
It's better on the back
for a woman of your age.
This is a standing desk
for a man of your height.
- Nice to see you, Jessica.
- No, it isn't.
And the last time I saw you,
I told you to
stay the hell away from my firm.
And a good lawyer
puts aside their feelings
when there's money on the table.
Oh, cut the shit, Daniel.
Second you get your foot
in the door,
you'll start hatching a plan
to put me on the street.
You're right.
But thanks to you,
the partners will put you
on the street anyway.
What the hell
are you talking about?
The client I was willing
to share with you
is looking
to make numerous acquisitions,
and those acquisitions
would have been new clients
for you too.
Instead, we're going to start
targeting your clients
as acquisitions,
and everyone we close
leaves you and comes
right over to me.
And now all the partners
will know why it's happening.
And your puppet, Jack Soloff,
tells the partners,
"If we let you back,
the bleeding stops."
Which is why I'm here.
To thank you.
It would be so much
less delightful
if you had just said yes
right away.
Well the least you could do
is tell me your first target.
I'll give you a hint.
It's one that's gonna hit you
right where it hurts.
I can't believe that
in a couple of months
we'll be back here
for your wedding.
I know, it's amazing.
I can't believe
how much we have left
to do.
Mmm, speaking of which.
Mm-hmm?
What's this?
Your wedding announcement
for "The Times."
I know that you're busy,
so I took the liberty
of writing it up.
Wedding announcement?
Yes.
Um, Mom, I don't think that--
I left a couple
of things blank.
I wasn't sure
where Mike went for undergrad.
Was it Cornell or Columbia?
Oh, and was he
on The Harvard Law Review?
And they're gonna want
a picture of the two of you.
I was thinking maybe
the Central Park Boathouse?
We're not doing
an announcement.
What?
Mike and I,
we're not interested in this.
I don't understand.
When you read your cousin
Nicole's announcement,
you didn't have
a problem with it.
'Cause something like this
is right for Nicole.
It's not right for me.
You mean it's not
right for Mike?
Oh, come on, Mom.
What are you talking about?
Two years ago,
you wouldn't have had a problem
with something like this.
Well, it's not two years ago,
and this is how we both feel.
So I'm just asking you
to respect my wishes
because we have
so much more to go over, okay?
I'm telling you
it's Cutie Pie Cosmetics.
Joan's ready to retire.
No one gives a shit
about Joan Walsh's business.
It's Nader Communications.
Why, because they're
you're client?
No, because
they were Jack's client
and now they're my client.
So this is all about you?
- Louis, calm down.
- No, this is all about you.
You know what?
You're the one who gave
Hardman the opening he needed.
- Did you hear what I just said?
- Excuse me?
Yeah, you heard me.
This wouldn't be happening
if you didn't try to suspend me.
After you punched me
in the face.
If you really want
to know who's at fault here,
why don't you take a look
in the mirror?
That's enough.
This is exactly
what Hardman wants.
He's trying to get us
to turn on each other.
Well, the fight is out there,
not in here,
and we have to figure out
who Hardman's target is.
Where the hell are you going?
You're right,
the fight is out there,
but Jack Soloff's in here.
You think it's a good idea
to let him go after Jack?
What's he gonna do?
Make him less on our side?
You're right.
There's more important things
to do here anyway.
Yeah, and number one
on the list
is if you think that Hardman's
really going after
Nader Communications,
then we need to get over there
and warn them.
It's not Nader,
it's McKernon Motors.
It can't be McKernon.
They're too small.
Not since we did
that battery deal.
And I know
what you're gonna say,
"Avery McKernon's estate
still owns too much
of the stock,"
but not anymore.
Who bought it?
It doesn't matter
who bought it.
It matters
who the attorney of record is.
- Let me guess, Daniel Hardman.
- Exactly.
Goddamn it.
Harvey, what are you doing?
I'm going
to see Dominic Barone.
- Well, then I'm going with you.
- No, you're not.
They're my oldest client,
and this is something
I have to do.
Harvey, this is a client
that you gave to me and Louis.
Yeah, and you were
smart enough
to figure out
they were the target.
Now I need you
to use that brain
to start figuring out
how we're gonna get out of this.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna look Dominic Barone
in the eye
and tell him I'm the reason
this is happening.
Jack, I need to talk to you.
You can save your breath,
Louis.
I know what you're here to say.
You're here to tell me
not to go against
your precious
Harvey and Jessica.
No, I'm here to tell you
that you have no idea
who you're in bed with.
Well, I appreciate
your concern for my well-being,
but I can handle myself.
No you can't.
What difference does it make,
Louis?
It's too late.
It's not too late.
You think if
I suddenly abandon Daniel,
Jessica's just gonna welcome
me back with open arms?
Yes, you don't know
how forgiving she can be.
I trust her.
The only thing she's going
to forgive me with
is a knife in the back.
Jack, listen to me.
Daniel Hardman
treated me like a son.
He promoted me
to senior partner,
used me to take over the firm.
After he lost power,
he turns around
and slaps me
with a sexual harassment claim.
I know.
Monica Eaton.
But what you don't know
is that it was bullshit.
He betrayed me.
Humiliated me.
And after I finally
confronted him about it,
he tells me...
that I got
what I always wanted.
So, Jack, believe me,
if you think this man
cares about you, he doesn't.
I know what kind of man
he is, Louis.
Then why are you siding
with him?
I'll tell you why.
He promised to do something
Jessica never would.
Put my name on the wall.
What if she would?
You're not in reality.
Jack, she did it for me.
Even if I wanted
to go with you, I couldn't.
He's got something on you,
doesn't he?
This conversation is over.
Harvey, what the hell?
I just to notification
of a tender offer.
They're coming after
my company.
I know,
that's why I'm here.
So they sent
the big guns to fight
because it's a hostile takeover?
I'm not here
because it's a hostile takeover.
I'm here because
this whole thing is my fault.
What do you mean your fault?
The reason you're
in the crosshairs is because
Daniel Hardman
has a vendetta against me.
You're telling me
we just closed a deal
that ensures
this company's future
and you put it in jeopardy
because you pissed off
your former partner?
Yes, that's
what I'm telling you.
God damn it.
Well what do you
want me to do, Dominic?
I want you to stop being
an asshole to people.
It's too late for that.
But it may not be too late
for this.
Drop us as your attorneys.
What?
As long as
you're connected to us,
there's gonna be
a target on your back.
You let us go,
there's a chance it goes away.
Harvey.
If I was just gonna
cut you loose because
someone hates you,
I wouldn't have hired you
in the fist place,
because we both know
I used to hate you.
Thanks, Dominic.
- So what are we gonna do?
- I'll let you know.
But I'll tell you this:
They want a war,
they got a war.
Hey, Rach, do you have
that Neilson brief for Louis
from last month?
No, I don't.
Are you sure?
Because he keeps telling me
that you have it.
And I keep telling him I don't
and I have more
important things to do
than sit around
and answer the same question
every other day.
And I have better things
to do with my time
than to be spoken to that way.
I'm sorry.
Rachel, what's going on?
I just had lunch
with my mom
to talk about our wedding,
and she wants to put
an announcement
in "The New York Times."
Oh, my God.
Did you tell her
that she can't do that?
Yeah.
I made up some story
about it being snobby,
but Donna, that's just
the tip of the iceberg.
What are you talking about?
This is her
proposed guest list.
It is 300 people
and it includes
the Attorney General
and the Dean of Harvard Law.
What am I gonna do?
You're gonna tell her
that you don't want
a big wedding and that's that.
And if I do that,
she's gonna know
that something's not right.
Rachel, this is
the type of argument
that every mother has
with every daughter
about her wedding.
She's never gonna think
that Mike's a fraud.
- How'd Dominic take it?
- He took it fine.
Good, 'cause I have a plan.
Let's hear it.
We go to the last place
they'd ever expect
and we offer to merge.
Where?
Fletcher Engines.
Are you crazy?
We go to Fletcher,
they're gonna kick Dominic out,
Jack gains power.
Might as well have
let McKernon get bought out
in the first place.
Then the only other option
that's even remotely possible
is we take them private.
That actually might work.
Come to think of it,
why the hell didn't you
just say that to me
in the first place?
Because I knew you'd shit on
whatever my first idea was
and that you'd be open
to the backup.
You're telling me
you set up a straw man idea
to manipulate me
into liking your real idea?
- Yep.
- How long you been doing that?
Peabody versus Danthorpe.
Son of a bitch.
All right, smart guy.
Now where are we gonna get
the money for the equity?
I'll tell you where.
Sidwell and Gianopolous.
Is that another
straw man idea?
Because you'll never get
the two of them
to go in on a deal together.
They hate each other.
Oh, those two hating
each other is exactly
what I'm counting on.
- Hey, Mom.
- Oh, Rachel!
You're just in time.
The caterer dropped off
some samples.
I was just about to try them,
but it'll be much more fun
if we do this together.
Okay, Mom,
but before you pout that.
I don't think that
the crostini travels very well.
Mom, please.
I know that you have given this
a lot of thought,
but I need to talk to you
about the size of the wedding.
It's way too big.
I have given this
a lot of thought,
and 30 people
at a wedding
isn't going to get
a chef like this.
Right, but I'm not
having a wedding
based on the chef,
and I'm not here
to talk about the menu.
I'm here to talk about
the guest list.
Rachel, did I ever tell you
what your father did
three weeks
before we got married?
Bought two tickets to Bermuda
and said we're eloping.
And he did that
because he didn't want
to deal with my mother.
But you know what stopped me?
I knew that I would regret
doing that to my mom
for the rest of my life.
But I told you
this isn't about Mike,
and it isn't
about eloping.
This is just about
me not wanting to get married
in front of hundreds of people
that I don't know.
What's going on here, Rachel?
I'm telling you
what's going on.
You're just not hearing me.
I don't want this big
of a wedding.
I'm hearing you,
but I know my own daughter,
and there is something
that you're not telling me.
Okay, Mom.
Yes, there is something
that I'm not telling you,
and that's because
it's really hard for me
to say it.
You keep thinking
that this is about Mike.
Well, it's not.
This is about you
not accepting that it's
my wedding and it's not yours.
Rachel.
And if you can't
figure out a way to accept that,
then I think maybe
we will have to elope.
Jessica, can I talk to you
for a second?
Can it wait till tomorrow?
No.
I think we should consider
promoting Jack Soloff
to name partner.
Are you crazy?
Jessica, we are
under attack.
And you're asking me
to reward our enemy.
No, I'm asking you
to bring our enemy's right hand
over to our side.
Louis, it's late.
I'm going home.
Jessica, you have to
listen to me, please.
Hardman's got something on him.
Has what on him?
I don't know,
but until two months ago,
the only thing we knew
about Jack Soloff
is that he bills more hours
than anyone but me.
So, what, you think
he just woke up one day
and became mastermind
of a palace coup?
The question isn't
who's in charge between
those two,
it's whether Jack is a volunteer
or a conscription.
I'm telling you,
I talked to him.
He's doing all this staring down
the barrel of a gun.
Then putting Jack's name
on the door
only gives Daniel more power.
What are you saying?
If Hardman
has something on him,
then we need
to have it on him too.
So instead of telling me
that we should promote him
why don't you get
to work on that?
♪ ♪
I thought I made it clear
last time we talked
I'm not interested
in whatever you're selling.
Well, you're gonna be
interested in this.
There is no deal
you're gonna put
in front of my face
that's gonna make me want to
get in business with you.
You're not doing it
to get in business with me.
You're doing it to keep me
from getting into business
with Tony Gianopolous.
'Cause, right now,
Harvey is over there
pitching him the same deal.
And you think I give a shit
what deals Harvey Specter does?
I think you give a shit what
deals Jonathan Sidwell does.
And you're here
to pit us against each other
just to jack up the price.
Damn right I am.
Then you can walk your ass
out that door right now.
Because I guarantee you that's
what Sidwell's telling Harvey.
And what Harvey's telling him
is that one of you
is gonna be on CNBC tomorrow
announcing their new deal...
And the other one's going
to be left with nothing
but his dick in his hand,
so, it's up to you.
But whoever calls first
is gonna have it
over the other one
for the rest of their life.
Clock's ticking, Tony.
I get a text,
he beats you to the punch.
I walk out that door.
So, what's it gonna be?
You're a son of a bitch.
I like that.
I'm in.
♪ ♪
No, no, listen.
I don't care when they need it.
I get 15 minutes a day
to eat my breakfast
and I didn't
get it this morning.
Okay?
I just reheated my Egg McMuffin
and I'm going to eat it
in peace.
Hello, beautiful.
Finally, it's just you and me.
Barnaby, right?
Actually, it's Benjamin,
and I'm kind of on--
Oh, I don't care
what you're on.
I need everything you have
on Jack Soloff.
I don't know what that means.
It means that I need
a detailed account
of all the cases he's worked on
since he started here.
Well, that's really more
of a file room issue, so--
Hey, Benson,
if I wanted to go
to the file room,
I'd go to god damn file room,
but I don't because I also
want all billing records,
phone records,
personal e-mails--
Whoa, personal e-mails?
Yes.
If he scheduled a prostate exam,
I want to know about it.
Isn't that just part
of the annual checkup?
What are you, C. Everett Coop?
Just get it done.
And the next time I ask you
to do something,
do it without asking
any stupid questions,
you got it?
You know,
Mike Ross always brings me food.
What?
I'm just saying,
whenever Michael needs a favor,
he brings me something.
You know, like,
a warm bag of bacon
or French fries.
This isn't a favor.
This is your god damn job.
So get me what I ask for pronto
or the next time I'll stop by
and bring you
a warm bag of shit.
♪ ♪
And now I don't even want
my Egg McMuffin.
Hey, Donna,
do you have a second?
Of course.
Rachel, what's wrong?
I talked to my mom last night.
And I take it
it didn't go well.
No, it went horribly,
and I threatened to elope.
Rachel, it's okay.
Look, we talked about this.
If she's thinking that
you're being difficult,
then she's not thinking
something else is going on.
No, no, but she could tell
that I'm hiding something
and I had to sit there
and lie to her and...
and tell her
that it was her fault.
Rachel, she's not
going to know about Mike.
You don't get it.
I'm thinking about
telling my mom the truth.
Rachel,
that is a bad idea.
Your mom can get over
some spat about the size
of your wedding, but she's not
going to get over this.
All I know is,
my mom loves me no matter what.
I understand that,
but Rachel,
if you do this,
you're going to be burdening
your mother with a secret
that she has to keep
from your father
for the rest of her life.
How did you two get in here?
You should us
you can get to us.
Now you know
we can get to you.
Then you must be here
to hand me the keys
to McKernon Motors.
Actually, we're here
to inform you
that McKernon Motors
is going private.
That's all well and good,
but there's the matter
of my tender offer,
which is up to the shareholders
and my 20%
is voting to take it.
Good for you.
We're pretty sure
the other 80%
is gonna want to take our offer,
seeing as it is
ten dollars per share
higher than yours.
Bullshit.
Where'd you get
that kind of money?
We got it at the United Bank
of Take Your Ass Back To Jersey.
So, you can keep coming
after us all you want, Daniel,
but they're all going
to end up just like this.
Then I'm going
to raise my offer.
Ten dollars a share,
because if you two think
you can beat me, you can't.
- Told you.
- Told him what?
That was your ceiling.
He thought it was
15 a share more.
I thought
you had bigger balls.
Either way, we just
wanted to find out
what it was so we could
come over the top
and crush you.
Because our real offer
is 20 more per share
and we don't care
who your investor is,
there's no way
they're paying more than that
just to fund your grudge.
See you around, Daniel.
By the way,
Mike pissed in your Bonsai.
Yeah, that's right.
Two times.
By the way,
nice Usual Suspects reference
back there.
Really, you caught that?
Yeah, I caught it.
What do you think I am?
Nothing, I just didn't think
you'd get it.
It was so subtle.
Trust me, not so subtle.
Well, if it was so ham-fisted,
why didn't you just
chime in back there?
Because I was there
to stick it to Hardman,
not clown around
with some quote-fest.
That's the difference
between you and me.
I can do both
at the same time.
Really?
See, at your age,
I'm surprised that you can
even make it through a meeting
that long without
having to pee.
Okay, why do you always have
to go straight to the prostate?
It's so distasteful.
Oh, right.
And you telling Hardman
that I'd peed in his Bonsai
was just pure class.
I didn't say
you peed in his Bonsai.
I said you pissed in it.
What are you, five?
Oh.
And by the way,
you're the one who told him
you did it twice.
Because you started it.
I had to lean in.
It's called committing.
Then how about you commit
to buying the next round
for a change?
I'd love to,
but I can't.
I got to go meet Rachel
at her mom's.
Talk about some wedding stuff.
Ugh.
I'd love to join you,
but I'd rather
have a prostate exam.
There you go.
See?
You're leaning in.
I'm proud of you.
Excuse me, ma'am,
could you make sure
to cut him off
when he starts mumbling about
how they don't make shows like
Welcome Back Cotter anymore?
♪ ♪
What are you doing here,
Daniel?
Just wondering what color
to paint the walls.
I've never been partial to red.
Instead of commenting
on my wall color,
why don't you go back
to your office?
Lick your wounds.
What wounds?
I'm about to win.
You have
a funny definition of win.
Since we just blew your
best offer out of the water.
Here's a copy of my new offer.
It'll be
in "The Journal" tomorrow.
There's no way the deal
holds up under this price.
And once your client
figures that out,
your offer falls through.
Well, then lucky for me,
my client's Japanese
and the dollar just
took a dive against the yen.
So my deal will hold up
and then some.
You know, I don't give a shit
where your client's from.
I don't lose to you.
Yes you do.
Because after this deal,
there'll be another one
and another one
and another one,
because you took my firm from me
and I'm going to take it
right back from you.
Get the hell out of my office,
Daniel,
before I do something
you'll regret.
Speaking of walls,
how does it feel
to have them closing in on you?
Son of a bitch!
Louis, is something wrong?
See this?
It contains everything
on God's green earth
there is to know
about Jack Edward Soloff
from his pirate beard
to his stupid pen
that he carries around
like Linus's blanket.
- And...?
- And there's no dirt on him!
There's not one case
he crossed a line on.
There's no debts.
Nothing.
Louis.
Did you hear me?
Is Soloff did something
and Hardman's a part of it,
it is buried so deep,
we'll never even
see the top of it,
let alone get
to the bottom of it.
Louis, I'm about to tell you
something I never
thought I would.
What?
The night that Harvey and Mike
put it together
about Daniel and CM,
they got stoned first.
What?
They thought you and Daniel
had them and they were screwed
and they figured,
"What the hell?"
So they bought some marijuana
and they got high.
Are you suggesting
we take the pot?
Worked for them.
Well, it's not
gonna work for me.
- Louis--
- Donna look at me.
Do I look like someone
who needs to be hungry
and paranoid?
Relax.
It was just a suggestion.
Well it was
a stupid god damn suggestion,
and if that's all you have,
just walk you ass out of here.
Louis, what is going on?
Why are you so angry at me?
I'm not angry at you.
I'm angry at myself.
Louis.
After the vote,
Harvey told me it was my fault
and you want to know what?
He's right.
Harvey says a lot of things.
- You told me too.
- What?
This whole thing started
because I told Jack
that he could
bring up Harvey's compensation
for a vote,
and you told me not to.
Well, then maybe
it's my fault too.
Because this whole thing
really started when you tried
to make things right with Harvey
for me coming to work for you.
Donna, are you saying
that you regret coming to me?
No, Louis.
I'm saying maybe
I had a hand in this too.
What do we do now?
We keep looking together.
And if we can't find anything,
then we tell Jessica the truth.
- Hey.
- Laura, hi, how are you?
Where's Rachel,
I thought for sure
she'd beat me here.
Uh, Rachel's not coming.
I told her
I wasn't feeling well
because I wanted
to talk to you alone.
Is something wrong?
Yes, there is.
Rachel told me today that
she wants to
scale back the wedding
and that you two are
in sync on this.
Sounds like
you don't believe her.
Found it hard enough
to believe that she wouldn't
want to put an announcement
in "The Times,"
but that my little girl,
who always dreamed
of getting married
at The Plaza Hotel
now only wants
a handful of people there?
I'm sorry, Michael.
I just don't buy it.
This is coming from you,
isn't it?
You're right.
It is.
And I'll tell you why.
I don't have a family.
I don't have a lot of people
that I can invite,
and I asked her
if we could please
keep the entire wedding low-key.
And she said that
she would do that for me.
And I understand that.
I think it's incredibly
sweet of her
to be willing
to do that for you.
But...
If you could find it
in your heart
to let my little girl
have the wedding
that she's always wanted,
I am telling you,
she'll remember it
for the rest of her life.
Again?
You know, I'd really prefer it
if I gave you a key
so I wouldn't have to wonder
how you keep getting in.
And I'd really prefer it
if you checked your cell phone
every once in a while
so that I wouldn't
have to keep doing this.
- I have a cell phone?
- You do
and if you'd check it,
you'd know that Daniel Hardman
topped our bid by 20%.
- That's impossible.
- No, it isn't.
Because the dollar
took a dive against the yen
and it turns out
his client is Japanese.
God damn it,
we are not losing
to that son of a bitch.
Why the hell
did you think I'm here?
We need to go back to
Gianopolous and get more money.
Jessica, he's not going
to pay that much.
No one in his right mind would.
Then go to somebody
who's not in his right mind,
because that lying bastard
isn't going to stop
until his name is
back up on the wall.
Wait a second,
the dollar took a dive
against the yen two weeks ago.
Which means there's something
else going on here.
Oh, I'll tell you
what's going on.
Hardman's been playing with us
this whole time.
What are you saying?
I'm saying I need to go
see a guy about a thing.
Hey.
Where were you?
- I was with you mom.
- What?
Didn't you get the message?
She had to postpone.
She didn't postpone, Rachel.
She blindsided me.
What are you talking about?
Why didn't you tell me
you were fighting with her?
Because mothers and daughters
fight about weddings
all the time.
But you weren't fighting
about the wedding.
You were fighting
about my secret.
And what does that
have to do with anything?
Because she doesn't
even know it.
Because I'm trying
to protect you.
I understand that,
but you have to share
these things with me.
Why?
'Cause instead of
protecting me,
you hung me out to dry.
And how exactly did I do that?
By making it seem like
I'm the one
that's taking away
your dream wedding.
You are the one
taking away my dream wedding.
Rachel.
I'm sorry.
It's just, it's a lot,
and she wanted
to make this announcement
in "The New York Times"
and had this huge guest list
and the Dean of Harvard Law
and I just--
I don't want you
to get caught.
You don't want me
to get caught
or you don't want to marry me?
What?
I went to see Claire.
I know she knows.
And I want to know
if that made you
have second thoughts about us.
You went to see Claire?
Why...
Why didn't you tell me that?
Because she told me
that if I really loved you,
I wouldn't marry you.
And I was afraid
to tell you that
because I thought
maybe you feel the same way.
Well, it, um,
it sounds like you're the one
who's having second thoughts.
No.
No, I'm not
having second thoughts,
but I do hate the idea
that I am somehow dragging
you into something
that is gonna ruin your life.
You are not dragging me
into anything
and you're not ruining my life,
Mike.
I don't care about the plaza
or who comes or--
I don't care about any of it.
The only thing
that matters to me is that
the man that
I'm marrying is you.
And if you take that
away from me,
I don't--
Rachel, Rachel, listen,
look at me, look at me.
I'm not going anywhere.
Okay?
We're getting married.
And it could be
as small as possible
with just our close friends,
okay?
Okay?
Okay.
I need to talk to you.
What is it, Louis?
I couldn't find
what Hardman has on Jack.
That doesn't sound like
something you needed
to be waiting by the elevators
to tell me.
I've been thinking.
What if we tell him
we'll only make him name partner
if he takes a public stand
against Daniel first?
That way, even if he tries
to go against it later,
it won't work.
Did you speak
to him about this?
- I have.
- And?
- He said
he'll be onboard.
And Jessica,
I believe him.
- Then tell him to come see me
at the end of the day.
- Hey.
Turns out
I'm getting married.
Yeah, I know.
I was telling my future
mother-in-law
about how I didn't
have any friends or any family
when I realized,
whatever happened between
you and me...
you're the closest thing
to family that I have.
So what do you say
we get together?
- You wanted to see me?
- I did.
- I, uh...
I just want to say,
based on what Louis said
that you're prepared to do--
- Louis has no idea
what I'm prepared to do
because the only thing
I'm prepared to do
is give you a chance
to come to Jesus.
And you're looking at her.
- Come to Jesus about what?
- Stop tap dancing, Jack.
What the hell does
Daniel Hardman have on you?
- You can ask me that question
a million times.
I'm never even going
to acknowledge its premise.
- And you just did.
And if it's that bad,
and Daniel knows it
and I don't,
then I only have one choice.
So, what I'm prepared
to do now is this.
Resign tonight
and I'll waive your non-compete.
- What?
- Oh, you didn't actually think
I was going to make you
a name partner, did you?
- Here's my counter.
You resign,
and I waive your non-compete.
- You want me gone,
call for a vote.
you do the same thing
because I'm a partner
as much as you
and you're the one
on the ropes.
- I'm not on shit,
because we know what's going on
with Daniel's investor
and Harvey's about
to put a stop to it right now.
- If you really knew
what was going on
between Daniel
and his investor,
you'd know
it's never gonna happen.
- Then I guess we'll just have
to see what we see.
♪ ♪
- Harvey Specter.
What a nice surprise.
Wanna play a little pool?
We go for 10,000 a game
in here.
- You're playing a lot more
expensive game than that,
funding Daniel Hardman
to be your frontman.
- And you're welcome
to go ahead and prove that,
but he's got full power
of attorney
until I get out of here
in two years.
- Yeah, I don't care
how many years you have left.
It's about to feel
like the rest of your life,
because this is where
you're gonna spend it.
Bullshit.
Only the Bureau of Prisons
can approve a transfer.
- I know, but the thing is,
I went to see Sean Cahill today.
Turns out he wants you
to testify in a trial.
So, you can call
the Bureau of Prisons
all you want.
By the time your lawyers
get you out,
you're never gonna
be the same again.
I get it.
You want me
to stop backing Hardman.
- And you go back
to working on your break
and I don't have
to see your face again.
- You're living
in a dream world, pal,
'cause that's
never gonna happen.
- Well then here's my advice.
When you get to Rikers,
drink bleach.
It'll get you
sent to the infirmary.
It's much safer there.
Oh, I don't need
to go to the infirmary
'cause I got something
that's gonna keep me
as safe as a baby
in his mother's arms.
Money.
- You take that chance, Charles,
but if there's one guy
who doesn't give a shit
about your money,
he's gonna get you,
and nobody's gonna stop him.
- Here's the thing, Harvey.
Nobody doesn't
give a shit about money.
Besides, in a week,
I'll be right back here
picking off your clients
one by one.
You want to stop me,
step down.
- What?
- You resign,
his money goes away.
I knew it.
You care about the people there,
just like you cared about your
little brother way back when.
- No way.
No deal.
- Now, before you give me
an answer--
you came here tonight
because you know
you're gonna lose anyway.
So why not save whatever
poor sap it is
while you still can?
- Why should I believe
you would even live up
to your end of the bargain?
- Because I don't
give a shit about your war
with Daniel Hardman.
And I sure as hell
don't give a shit
about your firm.
All I want to do
is see you get down
on your knees
and say, "I quit."
- Trevor.
- Hey, Mike.
- Thanks for coming.
- Yeah, hey,
I'm glad you called.
- Yeah, me too.
- Listen, uh,
about the last time,
I said some things--
- Ah, we both
said some things.
But I did some things.
And I'm sorry.
- Well, uh, I have a way
you can make it up to me.
Come to my wedding.
- It means a lot to me
that you want me there,
but I'm sorry.
I can't.
- What do you mean you can't?
- Look, I'm married now,
and I promised my wife
that that part of my life
is behind me.
- What does that have to do
with you coming to my wedding?
- She didn't even want me
to meet you here.
Don't you get it?
You're breaking the law
every day.
- You're judging me?
- No.
I'm not judging you.
Nothing would make me happier
than to raise a glass
to your new life,
but I can't.
And you shouldn't either.
- Oh, so now
I shouldn't get married?
- No, I'm saying
you should quit.
Oh, okay.
Well, thank you
for the advice, Trevor.
But I don't think
I'm going to do that.
- Michael, the longer you go,
the less the money matters.
The food doesn't taste as good.
The car isn't fast enough.
The view isn't high enough.
And finally you realize
that you would trade it all in
for one night of going to bed
where you don't have to worry,
"When are they gonna
come for me?"
- You almost got caught,
didn't you?
- No, I didn't.
I just couldn't take it anymore.
So finally, I went
to talk to someone.
- Who?
- You know who.
I gotta go.
Take care, Michael.
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net