Sheila Amanda Sazs,
will you marry me?
Yes, I will marry you.
- I want to go legit.
- You can't.
Then I get Lola Jensen
to hack into the bar
and just put me in there,
just like she did with Harvard.
Rule number one
of not getting caught,
you don't move
the goddamn body.
Harvey, I'm stuck.
I can't live my whole life
like this.
You want me to set up
your new corporation?
I want you to join
my new corporation.
We're not lawyers.
We're investment bankers.
Our job blows yours
out of the water.
Scottie, I need you to give
Louis his transaction back.
Does this have something to do
with that favor he did you?
- Yes.
- Tell me what it is.
- I can't.
- Guess we're not sharing
everything with each other
after all.
- Scottie.
- You can't have it
both ways, Harvey.
- Louis, I don't want kids.
- What are you talking about?
I don't like kids.
I was willing to give up Harvard
for you.
You can't give up something
for me?
I understand.
Can I just say something please?
I know you keep saying that
I won't feel this way forever,
but why is it
when the guys shows up
with chicken vindaloo
40 minutes late
with no naan
and no silverware,
instead of throwing the chutney
in his face,
I'm thanking him
and I am tipping him $20?
Do you want to tell me
why that happens?
I don't care.
I hate myself.
I hate my life.
The woman I love is gone,
my heart is broken,
and I really--
to be honest with you,
I just don't have
the will to live.
Hold on.
It's my associate.
Katrina.
Louis, it's 7:55.
Yeah.
I have an 8:00 a.m.
Please cover it for me.
In fact, cover everything,
and unless the building
is on fire and Sheila's in it,
I'm not coming in.
Louis, what happened?
You wanna know what happened?
I'll tell you what happened.
My heart's been shattered
into a thousand million pieces,
and if I can't put my heart
into my work,
then I'm not gonna do
any work at all, so...
How long do you think
you'll be out?
I don't know.
Today, tomorrow,
the rest of the year.
You know,
just don't call here again
because I'm not gonna answer
the number.
Doc?
Dr. Lipschitz?
Hello?
What, are you shitting me?
That was not 50 minutes.
Waiting outside for me?
Bold gesture.
I called you three times.
I had to do something.
- You must be feeling bad.
- I am.
What for?
You're just doing your job.
Scottie, I'm sorry.
What happened with Louis,
I didn't like doing it.
- Yeah, but you still did it.
- And what I'm doing now
is asking you to let it go.
Harvey, it's not that you
picked Louis over me.
It's that you wouldn't
tell me why.
I couldn't tell you why.
There's a difference.
And I'm asking you
to trust me.
Okay.
I can let it go,
but keeping things from me
just can't keep happening,
okay?
I can't tell you
whether or not that's okay,
and I definitely
can't tell you why.
Too soon?
What are you going to do
to make it up to me?
Nothing right now.
I'm taking Mike
to the marathon footwear brunch.
You're taking a date
to an I.P.O. event?
That's so cute.
It's not a date.
He's never gonna put out.
Well, it's too bad
that you're not taking me
because I was thinking
of letting you...
Mr. Specter.
James Quelling.
I'm in a bit of a hurry,
Mr. Quelling.
- I want to do you a favor.
- I don't need any favors.
Yeah, you do, unless you want
Friday's headline to read,
"Marathon Footwear builds
playgrounds that kill children."
My client builds playgrounds
that help children.
And uses a synthetic
full of toxins to do it.
Look, I don't know
who you are,
but I know what you're trying
to do, and it isn't gonna work.
Look,
I'm a reasonable man.
This is a huge moment
for your client.
I won't file this
before Friday.
You think I'm gonna let you
extort my client?
No, I think you're gonna
protect your client
from a claim
that could ruin them.
In fact,
I'm counting on it.
Nice offices.
Enjoy that brunch.
- I got a job offer.
- Holy shit. From who?
Last night.
Jonathan Sidwell.
But I thought Louis
was his lawyer.
He doesn't want me
to be his lawyer.
He wants me to be a partner.
- Investment banking?
- Yeah.
- And?
- I don't know.
- What do you think?
What do you think?
I think that I love you,
and what you want to do
is what I want you to do.
I don't know what to do.
Okay.
Did you talk to Harvey?
If I do that,
all he'll hear is, "Hey, Harvey,
"thanks for doing everything
for me.
I'm thinking about quitting."
Well...
No, but you said
that you don't think of him
as just your boss.
You consider him a friend.
- So?
- So if he can't have
an honest conversation with
your best interests in mind,
he's not your friend, and--
and he shouldn't be your boss.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Suits 3x15 ♪
Know When to Fold 'Em
Original Air Date on April 3, 2014
♪ all right ♪
♪ all that time
imagine this ♪
♪ the greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
I have to talk to you
about something.
Well, unless its value
is in excess of $575 million,
it can wait.
Yeah.
Yeah, it can wait.
Good because our I.P.O.
is in jeopardy
unless we can deal
with this.
Endangering children?
Wait, these things just opened.
This is a bullshit claim.
Maybe, but a bullshit claim
on the right day is better than
a great claim on a bullshit day.
Did you come up with that
all by yourself?
My grandmother
taught it to me.
- What do you need me to do?
- I need you to find
everything there is to know
about this Quelling guy.
Harvey, why don't you
just pay him off?
Protect the I.P.O.?
I worked my ass off
for this day.
He's trying to hijack it.
I'm not gonna be extorted
by some piece of shit
I've never heard of.
Okay. On it.
Jessica.
Donna,
what can I do for you?
I was just walking
by reception,
and I thought you might
like to know--you know,
because it's your firm and--
Donna, get to it.
Charles Van Dyke
is in the lobby.
- Right now?
- 30 seconds ago.
You were right
to come to me.
Would you like me
to send him on his way?
I prefer to take care
of Charles Van Dyke myself.
Excellent.
You can stare at it
all you want, Charles,
but it's not going to change.
I was just thinking,
"I can't believe you put
the mailroom boy's name
on the wall."
I think what you mean is
that you can't believe
yours was ever taken off.
I put that behind me
years ago.
What are you doing here,
Charles?
I suggest we go
in your office and talk.
Right here is just fine.
What do you want?
I want a 30% increase
in my dividend check.
- Good-bye, Charles.
- I thought you'd say that.
This is formal notice of
my demand to audit your books.
You have until Friday
to comply.
You gave up this right
when we ran you out of town.
I think you're forgetting
I retain that right
in the event of any
material change in my dividend.
Your dividend went up.
Materially.
You think
we're hiding profits.
From what I know of you,
you're always hiding something.
- I'm gonna make it fast, Jim.
- James.
That's not what your ex-wife
calls you.
She calls you Jim.
That's one of the nicer names
she uses.
She's been calling you
a lot these days.
Wow, you found out
I'm divorced.
Well, I'll withdraw
the lawsuit.
It's not the divorce, Jimbo,
it's the huge wall
of mounting debt
that's closing in on you
since you tanked
the tobacco litigation.
I didn't tank it.
I lost.
You didn't just lose.
You had an offer that
would have set you up for life.
Instead, you rolled the dice,
went to verdict,
and now you got nothing.
Which is why your wife
left you,
and now you're coming after us
with a fabricated claim.
I didn't fabricate anything.
I have expert reports here.
You've got one report
of possible toxins
in the playground material.
And not one sick child.
And you have an I.P.O.
on Friday,
and if this suit appears
in the Journal that morning,
what do you think
the stock price is gonna be
when they ring that bell?
Got me.
Give me your number.
- 100,000 and we're done.
- Done.
We'll draw up the paperwork.
I've got it right here.
But one thing,
this precludes you
from representing any other
plaintiffs with the same action.
You got me.
I have 100 other plaintiffs
waiting in the wings.
That's a $10 million hit
you just avoided.
I tell you what.
Give me a million,
and we're really done.
James, this covers your debts
and gets you out from under.
You think that means I'm gonna
take less than it's worth?
- It isn't worth anything.
- It is today.
You know where to reach me.
Thought you said
you were willing to go
as high as 500,000.
Yeah, that was before
I realized
what we were dealing with.
This guy doesn't owe money
'cause he got divorced.
He got divorced
'cause he owes money.
- What are you talking about?
- He's a gambler.
How does that help us?
He doesn't know I'm one.
Where's Louis?
- Jessica.
- Where is he?
He's not answering his phone.
He's not answering his emails.
The thing is
I don't know if he--
Katrina,
your job as gatekeeper
does not apply to me,
so I'm going to ask you
one more time.
Why isn't Louis
in the building?
He must still be in court.
Is there something I can do?
What you can do
is find Louis and have him
come up with a way around
this demand
to look at our books.
When should I tell him
you need it?
Yesterday.
You were right.
Quelling's got a game.
- What night?
- Every night.
Well, I hope you know where
tonight's game is because--
- Great.
- Mm-hmm.
You and I are going.
- Um...
- What?
I got a job offer,
Harvey.
Supposed to go have drinks
to talk about it tonight.
I can move it,
it's just, that's...
that's why I hesitated.
- When?
- When what?
When'd you get
the job offer?
- The other night.
- And you didn't mention it.
I didn't know
what I thought.
- And now you do?
- No. It's--
Who?
Jonathan Sidwell.
The spin-off idea?
- Yeah.
- I should have known.
He wants you to be
his general counsel?
No, he wants to make me
an investment banker.
Well, if it were me...
I'd take it.
What? Why?
Because you can compete there
like you do here
with nothing hanging
over your head.
What if I don't want to stop
being a lawyer?
Well, then don't
take the job.
I mean, what do you want
from me?
- I want your advice.
- I just gave you my advice.
No, you told me
what you would do.
I want to know what you think
I should do.
Mike, last week,
you said you'd do anything
to stop being a fraud,
so my advice is take it.
Still be in the majors,
just be a different sport.
Excuse me,
do you have a minute?
Look, you and I have never--
No, we haven't.
I need your help.
You must be scraping
the bottom of the barrel
if you're coming to me.
It's about Louis.
He and Sheila are done.
That's awful.
It's worse than awful.
Jessica needs him on a case
right now.
He won't leave his apartment.
He won't even answer his phone.
Then I'll just go over there
right now.
That won't work.
Even if it did,
we don't have time.
So then why are you here?
Rachel, you don't trust me.
I get that,
but Louis asked me
to cover for him, and that
is what I'm going to do.
You're the best paralegal here,
and you're his friend.
So will you help me or not?
I will.
So...I figured out
what you can do
to make it up to me tonight.
I thought we were good.
Yeah, I'm just--I'm feeling
some residual anger.
Scottie, I'm kind of busy
right now,
and I have plans tonight.
Taking Mike
on another I.P.O. date?
- What difference does it make?
- Hmm.
Sounds mysterious.
Bet you can't tell me
what it is.
- I'm playing poker.
- Poker?
Can I come?
It's a work thing.
- You bring Mike to work things.
- Scottie, I told you I'm busy.
You can't come.
Can I get back to work now?
- What got into you?
- Nothing.
Sometimes at the office,
I'm working.
Fair enough, boss.
Are you sure that's how
you want to play that?
Play what,
the fact that I'm busy?
The fact that you
just snapped at her
when we both know what
you're really angry about.
I'm not angry.
I'm annoyed at the interruption.
You're angry
that Mike wants to leave,
and you just
took it out on her.
- I'm not angry about that.
- No, you're hurt,
and the anger covers the hurt,
but I knew you didn't know that.
I was annoyed
about the interruption
just like I'm annoyed right now.
Bullshit.
You're feeling
exactly what I'm feeling.
The idea of Mike leaving sucks,
and the sooner you get
your brain around that,
the sooner you can maybe
do something about it.
Can I get back to work now?
You can get back to work
whenever you want.
But if all you're gonna do
is stick your head in the sand,
then you're not going to have
an associate or a girlfriend
to get back to work from.
- You give it to her?
- I gave it to her.
She suspect anything?
I wouldn't be standing here
if she did.
- And?
- She thought it was awesome.
Well, she should.
Louis didn't just
come up with a way
to keep Charles Van Dyke
out of our books.
Louis came up with a way
to blow him out of the water.
That Louis.
He is one hell of an attorney.
- Thank you, Louis.
- Right back at you, Louis.
Don't get used to it.
Don't worry.
I'm not looking
to work here again.
Not here,
but you are looking to work?
I've always been able to see
through your bullshit, Charles.
Which is why I'm offering you
these, five cases.
We're co-counsel,
split the profits 50/50.
It announces to the world
that you are back in business,
which is what you really want.
You came to me
bearing gifts.
I still have the card.
"To the man who hired me
for all you've done."
Two days later,
you shoved me out.
I take this to mean
you're passing on my offer.
I'm shitting on your offer.
Okay, Charles.
You were right.
Your dividend check did have
the wrong amount,
but from now on,
it's going to have
the right amount, zero.
- I don't think so.
- Oh, the firm
you had your exit agreement with
no longer exists.
We became Pearson Darby,
then Pearson Specter,
which means
you're not entitled to a thing.
That's not in the spirit
of our agreement.
And neither is your claim.
There's only one problem.
You should have dug deeper
into the fine print.
The entity referred to
in our agreement
is defined in your bylaws
as "any partnership
in which the name partner
is Jessica Pearson."
You didn't know.
My number just tripled.
Your call.
Our hearing is Friday.
You guys playing cards?
You're out of your league.
This game is for real players.
Why don't I give it a try?
Buyin is 25,000.
- What's the limit?
- There is no limit.
Maybe I am out of my league.
Raise $45,000.
I'm putting you all-in.
I've seen guys like you
before.
You think if you bully me
with your big stack,
I'm gonna run and hide.
Here's the difference
between you and me, Jimbo,
I lose,
I pull out another 25 grand,
and another 25 after that.
You lose,
you've got nothing.
You're bluffing.
Then call
or get up and walk away,
but I've sat across from you
1,000 times before.
You won't walk.
Tough beat.
Take your winnings.
What winnings?
I thought maybe it was time
we do a little negotiating.
Well, you have my offer.
- I have a counter.
- I'm all ears.
I want a 50% increase
in base salary.
I want a guaranteed bonus not
tied to our investment returns,
a four-week vacation,
and I want a piece.
- A piece?
- A piece.
- No.
- No piece?
No negotiating.
Look, I know what you're doing.
You can't make up your mind,
so you want me
to make it up for you.
But I don't want someone
who's with me for the money.
I want someone who's with me
'cause they want to kick
some ass.
- I do kick ass.
- And if you want to take
this job right now,
I will negotiate in good faith.
But you don't.
I don't yet.
Starting tomorrow,
I'll be interviewing
other people.
Once I find the right person,
job is gone.
I'm not dropping my suit when
you're going public in two days.
James, you've read
all about Hessington Oil.
The odds were stacked
against me.
I won anyway, because I win.
You won because Edward Darby
came forward.
You got lucky.
Guys like you always think
other people get lucky.
I don't get lucky.
I make my own luck,
and in this case,
it's bleeding you dry.
Right there.
You just gave me your tell.
You have no other money.
You're done.
There's $100,000 in that pile.
It's the exact amount
of the deal we offered you.
Sign it.
We'll fix the paperwork
tomorrow.
This is $1,000.
Cash me out.
He doesn't play anymore
the rest of the night.
You didn't sleep well.
I didn't sleep at all.
It's a big decision.
You still haven't told me
what you think.
Mike, I can't make
the decision for you.
I don't want you
to make it for me.
I just want to know
what you think.
And I already told you
that I will support you
with whatever you decide.
And the way you can support me
right now is by telling me
how you feel.
- It's not my place.
- Not your place?
Just admit it.
You want me to take the job,
but you're too afraid
to say it.
Okay, you want to know
the truth?
You already know
what you want to do.
And if I try to change your mind
and it goes wrong,
then I'm afraid
you're gonna hold it against me.
Would you just say it?
Yes.
I want you to take the job.
Look, I know that you love
what you do,
but every day, you go into work
with the possibility
of being caught,
and it is eating away at you.
If you stay there,
that's just not gonna change.
- Jessica. How did--
- It go?
I'll tell you how it went.
I got hung out to dry.
What?
No, it was a good move.
Oh, it would have been
if our own bylaws
didn't supersede it.
Th--that's impossible.
It was convoluted
and buried in the fine print,
and something Louis Litt
never would have missed.
Look me in the eye
and tell me I'm wrong.
You're not.
He wouldn't have missed it.
So when you came
into my office
and told me Louis
had come up with that move,
you were full of shit.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to help.
Well, that kind of thing
only happens once.
You know how I know
it's not gonna happen again?
Pack up your shit.
I don't care what kind of deal
you have with Harvey.
You're done.
Why wouldn't you tell her?
I said I would cover.
I didn't say I would cover
when it suited me.
Yeah, but he wouldn't want you
to get fired over this.
I should be fired.
I let Jessica look stupid.
Katrina--
Thank you for your help,
Rachel.
I really appreciate it,
but if you don't mind,
I'd like to be alone.
He's not here.
Where is he?
To tell you the truth,
I don't know.
All he said was he had
a late night.
Hmm.
Well, I can come back.
- I was just--
- You're taking the job,
aren't you?
I don't know.
Yeah, you do.
You just don't want
to admit it.
Yeah.
I'm taking the job.
God damn it.
Do you know what that man
has done for you?
Do you know what it took for him
to start trusting someone?
- Donna--
- Don't interrupt me.
So someone's dangling some money
in front of you.
- It's not about that.
- I don't care what it's about.
I'm gonna say what he won't.
He needs you.
You need this job,
and if you can't see that,
then you might as well
just leave right now.
Donna, someone's offering me
a way out.
- So you don't care about him.
- Of course I do,
but I also care about my life
with Rachel.
I don't want to live my life
like this anymore.
Then you better be the best
goddamn investment banker
this city has ever seen.
Scottie, I'm sorry
I was angry in your direction,
but it was really
about something else.
Let me guess, Donna explained
your feelings to you,
and now you're here
to apologize.
Maybe.
What was the something else?
Mike got a job offer.
And you don't want him
to do it.
No, I don't.
Well, if you want him to stay,
you know what's actually
a nice tactic?
Telling him
you want him to stay.
What?
Had I known "tell me
what's going on with you"
meant "I'm going to tell you
what to do,"
I might not have
taken you up on it.
Oh, okay.
Mmm.
- I'll see you in there.
- Okay.
You have that paperwork
for me?
Well, I got something for you,
but it's not that.
Didn't you learn your lesson
last night?
I learned to listen.
When you talked,
you mentioned Hessington Oil,
so I looked back into it.
Turns out you don't create
your own luck.
Your associate does.
What the hell
are you talking about?
He conspired
with Harold Gunderson
to file a lawsuit
against your own client
so you could bribe witnesses
not to testify.
We didn't bribe anyone.
- That was a legal settlement.
- Don't try to tell me
two rookie associates
who went to law school together
and started at the same firm
made this happen
without collusion.
I don't need to tell you
anything 'cause
there's nothing to tell.
Well, you're gonna
have to tell someone something,
because that suit was filed
one day, settled the next,
and those witnesses cancelled
their flights to New York.
That is a bribe,
and when I bring it
to the attention of the bar,
you and your associate
are going to be in deep shit.
Now who showed his tell?
Here's your money back.
And either I go to the bar,
or you settle for $2 million.
You have until tomorrow.
Where's Mike?
He's in there.
Harvey--
- Harvey.
- Not now.
You need to call Lola Jensen.
What?
You need to get her
to hack into the bar
and put your name in.
What the hell
are you talking about?
A week ago, you told me
that the number one rule
was not to move
the goddamn body.
A week ago, people weren't
sniffing around you.
- Harvey, my job offer is not--
- This isn't about your offer.
Quelling knows
about your bullshit lawsuit
with Harold Gunderson.
He turned me in?
No, but he will
if we don't cave.
- He can't prove anything.
- He doesn't have to.
He hands you in to the bar,
they look you up, we're done.
Not if I'm not here.
Oh, that's why
you're in here.
You're taking the job.
I am.
And you think
an addicted gambler
who lost his wife, his child,
and his house is gonna stop
coming for you just because
you're not working here?
You said it yourself.
Hacking into the bar
is twice the crime
I've been committing.
I am telling you
Quelling is on the trail.
You don't do this,
we're gonna get caught.
- There's got to be another way.
- There isn't.
- I don't believe that.
- Then you better
figure something out fast,
because tomorrow morning,
we're done, and you quitting
isn't gonna change that.
You can't fire
Katrina Bennett.
I can fire
whoever I want to.
She was covering for Louis.
What are you talking about?
Louis's engagement is over,
and he's losing it.
He won't come in to work,
he won't pick up his phone,
and he just didn't want
anyone to know.
Then why are you
telling me?
Because I helped her
cover for him.
Are you saying
I should fire you too?
I am saying that...
We made a mistake,
but that we were just
looking out for Louis,
and I know how much
you value loyalty,
so I don't think
that should be the thing
that costs Katrina her job...
or mine.
- Jessica.
- I need you.
No, listen, I just need
a little more time.
And had you asked me for it,
I would have said yes,
but instead, you had Katrina
cover for you.
Oh, that little traitor.
What, did she rat me out?
No, she didn't.
She's so loyal to you
that she tried to pass off
her work for yours.
Louis, Van Dyke wants
to look at our books.
What?
We can't have that.
I know.
This was her fix.
Oh, no,
and you used this on him?
I did,
and then I fired Katrina.
- Jessica.
- I know.
I can't fire her
for being loyal.
But I can't afford you
sitting here licking your wounds
while I get my ass
handed to me.
Please, just listen to me,
okay?
I cannot see straight.
I cannot think straight,
and even if I wanted
to come and help you, I wouldn't
be any good to you, so...
Louis...
I know you loved Sheila,
but do you love your firm?
You know I do.
And when you love a woman,
can you stand the thought of her
being with another man?
- No.
- Well, Louis,
Van Dyke is trying to get
into Pearson Specter's pants.
What are you going to do
about it?
I'm gonna put on
a goddamn chastity belt.
How?
'Cause Katrina actually
was on the right track.
Van Dyke's claim is gone
if the partnership is gone.
The bylaws say it's not.
No, it is
if we become an L.L.C.
We can't do that
by tomorrow.
We'd have to rewrite
every contract.
Boy, wow, Jessica, you
sometimes really surprise me.
You don't think I know that?
I have an army of associates
that I've trained
within an inch of their lives.
My name is
Louis goddamn Marlowe Litt,
and my firm is under siege,
so don't you tell me
what I can and cannot do!
- Hey.
I don't want to interrupt,
but I was just wondering
what happened with Mike.
He's leaving.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Can I ask you something?
Did you tell him
that you wanted him to stay?
I didn't get around to it.
You--you didn't
get around to it?
I was gonna tell him, and then
he told me he was leaving,
and then other shit
came up, so...
So you just dropped it?
I told you other shit came up.
What other shit?
I mean, you had
an emergency case filing,
so you let your protege
walk out the door?
- It's complicated.
- Okay.
Well...then share it with me.
Quelling came after us.
The Hessington witnesses.
What?
That's bullshit.
You may have blurred some lines,
but you certainly didn't
cross any.
Fight him.
- No, I can't.
- Why?
Look, I don't want
to talk about it.
What is going on here?
When somebody pisses you off,
you get in the ring.
What are you saying?
What I'm saying is that
you're not taking on Quelling,
but you're letting Mike
walk out the door
without trying to stop him.
I think one thing changed
the other,
and I want to know why.
Maybe what changed
is his desire to be here,
and maybe what I have to say
doesn't matter.
Of course it matters.
Now, what is this really about?
Because it's sure as hell not
about some stupid case.
You know what?
God damn it!
For once, can't it just be
about what I said it's about?
You didn't say
what it was about.
Harvey, I'm really sorry
that the Mike thing turned out
this way.
I am, but I can't say
that I didn't see it coming.
- Scottie, it isn't--
- What? It isn't what?
It isn't what it seems?
Because I don't know
what it seems.
All I know is that any time
I ask you about anything,
all you say is,
"I can't talk about it."
I'm just gonna stop asking.
Then we'll just
make up later,
and we can do it
all over again tomorrow.
Quelling can't hurt us
anymore.
- You went to see Lola.
- I looked at his accounts.
I wanted to find out
where all that money came from
to find all those clients.
He doesn't have the money.
And yet his rent gets paid,
and they don't turn off
his electricity.
Holy shit.
Guess you didn't have to see
Lola after all.
You think I got access to that
with a court order?
So you did go see her?
You put the idea in my head.
I just came up
with a different agenda.
We got him.
No.
You got him.
What?
Your going-away present.
Be a lawyer one last time.
Knock this guy out.
You have
my settlement check.
I don't have a dime
for you.
Then I guess the bar
is going to be hearing from me
first thing in the morning.
Well, then, they'll also
be hearing from me.
Disciplinary rule 5-107a,
"accepting compensation--"
- I know what it says.
- Then you also know
the penalty
is being disbarred.
You took money
from our client's competitors
to trump up
your bullshit suit.
You didn't come by that
legally.
And they're not gonna care.
I don't know
if you've noticed,
but I don't have
a hell of a lot to lose,
so sign my deal or get
the hell out of my office.
Well, here's the thing,
James.
I don't either...
Because today is my last day
as a lawyer anyway.
- Bullshit.
- Look at me.
Good luck
in front of the bar.
I wasn't always like this.
I had tobacco in my sights.
They offered me a lot
of money.
I could have made a fortune.
But $15,000 per client
for people with cancer?
I risked going to verdict
because I wanted
to get those people something
that could make a difference!
And I lost everything...
My clients, my wife, my kids!
You lost them because
you gambled them away, James.
I know that.
Please.
Being a lawyer is what I am.
It's who I am.
And if you take that away...
It's up to you, James.
I'll drop the suit.
I promise.
Louis,
where the hell are you?
You said
you could get it done.
I walk through those doors,
our books fly open.
Get here now.
Well,
this should be fun.
We've never been across
the aisle from each other.
Which is why you don't realize
that it won't be fun.
We'll see what we see.
Case 41432,
Van Dyke versus Pearson.
Look at that.
Game time.
Ladies first.
Son of a bitch.
For being polite?
Were you being polite
when you hired me?
What does one have to do
with the other?
"To the man who hired me,
for all you've done."
Do you want to know what I meant
when I wrote that card?
The day you made me that offer,
I asked you,
"did it have anything to do
with gender or race?"
You swore it didn't.
You lied to me.
- It didn't.
- You're lying now.
You know, Daniel Hardman
may have used people,
but he didn't give a shit
about their gender
or their color.
- He showed you the list.
- Right next to my name,
an asterisk.
Not "Law Review."
Not second in my class.
Diversity.
- You were treated the same.
- You tell yourself that,
but we both know the truth,
which is why I sleep at night
just fine.
Well, it doesn't change
the facts in this case, does it?
No. No, it doesn't,
but this will.
Charles, you remember
Louis Litt?
Sorry, I couldn't run.
Doctor wanted me
to take it easy.
Hey, Charles.
Great to see you.
You told me that story
to stall.
- That was a stall...
- Hmm.
But this is for me.
When I saw that asterisk
next to my name,
it made me sick to my stomach,
because in one second,
I understood
how you will always see me.
So that card was a thank you,
because if I hadn't
have felt sick,
then I might not have worked
as hard as I did
to get where I am today.
You woke the dragon,
Charles.
How do you like me now?
I know you're there.
You need anything?
No.
The I.P.O. is wrapped up.
We go public Monday morning.
I wasn't talking
about the I.P.O.
I was talking about
how you're feeling about Mike.
I know.
Okay.
Good night, Harvey.
I'm gonna tell Scottie.
About Mike?
Are you crazy?
You can't have it
both ways, Donna.
You can't tell me to open up
and then keep my secrets.
You spent more than a year
covering it up.
You tried to get him to commit
another crime to cover it up,
and now--
You said I should tell her
what's really bothering me!
I meant your feelings.
I didn't mean
confess to a felony.
These are
my goddamn feelings!
Donna, I did something
when I hired him.
It's caused all of this.
I can't tell her,
and it's driving me crazy!
Okay.
Look, Mike is gone, Harvey.
I hate that he's gone,
but the jeopardy's gone too.
It's done.
And now you want to turn around
and tell someone who--
Someone who what?
Nothing.
No, you better
finish that sentence.
Someone who's pissed at you,
Harvey.
Someone who keeps finding
a reason to be pissed at you,
and it's not the third time,
and it's not the fifth time,
and it's not the last time.
I thought you were trying
to help my relationship,
not shit on it.
Okay, you want to yell at me?
Fine.
Because I know
you're not mad at me.
And I know you're only
telling me this stupid idea
because you want me to tell you
what you already know.
You can't, Harvey.
It's good that you want to,
but you can't.
Could I have a minute?
Congratulate me.
I'm officially
a member of the New York bar.
You went to Lola?
I made a mistake.
I want to stay.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net