Ava Hessington,
you're under arrest.
Conspiracy
to commit murder.
If you're looking
to ride
some partner's coattails,
you're gonna have
to look somewhere else.
Stephen Huntley,
senior partner, London office.
I want you to find out
what the hell that guy's up to.
I know about your deal
with Edward.
I don't need you
baby-sitting me on this case.
Tony Gianopolous got a hold
of that video.
I think he's trying
to take over the company.
You told me
to take this deal.
I did,
and now here I am.
I didn't know
about these murders.
What you don't seem to believe
is neither did I.
You're not the fool anymore,
Louis.
Mike Ross is.
And I can't take it back.
Your future at this firm
is over.
This is everything I have
on Tony Gianopolous.
Welcome to team Litt.
We just admitted to each other
that we're defending a murderer.
It doesn't really seem
like cause for celebration.
It's not a celebration.
I made a deal with Darby
to take over the firm
from Jessica.
- You heard?
- I heard.
- Vote's in 48 hours.
- She's not losing that vote.
- I'm getting my shit.
- I got my shit.
- Conference room.
- Five minutes.
What is she doing here?
She's my new associate.
So that's why you made
the video.
You seem upset
that she led you to believe
that she was trying
to befriend you
when it turned out
she was gonna betray you.
- Louis.
- You got a problem with that?
No.
No problem.
Not as long
as your daddy's here.
Do I have to have
another talk with you?
- He had a talk with you?
- Yes.
But I didn't feel the need
to run to you to protect me.
Second choice never does.
I can't believe it's up to me
to be the adult in the room.
Maybe it's time
we get down to business.
Good, because the first order
of business
is discussing what to do
following Ava's statement.
She's not making a statement.
- Yes, she is.
- Ava makes a statement,
Cameron's gonna be all over it.
Cameron Dennis
isn't the problem right now.
The problem is Ava Hessington
isn't a credible CEO.
The problem is she's on trial
for murder.
And public perception
says that she's as guilty
as Jean Valjean with a loaf
of bread in his pants.
We're facing a vote for control
of her company in two days.
Talking under threat
makes her look desperate.
And not talking makes her look
either guilty or incompetent.
We need to send the message
to Wall Street
that she's in control
and she's got nothing to hide.
This is a meeting
about how to keep Ava's company
without endangering
her murder defense.
Did it ever occur to you that,
if she's cold enough
to kill off opposition
to her pipeline,
she's cold enough to pull off
lying to the press?
I mean, we all know
she did this, right?
This isn't open
for discussion.
She's not saying a word.
I'm afraid it's too late.
What did you do?
She's on her way
to an interview right now.
It'll run in the Journal,
and then it will blow
Gianopolous
and his bullshit takeover
attempt out of the water.
- Connelly.
- Mr. Connelly, I do apologize,
but I'm afraid we have to change
the location of our interview.
- Who is this?
- Miss Hessington's assistant.
Well, I spoke to her assistant
this morning--
Yes, Rebecca handles
Miss Hessington's schedule.
I handle her life.
What, so I'm supposed
to traipse all over town
because of what she'd prefer?
- Not prefer. Insist.
- Insist?
I'm giving her a forum
to tell her side of the story.
An exclusive forum
which needn't be the case.
Now make no mistake,
Mr. Connelly,
Miss Hessington is the one
doing the favor here.
So, if you'd like
to speak with her,
my driver will be more
than happy to take you to her.
Or if you would prefer
to call Rebecca,
I'm sure she'll be able
to set something up for you
sometime say next December.
Go ahead and order.
Connelly's
running a little late.
He should get here
at ten past "you're not giving
an interview."
I wasn't trying
to keep this from you.
You didn't exactly cc me
on the memo.
Very well.
You want the truth?
I don't particularly appreciate
being muzzled.
I suggest you don't think
of it as muzzled so much
as keeping you out of jail
for the rest of your life.
And what'll you have me do,
Harvey, hmm?
Take a week in St. Barts?
Because that is not going
to happen.
I know that's not going
You're on trial for murder.
And because of that
a tender offer's being made
on a company
with my family name.
And with all that going on,
the fact that I haven't made
a statement defending myself
is bullshit.
It's not bullshit.
It's smart.
Of course you see it that way.
You think I'm guilty.
I've told you before
it doesn't matter what I think.
But if you think saying you're
innocent is gonna make people
believe you, it won't.
Because you know who says
they're innocent?
Everybody.
Every day
I keep my mouth shut
our stock takes a dive,
and that makes me vulnerable.
I get it.
You want to convince the world
you're not responsible
for these murders
so you can keep control
of your big oil company.
That is not what I said.
Well, that's how Cameron
Dennis is gonna make it sound.
Ava, you're on trial
for your life.
This company is my life.
And that's exactly
what it's gonna look like--
a greedy oil exec
clinging to her money factory
with her blood-stained hands.
Very well.
You've made your point.
Now I suggest you find a way
to get me out of both situations
'cause I am not losing control
of my company
to Tony Gianopolous.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ Suits 3x04 ♪
Conflict of Interest
Original Air Date on August 7, 2013
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ the greenback boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
New dress?
What can I say?
It deserved me.
What's the occasion?
Does a girl need a reason
to look spectacular?
Sugar me.
Um, before anyone sugars
anyone, if you two are dating,
you need to know that we have
a very strict policy
in favor of that.
And we have
a very strict policy
to keep our sugar
to ourselves.
Oh, that's a pity.
I'm partial to a little
sweetness in the morning.
Well, then I would recommend
the bakery on 52nd.
You care to join me?
I hate to deny you the pleasure
of my company.
I think I can manage
without it.
Since you're
from a different country,
I'll translate: "She finds you
a bit douchey, love."
My loss.
Ladies.
Oh, that man is trouble.
It's okay.
I can handle it.
Oh, no, it's okay.
I don't need you to.
Wait.
What are we talking about?
The fact
that he's into me.
Were you here?
He's into me.
Then why was I the one
getting all the stares?
Haven't you ever heard,
"go after the second prettiest
to get
the prettiest's attention"?
No, I've never heard that.
- Well, it's a thing.
- Oh.
Are you saying
I'm the second prettiest?
I'm saying you are to him.
Oh, the dress.
He asked you out?
Last week.
- And?
- I passed.
- Why?
- Why should I go out with him?
Just because he's charming
and hot?
- And witty and British.
- And has a title.
- He does?
- No.
But even if he did,
that wouldn't be a reason.
I told you, Rach,
I don't mix business
with pleasure.
Business?
He's only here
for six weeks.
And he is based
out of London.
It's practically
a different company.
And it's definitely
a different country.
- So you'll consider it?
- Nope.
Well
What's going on
with Ava Hessington?
I convinced her
not to give an interview.
How'd she get it in her head
it'd be a good idea
in the first place?
Louis.
Is he aware
she's up for murder?
Is he aware that most people
don't line their offices
with pictures of themselves?
Evidently not.
You know he's still got one
of his dead cat?
Harvey, leave the cat alone.
Stupid cat.
How dare
you sabotage my case?
I didn't sabotage shit.
You set that thing up
behind my back
and you didn't tell me about it
until you thought
it was too late.
Yeah, because I knew
the minute things heated up
on the takeover attempt,
you'd want to take my case back.
Take your case back?
I don't know how familiar
you are with the game of law,
but murder trumps takeover.
- You condescending piece of--
- Louis.
Harvey's right.
The woman
can't make public statements
while she's on trial for murder.
Trump.
Well, if she's gonna keep
her mouth shut,
then she's gonna have
to step down
or we're gonna lose this vote.
Asking her to step down
would be asking her
to cut off her arm.
If we don't cut off her arm,
Harvey,
we're gonna lose the patient.
She's my client.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Ava Hessington
is not my client.
Hessington Oil is.
And they generate $14 million
a year in billables.
Have you not been listening?
Ava Hessington
is Hessington Oil.
Not for long.
- Excuse me?
- Louis is right.
If she steps down now,
we can still win the vote
and keep them as a client.
Well, who's gonna convince her
to do that?
We don't have
to convince her.
We can just go to the board.
We don't even have to tell her.
Like hell you will.
And like hell I won't.
Harvey, this needs to happen.
- No, I won't do it.
- This is my call.
I'm afraid it isn't.
Excuse me?
You and I both know
who assigned me to this case,
and it wasn't you.
It was the man you chose
to merge with.
The same man who has a 51% share
of our law firm.
So unless
you're gonna undo that,
you're gonna live with this.
Was she pissed?
I bet she was pissed.
Not as pissed
as you're gonna be.
What are you talking about?
You're on Katrina duty
for the next two days.
What?
I'd rather be on latrine duty.
- It's not an option.
- Okay, then I'm going AWOL.
Well, let me connect
the dots for you, Forrest Gump.
Even though Jessica gave in
on the strategy,
Louis made it clear he's willing
to sacrifice Ava.
And you don't trust him
to play by the rules.
Which is why you're gonna work
side by side with her
to figure a way out of this jam.
And at the same time make sure
she and Louis don't shaft us.
Not bad, Forrest.
Okay, if I'm Forrest,
then you're Bubba.
- Shrimpin' bidness.
- Harvey...
If Ava loses her company,
will Darby still back you
as managing partner?
I didn't ask,
but I sure as hell wouldn't.
What is it, Louis?
I just wanted to thank you
for backing me earlier.
I had your back because you
had the best strategy.
It still means a lot to me.
And, you know, I don't know
where Harvey gets off
telling you how to run things.
It's over, Louis.
I'm moving on.
It doesn't have to be.
What exactly
are you proposing?
Allow me to be
your black swan.
Let me do the things
that your position precludes you
from doing, the dark choices,
the distasteful wet work.
You mean like using lye
to dissolve a human body?
I mean using lies to dislodge
a pesky CEO.
Well, we've been told
that's not an option.
Not for you, maybe,
but as we just agreed,
it's the right option
for the board.
And Harvey and his master Lord
Poppycock don't have to know.
Louis, I appreciate
your offer, I do, but--
But the one time
you take my side over his,
you're not willing
to fight for it.
I'm willing to fight.
I just won't do it
behind Darby's back.
Look, I swear
it'll never come back to you.
I didn't say I was afraid
to get caught.
I said I don't want
to operate that way.
Now if you'll excuse me.
Need I remind you you had me
go behind Harvey's back
to do the same thing
with McKernon Motors?
That was not the same.
I get it.
You were in charge then.
You're not in charge anymore.
Hey
Ooh, all jammed up?
I'm afraid so.
You just need to coax it
a little.
Oh, and how does one
do that?
Oh, it's all in the touch.
Well, I've been nothing
but gentle.
There's a time to be gentle,
and there's a time
to be firm.
You should see
how I handle the fax.
I can imagine.
You know, in fact,
given your skills,
I think you'd probably be
the ideal person
to handle my short-term needs.
See, I'm in the states
on a limited basis,
and I've got nobody to help me
with my workload.
I get it.
You're forced
to do everything yourself.
It's getting exhausting.
And you need someone
to help relieve the pressure.
Naturally, I thought of you.
Not Rachel?
I think you know
the answer to that.
I knew it then.
I know you did.
It'll be a brief,
casual arrangement
whilst I'm in New York.
I wouldn't have time
for anything more.
Then we have
an agreement?
I don't know.
What kind of boss would you be?
Demanding.
But very generous.
Generous is good.
As is Daniel Day-Lewis
doing MacBeth.
You do realize
that this arrangement
would involve
no secretarial work?
I'd be disappointed
if it did.
- Katrina Bennett.
- At your service.
- God, I love the sound of that.
- Your wish is my command.
- My wish is for you--
- To work hand in glove
with Mike Ross on getting rid
of Tony Gianopolous,
keep an eye
on what they're doing
while at the same time
limit their understanding
of what we're doing.
How do you know all that?
- It's my job.
- Wait a minute.
I thought you can't stand
Mike Ross.
All of a sudden
you're willing to work with him?
- It's my job.
- If I ask you to murder someone
on a rainy winter's eve,
how would you respond?
You want a gun or a knife?
If you were less attractive,
I'd love you.
I know.
Louis, why aren't we
just kicking Ava Hessington out?
She'd be gone before
she even knew what hit her.
If Harvey had
half your brains,
that's exactly
what we'd be doing.
But he doesn't,
and as much as I hate
to admit it, he's in charge
of this decision.
He's not in charge
of this firm.
Go to Jessica,
she'll agree with you,
you'll get the credit,
and Harvey will be
off Hessington Oil before
he even knows what hit him.
Katrina, as much
as I appreciate your suggestion,
I refuse to operate
in a duplicitous manner.
Then I'll find us a way to get
rid of Tony Gianopolous anyway.
Ahahah-ah.
I might have to let you look
at what I've got,
but I don't have
to let you touch it.
Touch it?
This room is a disaster.
This room is fine.
I know where everything is
and what everything is.
What are you even doing?
Finding dirt on Gianopolous.
You're dealing with one
of the most sophisticated
raiders in the world.
He's not leaving a trail
for you to follow.
Oh, yeah?
And what's your strategy?
You gonna record him and make
an embarrassing video?
No.
Gonna play a little game.
Monopoly?
You don't think
I started with that?
There's no way to have
a monopoly
in the oil business.
It's too goddamn big.
And even if you could,
these are all the companies
that Gianopolous owns
in any way,
and these are the biggest
companies in the oil industry.
There's no way
to connect the dots.
Well, do you want to go
down the same road and have
another fight or do you want
to try to figure out a way--
- Shit.
- What?
We've been looking
in the wrong place.
Shit.
Shitty shit.
You're into The Wire?
shit.
Jessica.
What a lovely coincidence
running into you in Toronto.
This is not a coincidence.
Well, I hope it's still going
to be lovely.
I need you to make it
perfectly clear to Harvey
that he has no say
in the Hessington Oil
takeover battle.
And why would I do that?
Because he's making
a huge mistake and using
your name to do it.
And let me guess,
you'd like her to remove herself
from management.
She can do it herself,
or I can do it for her.
But either way
she's got to go
until this trial is over.
I'm afraid
I don't see it that way.
Well, you're wrong.
And you're overstepping.
Listen to me.
She stands to lose control
of this company permanently
if we don't do something.
Then do something.
I'm trying,
but you're cutting off my legs
because of a bond you had
with her father.
No, because I value
relationships over money.
Well, I value the terms
of our merger.
And Hessington Oil was one
of your biggest selling points.
And Harvey Specter
one of yours.
I'm not going to stand
for losing this takeover.
Then don't.
But Ava isn't going anywhere.
One more thing.
Instead of spending firm money
to fly
to another country
to question my judgment,
feel free to call first.
I'll be happy to give you
the same answer over the phone.
This is brilliant.
We've got the connection.
We just need to figure out
how to stop it.
I already have.
This is great work, Katrina.
You struck oil.
It was actually Mike's idea.
Why do you want
to give him credit?
Because if I don't,
you won't listen
when I say
you should take him with you.
I'm not taking anyone
with me.
It's an opportunity
for him to see you
beat the shit
out of a living legend.
Tony Gianopolous
gets blown out of the water,
and Mike gets blown away.
And Jessica hears
about it all.
I'm gonna suggest this
to Harvey.
Feel free to tell him
it was all your idea.
Don't mind if I do.
Oh, perfect timing.
Harvey, I was just gonna run
something by you.
I don't have time, Louis.
I'm working on a murder case.
I just dropped by to inform you
Mike's coming with you
to see Gianopolous.
Like hell he is.
- Excuse me?
- I'm not taking anyone.
- Louis--
- And don't Louis me.
This is my case, and you've
been sticking your nose in it
ever since I got it.
Sticking my nose in?
You only have this case
'cause I was kind enough
to give it to you.
You only gave it to me
because you hadn't realized
that you were responsible for
turning Ava's bribery charges
into murder charges.
- You're off this case.
- Go ahead.
Call Ava.
Tell her that you're diverting
your attention
from her murder trial
to work on this.
Yup.
Didn't think so.
Get out of my office
because I got a meeting
to prepare for.
What just happened to him?
- He got "Litt" up.
- Damn straight.
Have you seen this?
It's an article,
in today's Wall Street Journal
painting me as the picture
of corporate greed.
As I told you before,
if you speak out--
I have the chance
to save my company.
Louis Litt is doing that
right now.
- That is not the point.
- That is the point.
We can still save your company,
and you won't have to hurt
yourself at your murder trial.
No, the point is I want
to speak at my murder trial.
That's not wise.
And how many murder trials
have you conducted
in your many years?
- Ava.
- Silence is damning.
Look at this article.
I'm already guilty.
If you take the stand,
Cameron Dennis is gonna rip you
to shreds.
This is not up for discussion.
I will have my say.
Then I'm gonna show you
what you're in for.
Well, you wouldn't be doing
your job if you didn't.
Have a seat,
Mr. Litt.
I'll be with you
in a minute.
You'll be with me?
Yes. As I said.
In a minute.
Uhhuh.
Well, you know,
I'd ask you who you are,
but the truth is I, uh...
I don't really give a shit.
Where the hell's
Tony Gianopolous?
Mr. Gianopolous is upstairs.
To get upstairs, you have to get
through those doors.
And to get through those doors
you have to get through me.
And you're not getting
through me.
Well, perhaps I have the key.
This is a balance sheet
from one of our subsidiaries.
This is nothing.
Sorry.
Forgot.
It's a combination lock.
This represents the totality
of Gianopolous Limited holdings.
You control 40%
of the U.S. radio stations,
corn production,
interstate trucking,
and that's just the tip
of the iceberg.
Looks like I picked
the right employer.
One problem: Hessington Oil
owns enough of those industries
to get you in trouble
with the FTC.
Yeah.
Think we wouldn't find that?
You think we wouldn't?
These folders are out of date.
We've already divested.
Into this, this, and this.
So what? Hessington doesn't
have holdings in those areas.
They do now.
And if you don't leave 'em
alone,
you're gonna be tied up
with my friend from the FTC
until kingdom goddamn come.
Got that, spank?
Then it's a good thing
Mr. Gianopolous
arranged an exception for us
over dinner with his friend,
the commissioner of the FTC.
- That's not--
- Legal?
Yes, it is.
As long as we disclose it.
Which we always do.
You think
you're the first lawyer
to try to outsmart us?
We're not lawyers.
We're investment bankers.
We call you for the paperwork.
We didn't go to Harvard.
We went to Wharton,
and we saw you coming
a mile away.
Spank.
Oh, by the way, Mr. Gianopolous
is in Monaco.
Christina will validate you
on the way out.
Finally cleaning up?
Can't stay here forever.
How'd your meeting
with Ava go?
She wants to testify
at her own trial.
- Are you kidding?
- Yeah, I know.
We're working on it.
Thought you'd be with Louis.
He went to go see Gianopolous
by himself.
I hope it works.
We have a good plan.
For what it's worth,
I suggested Louis
take you with him.
Shit.
As Sil would say,
"just when I thought I was out,
they pull me back in."
Okay, so you watch
The Sopranos too?
Nobody watches The Wire
without starting
with The Sopranos.
You, uh, you really
suggest that to Louis?
It was your idea.
You deserve the credit.
Truce?
Truce.
Shit.
You trying to score some extra
edamame from the delivery guy?
Please, Yuki always brings me
extra edamame.
Well, then who's
the touch-up for?
And did you do a costume change
without leaving the office?
I have a number
that calls a guy...
Who knows my size.
I need that number.
- I can't give you that number.
- Mm.
Oh, my God.
You have a date with Stephen.
It's not really a date.
It's more...
of an arrangement.
An arrangement?
He has some short-term needs,
asked if I could help him out
while he's in town,
blah blah blah,
I'm meeting him at 8:00.
Blah blah blah?
What's blah blah blah?
Oh, you know,
it's just...
This, that, and the other thing.
Uhhuh.
And does he know
that blah blah blah constitutes
this, that, and the other thing?
Rachel.
Stephen and I communicate
a little more subtly--
suggestive banter,
double entendres.
We both know
what we agreed to.
It sounds to me
like you agreed
to a hot and steamy affair.
I'm not gonna even
dignify that with a response.
Oh, my God, did you agree
to a hot and steamy affair?
I have no idea.
- Louis, what can I do for you?
- I want off this case.
I take it you struck out
with Gianopolous?
I didn't strike out.
What I did was almost pull
a rabbit out of a hat.
But the truth is
the one good move we had
has been taken away from us,
and I'm not gonna be left
holding the bag
because Harvey chose
to handcuff me.
Louis, I'm not taking you
off this case.
But I am taking
the handcuffs off.
Wait, are you saying
that I have your blessing
to go to the board and convince
them to ditch Ava Hessington?
I'm not saying anything.
Got it.
Wet work.
This conversation
never happened.
What is it?
Have you ever said to Harvey,
"this conversation
never happened"?
- Louis.
- Please tell me you never have.
Would I tell you if I had?
I'll take that as a no.
Good night, Louis.
Black Swan.
Wednesday, 6:52 p.m.,
it happened.
Wow.
You aren't having
a heart attack, are you?
Would that put a crimp
in your evening?
Well, I guess I could scalp
your ticket,
seeing as it is the hottest
of the season.
You know, I practically had
to sell my spleen for them.
That's funny. I heard
you got them from a client.
Did you also hear
that I traded him my spleen?
I don't care if it cost you
a lung.
Daniel Day-Lewis in a kilt?
Worth it.
- I'm really glad to hear that.
- Of course you are.
You found out
how much I love the theater.
You don't think the reason
that I arranged all of this
is because I looked
into you?
Didn't you?
Sure I did.
You know,
I'm actually to theater
what Harvey is to sport.
Nah, you don't give a shit
about theater.
You love sports.
- Rugby mostly.
- Nice try.
We do what we can.
But we are going for dinner
with Daniel Day-Lewis
after the show.
You're kidding.
I may be indifferent
to the theater,
but I know
how to get things done.
You are good.
I told you that
on the first day we met.
I'm better than good.
What time is dinner?
10:30.
Then we better get going.
Oh, the show doesn't start
for another 20 minutes.
We aren't going to the show.
Taxi!
Is that really necessary?
It will be in the deposition.?
I don't care
about the deposition.
- Harvey--
- You want to know
how you come across, you have
to see how you come across.
Now answer my question.
Did you bribe
a foreign government?
Why are you hesitating,
Miss Hessington?
Something to hide?
Look, I think what Harvey's
trying to say--
You hesitate,
they won't trust you.
Your bribery
isn't in question.
Cameron is gonna enter that plea
into evidence.
You have to own it
and move on.
And I suggest you do it
more believably,
because when you're up there
staring down the barrel
of 12 executioners,
there's no changing your mind.
Do you think I don't know
you're trying to rattle me?
Rattle you?
I'm just giving you the facts.
Cameron's gonna rattle you.
And it's gonna work,
because you and I both know
you did this.
- How dare you!
- How dare I what?
This is your idea.
Then ask me
a goddamn question.
You bribed that government.
What's to stop anyone
with a pulse
from believing you knew
that money was payment
for killing those people?
Because life is more important
to me than money.
Then why the hell did you pay
that bribe in the first place?
Because that's how it works
over there.
Murder is also how it works
You did it.
You know it.
And you're not convincing
anyone.
Very good.
Finally we get to it.
If you check your records,
you'd know the reason we won
that bid is we were
the only company who took it
upon ourselves
to go to the people.
Because you needed to see
what your obstacle was.
My obstacle?
We paid $100 million more
than anyone else
on the condition that the money
be used to relocate any family
who lost anything within
50 miles of that pipeline--
job, home, land, livestock.
Anything.
What happened over there
sickens me.
I lose sleep over it
every night.
And as soon as I am
out of this nightmare,
I am going to shut down
the entire project--
the pipeline, the oil fields,
all of it.
So I've had just about enough
of you two wondering
whether I'm guilty
of these murders or not.
Is that a good enough trial run
for you?
Holy shit.
She didn't do it.
I understand
you have a strategy
to defeat the takeover attempt.
I do.
But it involves a conversation
about how essential
you find Ava Hessington.
If the only way
to beat Tony Gianopolous
is to get rid of her,
then I don't think
we have a choice.
If you need cover
for the other board members,
then you can just tell them that
Pearson Darby recommended that.
And I'll recommend to them
that we retain
Pearson Darby.
So we have a deal.
What's the matter with you?
We just deposed
Ava Hessington.
You deposed
your own client?
Practice.
You couldn't convince her
not to testify?
No, not that.
She convinced us
that maybe she should.
Well, there would be only one
reason to even consider that.
She didn't do it.
- No way.
- I know.
You said, if she's cold enough
to do it,
she'd be cold enough
to lie about it,
but this woman is about to lose
her title, her company,
her whole life...
And I know
that she is telling the truth.
You don't have to believe me.
Take a look for yourself.
- Hey.
- What happened?
- He agreed.
- She's out.
It'll be done tomorrow
before the tender offer vote.
- Then we still have time.
- What are you talking about?
She's innocent.
What?
Take a look at this.
I figured out
what we're gonna do.
And what is that?
What we should have done
in the first place.
We're gonna let her talk
to the board.
And preempt tomorrow's meeting
with one of our own.
If she can convince us
she's innocent,
she can convince them
to keep her in charge
and vote against the takeover.
Winwin.
- Have Louis set it up.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Louis?
Yeah.
He'll love it.
Letting her talk
is what he wanted her
to do in the first place.
Get it done.
Louis, what are you
still doing here?
You put in a long day.
You did a great job.
Now go home.
I can't.
Why not?
She didn't do it.
Who didn't do what?
Ava Hessington had nothing
to do with those murders.
How do you like that?
I'll see you
in the morning.
Jessica.
I'm serious.
She's innocent.
And what does that have to do
with me going home tonight?
It has everything
to do with it.
Harvey agreed to let her
talk to the board.
That's all I ever wanted.
Louis, if they don't oust her
tomorrow morning,
they will lose that takeover
vote tomorrow afternoon.
She will be pushed out
either way.
Well, at least
I won't be responsible
for taking away
an innocent woman's company.
You're not responsible for it.
This is a hostile takeover.
They're coming tomorrow,
and the market doesn't care
whether she's innocent or not.
Harvey's gonna think
it was me.
It was you.
And he would have thought that
before.
Please do not stop me
from going back to that board.
Louis, you offered
to do this.
You're not doing this to Harvey.
You're doing this
for your client,
Hessington Oil.
Ava Hessington
is Hessington Oil.
- Not anymore.
- Jessica.
Enough.
This conversation did happen,
and it's over.
How long have
you been standing there?
Long enough to know
that if this law thing
doesn't work out, you'd make
a lousy boy Friday.
I'd ask you to help, but I
wouldn't want to take advantage.
And I'd say yes, but I don't
want to be taken advantage of.
Though I am happy to watch.
I'm nothing but a piece
of meat to you, aren't I?
Quiet, copy boy.
Same time tomorrow night?
Absolutely.
Interesting.
If you find copy rooms
interesting,
you need to get out more.
Oh, I'm not talking
about the copy room.
I'm talking about you
and Stephen
and the spring in your steps.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say
you were sleeping with him.
Oh, my God,
you slept with him, didn't you?
No.
How was it?
Suffice it to say,
I was awesome.
Oh, wait, sorry,
you probably wanted to know
about him, didn't you?
That was the point
of the question, yes.
Eh.
- Really?
- God, no.
I may have met my match.
Oh, my God.
And the arrangement?
Ongoing.
- Well, did you tell Harvey?
- Oh, my God.
- What?
- I never thought about Harvey.
I'm Donna. How could I
have not thought of that?
Because you weren't thinking
with your brain.
- Good one.
- You were thinking with your--
- Yeah, I got it.
- So what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna tell him
as soon as he gets back.
- Have everything we need?
- Everything.
Where's Louis?
He's gonna meet us over there.
We should all be going
together.
Well, at least Ava's here
on time.
- What the hell did you do?
- What are you talking about?
I just got voted out
of my own company.
Wait, the vote on the takeover
isn't supposed to be
till this afternoon.
Well, they had a different one
before that,
and I'm out.
And what I want to know is,
did you know?
Ava, I didn't go
behind your back.
Well, you may not have gone
behind my back,
but this never would have
happened if you'd let me
speak publicly
in the first place.
Look, Ava, my believing
in your innocence
wouldn't change my mind
about you talking to a reporter.
Then why were you going
to let me speak today?
Because an interview
isn't the same thing
as a closed-door meeting
within your own company.
Well, they had
a closed-door meeting,
and the only person
who benefited from that was you.
How's that?
I may be out,
but you're not.
Pearson Darby has been
conveniently retained
as Hessington Oil's
legal counsel.
You think I don't know
this was you?
I don't care whether you know
it was me or not.
I stand by what I did,
and I'd do it again.
You mean selling Ava out
because of your personal issues
with me?
This isn't personal,
and it's not about you.
Bullshit.
Ever since Darby handed me
this case and not you,
you've been pissed.
I wasn't pissed until we had
a disagreement on strategy,
and you invoked his name
to cut me out.
I get it.
I wasn't wrong
about it being personal.
I was wrong
about which person.
You're not pissed at me.
You're pissed at yourself
for getting played.
What did you just say to me?
You heard me.
Fools rush in,
and you're the one
who gave him the 51%
in the first place.
I merged with Edward
for the sake of this firm,
just like what I did today
with Ava.
And the only one in this room
taking things personally is you.
Tell yourself
whatever you want,
but don't tell me it doesn't
have to do with Darby
and don't tell me
it isn't personal,
because you can't stand
being number two.
- Harvey, do you have a minute?
- No, I don't.
I need Edward Darby
on the phone right now.
By the way,
where were you this morning?
What are you talking about?
I was here.
You weren't here.
I was in the copy room.
Well, what the hell were you
doing in the copy room?
I was finishing up
a couple things for Stephen.
You're working for Stephen?
- I made some copies.
- You work for me.
Sorry.
It was a one-time thing.
Well, since you haven't gotten
Darby for me yet,
what do you want?
Nothing.
It can wait.
What do you want?
I want to tell you
that I enjoyed working with you.
I thought I was gonna be able
to say the same.
If it means anything to you,
I told Louis
to stop the plan
to get rid of Ava.
Did you know
he wasn't going to?
No.
But the truth is,
even if I did,
I wouldn't have done anything
to stop it.
Is that supposed
to make me believe you?
It's supposed to make you
understand me.
You're loyal to him.
I'm committed to him.
Good night, Katrina.
Good night.
What did she want?
Nothing.
Tell me
she enjoyed working with me.
- Did you?
- Did I what?
Did you enjoy
working with her?
I mean, I just kept seeing
you guys working together
all the time, and you just
seemed to be bonding away.
- Are you jealous?
- It's not funny.
I'm not smiling
because it's funny.
I'm smiling
because it's sweet.
You didn't think it was sweet
when I was jealous
of you and Jenny.
You and I
weren't together then,
but we are now.
Right.
Which is why
it bothers me more now.
Rachel...
I trusted you
with my secret,
my life.
If I trusted you with that,
don't you know that
that means I...
That I...
What are you--
what are you trying to say?
You know
what I'm trying to say.
Don't say it now.
I don't want to hear it here.
Here? Where we've done
pretty much everything else?
- Mike, I--
- I love you.
I love you.
I don't want
to keep it in anymore.
I love you too.
And in this moment
I don't care who knows.
What you did amounts
to nothing short
of insubordination.
Did you fly all the way
from another country
to tell me that?
You could have just called.
I gave you
a very clear directive,
and you defied me.
Do you want to get into it?
I most certainly do.
When I agreed to merge
with you,
I knew it was 51-49,
but I didn't think
you would lord your 2%
over me like a hammer.
And when I agreed
to acquire you,
I didn't think
I'd have to.
Are you saying
you regret this merger?
I'm saying perhaps I
should have paid more attention
to the red flags,
such as covering up
the embezzlement
of a former partner.
Something you were more than
willing to use to make the deal.
You went behind my back.
And you stuck me
with this case
and then risked losing me
a huge amount of money.
I gave Harvey this case
after already handing you
a huge amount of money.
I am in charge
on this side of the ocean.
Because I allow it
to be that way.
And there it is again.
51-49.
Until now I believed
that Harvey was the wild horse
that couldn't be tamed,
but perhaps it is you.
I think maybe Harvey was right.
It is personal.
But I didn't make it that way.
You did when you allowed
your feelings
for Ava
to cloud your judgment.
And as you pointed out,
I had a partner once
who made decisions
based on his personal shit,
and I will not allow that
to happen again.
And 51-49 or not,
I just took 14 million and put
it on my side of the ledger,
so do me a favor, Edward,
and turn off the lights
on your way out.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net