Previously on Suits...
You're guilty of bribing
a foreign government
to get your pipeline.
Guilty as charged.
You think
you're not replaceable?
I've been doing this
before I met you,
and I'll be doing it long after
I've forgotten all about you.
Please don't do this.
Your beloved associates
are mine.
What you want is
a long, drawn-out trial
that puts our stock
in the toilet.
I'm here to tell you
he's recusing himself
from the case.
So he appointed
a special prosecutor.
I win, you back me
for managing partner.
You want
to take down Jessica.
Yes, I do.
Holy shit.
Was that a good "holy shit"
or a bad "holy shit"?
Harvey, you just told me
that you're planning a coup.
Give me a second
to figure that out.
Not a coup.
It's a move.
And when you're done
with your lecture--
No.
No lecture.
I just have one question.
Do I get my own office?
Harvey, if you want
to be managing partner
and Darby
agreed to back you,
then I'll follow you
to the ends of the earth.
But before we start,
I want to make sure
you're ready to do this
to Jessica.
I am.
Then let's go beat the shit
out of Cameron Dennis.
I know you don't want
to see me.
And yet--
I just wanted
to let you know that I got
a copy of the letter that
Jessica blackmailed me with,
and I made it clear to her
that I would take it
to the D.A.
if she ever threatened me,
so what I did
will never happen again.
Never should have happened
in the first place.
Close the door
on your way out.
Donna and I
have work to do.
There's a harsh reality
I need to inform you of,
and it's a bitter pill
to swallow.
But the truth is,
a mistake was made.
A fatal mistake.
And as much
as I hate to admit it,
our time together is done.
No more work,
no more laughter.
Remember?
No more mentorship
and, um, no more anything.
See, I reached too high,
and I fell.
And my punishment is the end
of my tenure
as head of the associates.
So I would like to leave you
with the immortal sentiment
of Robin Williams.
There have been
other associates before you.
They believed they
were destined for great things,
just like you.
If you just listen,
you can hear 'em whisper
their legacy to you.
Carpe diem.
Seize the day, people.
Make your legal lives
extraordinary.
Oh, Captain,
my Captain.
There was a time
I would've been relieved
to see that--
no more Louis.
It's just wrong.
This whole merger
is wrong.
How'd it go with Harvey?
It didn't.
Did you tell him
about Jessica?
Yeah.
He didn't care.
What?
I just wish I could give you
a hug right now,
but I can't because we still
want to keep us quiet.
Well, come on.
You can give me a hug.
Something could've happened.
Something bad,
like a...
My dog could've died.
Oh, you have a dog now?
I was really close
to this dog.
Well, the best way
to get over the death of a dog
is to get a new one.
Mmmm.
- No?
- No.
I'm just--I'm just too upset.
I'm--I don't know
if I'm ready
for a new fake dog
right now.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Just leave me
like this.
How did it go?
I don't know.
Awful.
Probably the hardest thing
I ever had to do.
Louis, we just merged,
and I wish I could undo
you losing the associates,
but I can't.
What I can do
is take
what you've been giving
to so many for so long
and have you channel it
into one.
You mean...
I want you to mentor
your own associate.
Finally.
The D'Artagnan to my Athos,
Porthos, and Aramis.
All for one
and one for all.
En garde!
Sorry.
Jessica, wait.
I can have anyone?
Louis, take your pick
of the litter.
- Good morning, Ms. Paulsen.
- Spit it out.
Is that any way to start
the day?
You want something.
I need the 411
on the breakup.
- Are we in high school?
- Life is high school.
And I need to know
if the prom king
and his boy wonder
are still an item.
What high school
did you go to?
Donna,
it's a simple question.
Did Mike and Harvey
break up break up,
or did they take a time-out
and, like, say to each other,
"hey, let's see other people
and make sure that we're sure."
I see what's going on here.
Jessica feels sorry
for you,
so she's given you
your pick of the litter.
And now you're sniffing
around here,
trying to put the moves on Mike
behind Harvey's back.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I would never do that.
No, that's why I'm here
to ask permission.
So ask him.
Well, I think
it might go better
coming
from a different source.
- You want me to ask him.
- Yeah.
Would you please?
No.
Why?
Because it would be
so much more fun
for me to listen to you
ask him.
Well, let me
get this straight.
You want my permission
to take Mike
and force him to be
your associate.
No, I would never force him
to do anything.
It has to be consensual.
Not like Sally Jones
and senior prom.
Wait a second.
Did you just admit to a crime?
No, a crime was committed
upon me.
Okay, I don't want to,
but I have to.
What crime?
My mom felt bad for Sally,
so she forced me to take her.
Well, what was so bad
about her?
She had four nipples.
Okay, if that date
was so bad,
I mean,
how did you find that out?
Okay, you know what,
Harvey,
do I have your blessing
or not?
Knock yourself out,
Louis.
See, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
You're just saying that because
you think he's gonna say no.
- Oh, I know he'll say no.
- Well, I know you're wrong.
So you better think
about this very carefully,
because once permission
is given,
you cannot go back.
Speak now,
or forever hold your peace.
Fine.
He's yours.
I'm sure you two
will be very happy together.
Good, 'cause
when I'm done with him,
Mike Ross will be begging
to be my associate.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ Suits 3x02 ♪
I Want You to Want Me
Original Air Date on July 23, 2013
♪ all that time
imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Well, well,
what a surprise.
Jessica.
Last time we saw each other,
you were blackmailing me
out of my job.
Here to do it again?
Because you gave me
what you had on me.
I just want
to make one thing clear.
What I did to you,
I did to you.
Don't take it out
on Harvey.
Oh, that's sweet.
Like a mother
protecting her cub.
Take me on
anytime you want,
but don't punish
Harvey's client
for what I did.
You did?
You just happened on evidence
from his time
at the D.A.'s office?
Oh.
Ah.
The redhead.
Well, it doesn't matter,
because he may not have been
the one to betray me,
but he didn't stop it.
So after you threw him
under the bus and I saved him,
he should have thrown himself
back under the bus?
You just don't get it.
Yes, I do.
What you're really pissed at
is that he chose me
over you.
Not you.
What you are.
I put bad guys away.
You try to figure out
how to let them do
whatever they want.
So don't come in here
telling me
that I'm taking something out
on Harvey's client,
because I'll tell you
something--
she did this.
You made me a mixed tape.
Watch it,
and then make me an offer,
which I'll reject
because...
I got your client
dead to rights.
Mmm, mmm.
Well?
This is the best steak
I've ever had in my life.
That is the best steak
you will ever have
in your life.
As much as I appreciate
for once
not having to eat my lunch
from the hot dog stand,
what are we doing here?
Can't a man
just take out another man
in the middle of the day
for some steak and some wine
and some cheesecake that's
gonna knock your socks off?
Uh, some men could.
But I think you and I
both know
that you are not one
of those men.
- True that.
- Mm.
Want some more wine?
Don't mind if I do.
And you gotta
try this cheesecake.
Oh, no, Louis, I'm--
mm--
You know what I mean, right?
What do you think of that?
Hey, Louis! How was the steak?
- Heaven.
- How about you?
Best steak you ever had?
Uh, best steak
I will ever have.
You taught him well.
What are you guys,
brothers?
Oh, I'm just kidding.
Louis here's got
a lovely sister, Esther,
two wonderful parents.
Who the hell are you?
I am Mike Ross.
Louis and I work together.
I wanted him to know
who he was working for.
- Oh.
- And I would like you to know
who's working for you.
'Cause Mike here,
he's the best steak
you'll ever have.
You want to know
what you're working for?
Tina, Gina, Adrian.
They've been here 50 years
between them.
They are my family.
That's
what you're working for.
I-I understand.
I do not understand.
Eminent domain.
- Shit.
- Final hearing's Tuesday.
If we don't win, this place
becomes a shopping center.
Then this place
becomes a shopping center,
because nobody wins
eminent domain cases.
But what if we did,
Mike?
Then he'd get to keep
his restaurant.
He would get to keep
his dream,
and I would get to keep
my dream.
- And what is that?
- To rewrite the law.
And the way to do that
is to win
an un-winnable case.
What do you need me to do?
You went to see Cameron?
I was just coming
to apologize.
For interfering
on my case.
He's pissed at you.
He's going to take it out
on Ava.
I wanted to let him know
the person
he should be pissed at
is me.
Well,
it's not gonna stop him
from taking it out
on Ava.
Which is why
I was coming to apologize.
Are you also going
to apologize
for sending the message
that I need you
to help me fight
my battles for me?
I don't want
to fight Cameron for you.
I want to fight Cameron
with you.
When the evidence
is stacked against you,
you do what O.J. did--
you hire the dream team.
Oh, that's our bar?
O.J.?
Did he walk or not?
Fine.
But I'm Johnnie Cochran.
You know.
You know I know.
Mike told me.
Nobody had to tell me
after you sent me
on that wild goose chase
after American Gigolo.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You know, it's not
that you violated
the sanctity
of our friendship.
It's that you violated
the sanctity of Richard Gere--
something
I would like to do,
but not the way
you did it.
Look, I was just trying
to get Mike back with Harvey.
I understand.
Because I never want
their thing to be our thing.
It's not.
And the way to keep it
from becoming our thing
is to stop talking about them.
Done.
So you and Mike.
I know.
It's a lot.
Do you want to talk
about it?
Of course I do.
Okay, I think
we should start
with the most important
emotional question.
Okay.
I'm actually
getting worried for you.
You don't know
the half of it.
Louis, you said 5:00.
It's only 4:30.
I've been here
since we ate.
I've been researching
every eminent domain case
ever tried,
starting with 1905.
Clark v. Nash.
I thought you wanted me
to be doing
the research?
I did.
But if I don't do it too,
how can I help you?
You're helping me?
Yeah.
I help you help me.
That's how it works.
Help me help you.
What?
Help me help--
it's Jerry Maguire.
- Jerry Mc-what?
- You--
okay, if you've gone
over every case file,
then you know
that the reason nobody wins
is because there is no chink
in the armor.
Well, then we make
a chink of our own.
If I'm on a jury,
I'm looking at a bribe,
plain as day.
Because that's exactly
what it is.
I don't care
what it looks like.
There's no audio.
It's our story
versus theirs.
It's a shady deal
and a case full of cash.
Their story is going
to be more compelling.
Cameron's not going
to risk trial without more.
- Do you think he has audio?
- What would it say?
It would have this gentleman,
Colonel Mariga,
asking if we had
the money
and my number two, Nick Howell,
showing it to him.
Then he would thank us
for paying
a pollution remediation fee.
That sounds
environmentally sound.
Except we'd already
remediated everything
that needed
to be remediated.
Which is how you knew
it was a bribe.
- Yes.
- Hmm.
The question is,
did you ever use
that word in that room?
I may be brazen,
Mr. Specter,
but I am not a fool.
Then the audio
won't help them anyway.
The Colonel?
No, they're still in power.
He's not getting indicted.
What?
Cameron's got your protege.
No.
I've been grooming Nick
for ten years.
I've taught him everything
he knows.
Like how to bribe
a foreign government?
That is not the same.
He would never turn on me.
You'd be surprised
what people you trust
would do when someone
puts them in a position
where they think
they don't have a choice.
Harvey's right.
Once someone puts
another person down the path
of bending the law,
people tend to turn
on each other.
You don't know him.
When's the last time
you spoke to him?
A few days ago.
Call him.
He won't take your call.
You're wrong.
He always takes my calls.
Hi, it's Nick.
Leave a message.
Let me tell you
what that message really said.
"Hi, Ava.
It's Nick.
"I'm not here right now
because I'm cutting a deal
to sell you out."
- Hey.
How's it going with Louis?
You know,
it's actually not bad.
But the truth is,
I would rather be--
- No.
- What? Come on.
It's the middle
of the night.
Louis could be back
at any minute.
- I can be fast.
- I know.
That was a one-time thing.
Mm, mm, mm.
Enough, enough.
But I--
okay.
Yeah, you're probably right.
The last person
we want catching us is Louis.
Did it ever occur to you
that's he's trying
to recruit you?
Can we just
for once assume
that Louis doesn't have
an ulterior motive?
I got us
some refreshments.
I will leave you two
to your work.
- So?
- Yeah.
Louis, it's the middle
of the night.
Where did you get all this?
I'm the new quartermaster,
remember?
Okay.
Here, check this out.
Whoa, no one's thought
to come at it this way.
Mike, this is outstanding.
I actually got the idea
from a movie.
- Moneyball.
- I thought you hated sports.
Moneyball
isn't about sports.
- It's about math.
- Exactly.
One problem.
It's outside the scope.
- What if it weren't?
- What if I could fly?
Well, I can't help you
with that.
But if we want to get it
in the scope,
we just have to get
the other side
to put it there for us.
Morning.
Nice Mustang, Harvey.
I see you're still trying
to be Steve McQueen.
Not trying.
Being.
This is the scene
where he corners the asshole.
Speaking of movies,
did you enjoy
the one that I sent over?
It's not often we get
the whole crime on film.
All you have is a silent film
with no proof of anything.
And by the way, I'm going
to have you sanctioned
for withholding evidence.
I gave you that video
in a timely manner.
You gave us that video,
so we'd take our eyes
off Nick.
Nick who?
The Nick you have stashed
in a hotel room somewhere.
Oh, that Nick.
Now that you mention it,
I probably should put him
on my witness list.
I'm a little
out of practice.
Yeah.
There you go.
Now...
Why don't you get
that piece of shit
out of my driveway, okay?
The first time
I ever had steak,
it was at Peter's.
I mean,
I'd had steak before...
But I never
had steak before.
But that's not
why I'm here today.
You see,
halfway through the meal,
Peter came
over to my table,
and he asked
how I'd liked it.
He wanted to know
because he cared.
He cared about me.
I don't make friends
very easily,
but the second I set foot
in Peter's Steakhouse,
I had made a friend
for life.
And that is how Peter
treats every single person
who walks
through his door.
So I don't care
what they say.
Your Honor,
this is not a public benefit.
Your Honor, I'm...
I'm touched.
He makes me want to run
right over there
and get a steak.
But as for the Supreme Court
decision in Kelo,
public benefit is determined
on a quantitative,
not qualitative basis.
Well, I'm glad
you brought up Kelo,
because we happen to have
some quantitative evidence
right here.
Kelo was decided in 2005.
Eight years later
and still,
nothing has been built
on this land.
No jobs created, no taxes
collected, no money made.
Zero quantitative benefit.
Just because they say
it will be better
doesn't mean
it actually will be.
Even if it were true,
we have every right to do it.
The state determines benefit,
not the court,
and until such time
as the law is changed,
you have no authority to affect
the state's determination.
Uh, Your Honor, you can
establish authority today.
There's no basis for that.
You have no choice
but to uphold
the established practice
of eminent domain.
I'm afraid opposing counsel
is right.
Demolition begins next week.
I just remembered something
about Moneyball.
The A's never actually
won the World Series.
I'm sorry, Louis.
Now is not the time
to be sorry.
What is it the time for?
Get in.
Nah, I think I'm good.
Mike, there's nothing
to be afraid of.
It's just good, clean mud.
That doesn't make
any sense.
Is this about the fact
that I'm in the nude?
Please don't harp on that.
Yeah, I'm just saying,
I know
how the younger generation
gets hung up on that stuff,
but you don't have to worry
because you have
your own self-contained unit.
Okay, if I get in,
will you stop saying words?
You know,
if you go in with boxers,
you're not gonna
have them later.
You're gonna have
to go smokeless.
That disloyal piece
of filth.
Believe me,
I know how you feel.
Do you?
Because I've heard you prefer
to work alone.
Well, I don't.
I may have been above him
when we started,
but for the last two years,
we worked together
side by side.
I'm not a sentimental person,
but it meant something to me,
and I thought it meant
something to him.
- He deserves to be shot.
- He does.
But I suggest
we promote him instead.
You want to give him
a new title
to keep him
from testifying?
I believe it will require
a substantial raise as well.
You know
that's not what I meant.
You're suggesting
bribing a man
to get you
out of your bribery charge.
"In for a penny,
in for a pound,"
mother always said.
This is
what Cameron wanted.
He didn't give us that video
so we wouldn't find Nick.
He gave us Nick,
so you'd try to bribe him.
Well,
how can you know that?
Because Cameron knows
people are who they are.
You bribed once,
you'll bribe again.
Well, then what are you
suggesting I do?
Because I'm going to make
a run at him.
No, I'm gonna
make a run at him.
Louis.
Yeah?
This is the best damn mud
I've ever had.
Hey, I--
I know why you picked me
for this case.
I wouldn't have picked you
if you didn't.
If you wanted me to be
your associate,
why didn't you just ask?
Because you would've
said no.
- Louis, come on.
- No, Mike.
I know what people
think of me,
and I know
what you think of me.
I knew you'd remember
all the bad things
about working with me.
I just wanted to remind you
of some of the good ones.
I remember
all the good ones,
but I also remember
after those things,
you going back to being
the same Louis I met
the first day of work.
The Louis who fired someone
right in front of my face
for the sole purpose
of teaching me to be afraid.
You're right.
I remember you once said
that my actions matter
and that it's not water
under the bridge.
You've changed me.
You make me want to be
a better man.
Wait, are you saying
I complete you?
You have seen Jerry Maguire.
No, I'm quoting
my cinema hero,
the character of Melvin Udall,
expertly portrayed
by Jack Nicholson
in As Good As It Gets.
- Oh. Never saw it.
- Oh, well, then you're lucky.
Why is that?
Because you can still see it
for the first time.
The first time.
- Yeah.
- That's it, the first time.
- What?
- The judge.
You were making your argument
about the first time.
He wanted to rule in our favor,
but he couldn't.
I know, that's why we need him
to rewrite the law.
No, we don't,
because there's already
a provision in the law
that works for us.
It's in section--
No, no, no, no.
First of all,
I cannot mix work
with mudding, okay?
Let's hit the showers.
I can't wait to stick it
to opposing counsel.
Do you need me to give you
a hand out of there?
I know who you are.
You shouldn't be here.
No, Nick.
I'd like you to go.
No.
You wouldn't.
You'd like to give me
five minutes
to see if I can get you
out of the box you're in
before you sell your soul.
I didn't want to do this.
You wouldn't let me in
if you did.
I had no choice.
Ava's in trouble
whether I testify or not.
That's what Cameron
wants you to believe.
- You haven't seen the video?
- I saw a business transaction.
- You don't believe that.
- I can sell that.
You just got to keep your head
and shut your mouth.
Just do
what you're here to do.
Threaten me,
or offer me a deal.
- I've considered both.
- Cameron said you would.
Cameron's wrong.
I'm not going to do either
because I think
you care about Ava.
I do.
Then think about this.
Whatever deal
Cameron offered you,
it's based on a lie.
He doesn't have anything.
He's just trying to use
your fear
to pit you against Ava.
Look, I've seen it happen
before,
and the one thing
I can tell you is
you go through with it,
you'll regret it
for the rest of your life.
Because she'll
never forgive me.
Because you'll never
forgive yourself.
Okay, what is so important
that we need
to have
an emergency hearing?
Your Honor, we need to be
heard before demolition starts.
What's he going to do now,
tell us
about his first demolition?
It was riveting,
but this has nothing to do that.
Your Honor,
based on the new zoning
put through
for their project,
we're simply asking
for a revised valuation
of the property
that they're taking.
$100 million?
That valuation
has no basis.
It has
a mathematical basis.
Specifically, the present
value of future cash flow,
as shown right there.
Bullshit. You've heard
of voodoo economics.
This is voodoo math.
They're making crazy assumptions
to inflate their value.
Just like Kelo,
but that really
didn't seem to bother you
when it was in your favor.
Your Honor,
this is ludicrous.
They're only picking
that number
because they know
it makes our project
too expensive
to be feasible.
Well, in the words
of opposing counsel,
even if that were true,
we have every right to do it.
Hi, Donna.
I love your dress.
And I love
when you compliment me
before you ask
for something.
You're so insightful.
Look, I know we said
Harvey and Mike's problem
isn't our problem,
but Louis is stealing Mike.
It's not stealing
when someone's available
for the taking.
You knew?
When do I not know?
Louis asked
for Harvey's blessing with Mike,
and he gave it.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because we agreed
that their problem
isn't our problem.
I know.
But Harvey
doesn't really want this.
- And you know that because--
- Because he can't.
Look, he needs you
to do your Donna thing
and help him get over it.
Harvey listens to me because
I tell him what I believe.
What do you believe?
That Mike betrayed Harvey.
- Mike was blackmailed.
- And then he betrayed Harvey.
- Donna, how can you--
- How can I what?
I just spent
the last year hiding
your boyfriend's
double life.
I'd say I'm
a pretty understanding person.
But what I don't understand
is when someone
takes loyalty like that,
and they throw it
in the garbage.
Would you like me
to say that to Harvey?
Sorry I asked.
Won't happen again.
- Yeah, that was awesome.
- That was a great job, Mike.
- Thanks, Louis.
- Rachel.
- Looks like you won.
- The judge is ruling tomorrow.
Then what were you
just celebrating?
Well, we were
dead in the water,
and now we have
a fighting chance.
I'm glad.
Is something wrong?
Oh, I just got
into a fight with Donna.
About what?
I went to tell her about you
and Louis, and she just--
You went to Donna
about me and Louis?
- I thought she could help.
- You what?
I thought if she knew,
she'd go to Harvey,
and they'd just put
an end to it.
Someone butting in
and telling him what to do
is only going to push him
further away.
I didn't tell him
what to do.
I went to Donna.
If Donna tells him,
all it says is
that I'm too weak
to fight my own battles.
God, if it's coming from you,
that makes it so much worse.
Why?
What?
Harvey forbid me
to tell you anything.
You and Harvey
talked about me?
After we went out,
I went to him,
I said I wanted
to tell you--
And he said
I wasn't trustworthy.
It's not that.
He didn't want you
to go out with me.
No, it's not that either.
He didn't have a problem
with us going out, he--
Oh, so it's okay if you
screwed me so long as you lied.
Rachel.
Oh, my God.
That's why you cut things
off with me.
- I didn't want to lie to you.
- I can't believe him.
Rachel, he didn't
just risk everything
he had for me once.
When Jessica found out,
he put everything
he had on the line
for me again.
I hope you know as you
stand here defending him,
he has no intention
of ever forgiving you.
Because I found out when Louis
asked Harvey for his blessing,
he said, "Take him.
He's all yours."
So instead
of getting mad at me
for trying to get Harvey
to forgive you,
maybe you should
get pissed at Harvey
and think about moving on.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
I said I was sorry,
I gave back the office,
I helped you with your case,
I even blackmailed Jessica.
Harvey, I get that you
are pissed off at me,
but eventually,
you are going
to have to forgive me.
Forgive you for what,
making me hire Katrina?
Getting high on the job
your first week?
Betraying me
with Jessica?
Or for telling Rachel
about your secret?
You cut me loose.
Okay?
You fired me.
I was at my lowest point.
She was there for me.
She's still there for me.
Congratulations.
I hope you two
are happy together.
So you're gonna punish me
by giving me to Louis?
Well, let me
tell you something.
It failed.
I actually like
working for Louis.
He makes me feel
like I'm working with him,
not for him.
Well, I'm glad to hear that.
Because I didn't give you
to Louis as punishment,
I gave you to Louis
because you and I are done.
Harvey,
I regret what I did.
But I'm telling you right now,
you're gonna regret this.
Maybe you didn't hear me.
I said you and I...
We're done.
Whatever it is, I'm not really
in the mood right now.
Harvey,
I know how Cameron works.
He's setting something up.
You think
I don't know that?
He's setting Ava up
to bribe Nick.
- Isn't that what you just did?
- No.
I went to him and told him
he'd regret being disloyal
to her.
Something I know
a little bit about.
Harvey, do you know
what started it
between the Hatfields
and the McCoys?
I didn't catch the miniseries,
but I heard Costner killed it.
Doesn't matter.
Because whoever
they say started it,
I guarantee you,
the other side says,
"bullshit."
You went to Darby
for this merger behind my back.
And then you picked a fight
with him behind my back.
And then you
blackmailed Mike behind mine.
And I was only able
to do that
because you brought a fraud
into my firm
in the first place.
So you do think
it's my fault?
What I think is
I regret where we are,
and I've been trying to get us
back to where we were.
And what would the evidence
of that be?
What evidence
would you like?
Why don't you
tell me the truth
about why the hell
I'm on this case?
All right, Harvey.
I lied to you.
When I told you I fought
to get you on this case,
I didn't.
Darby made that call.
And I used it as an opportunity
to reach out to you.
- "Used."
- To reach out to you.
Which I am now here doing
without using anything.
So do you want
to let it go or not?
I want to know one thing.
If you had it to do over,
would you do it again?
Deposition's on the books
with Cameron tomorrow.
You want me there or not?
Harvey, I'd introduce
you to Nick,
but I understand
you two already met
when you witness-tampered.
Nick works
for Hessington Oil.
We're their lawyers.
Therefore,
I didn't witness-tamper.
And if you say it again,
I'm gonna slap you
with a slander suit.
Well, let me slap you
with something.
Tony Gianopolous got a hold
of that video somehow,
and he gave it
to your shareholders.
They're filing
some sort of lawsuit.
I think he's trying
to take over the company.
You son of a bitch.
You leaked it.
I deny that.
And if your client
says that again,
I will slap her
with a slander suit
to go
alongside her bribery charges.
And by the way,
Nick wasn't swayed
by your attempt to tug
at his heartstrings.
Emotional pleas?
What did you do to him,
Jessica?
This is not the kid
I mentored.
Hold on a sec.
You were never my mentor.
Jessica was.
You're just
a fast-talking car salesman
that hides behind the line,
"I do good."
Now get out of my face
while I confer with my client.
You told me
you knew this man.
I thought
that was an advantage.
Instead, you've goaded him
into orchestrating
an attempt
to take over my company.
You know
how sometimes the doctor says
you're gonna feel worse
before you feel better?
- What are you saying?
- What he's saying is
let us know how you feel
in half an hour.
- Hey.
Do you have a second?
I want to talk to you
about how we left things.
I don't know,
did you run it by Harvey first?
- What?
- I understand
that he has final say on who
his employees fraternize with.
Look.
Harvey wasn't just
trying to protect himself,
Mike, Jessica, and me.
He was also trying
to protect you.
Right, my protection's
at the top of Harvey's agenda.
He barely knows who I am.
Rachel.
And if he did know me,
he would know
that I would never tell anyone.
Okay, look.
You want to be mad
at Harvey, fine.
But you might as well
be mad at me,
because I told Mike
the same thing.
What?
I dragged Mike
into Harvey's office,
and I told him
that Harvey was right.
- That Mike should lie to me?
- No.
I told him
that he should get over you.
Was that before
or after I came to you
and told you
that I kissed him
and that I called him
and told him how I felt?
It was after.
You told him
not to be with me,
and then you let me think
that he didn't care about me.
No,
I told him what I thought,
and then I tried
to help you move on
because their truth
wasn't mine to tell you.
I thought you were my friend.
I am.
You cared more
about protecting Harvey
than protecting me.
Yes, Rachel!
That's my job.
I get that everyone's jobs
are important.
This wasn't about a job
for me.
It was about having a life.
But I guess
you wouldn't understand that.
Rachel...
I'm going to walk away
before you and I can't go back.
It's the second largest
oil deposit found
in the last decade.
We had the contract for it,
but to get it out of the E.I.R.,
we needed the pipeline.
What were you told?
And by whom?
We were told
by Colonel Mariga
we could build the pipeline
if we paid
a pollution remediation fee.
But?
We'd already remediated
everything
that needed
to be remediated.
So what was the fee for?
It was a bribe.
And Ava Hessington
paid this fee
with the full knowledge
that it was a bribe?
Yes, she did.
On this screen here, Nick,
are you sliding
a briefcase full of cash
across the table
to Colonel Mariga?
Yes.
And you were aware
it was a bribe?
Yes, but--
How was Ms. Hessington
as a boss?
She taught me
a great deal.
- Did she trust you?
- I believe so.
- Rely on you?
- Yes.
Did she look
over your shoulder
on everything you did?
No.
Was she aware
of everything you did?
She was aware of this.
Yet all we have
is your word on that.
So let me get this straight.
She groomed you,
promoted you,
gave you autonomy,
then you engineered a bribe.
And when you got caught,
you cut a deal
to lay that bribe
on your mentor.
Is that correct?
She knew.
Yes.
You claimed that before.
If Ava Hessington
were convicted of this crime,
who would be considered
next in line?
That's speculative.
Is it at all possible
it would be you?
Yes.
Wow, sounds like
you have a lot to lose
and even more to gain.
We're not in court.
Your testimony
doesn't help you here.
No, but we wanted
to give you a taste
of what it would be like
in court
when Nick still won't be able
to look her in the eye
when he stabs her
in the back.
We won.
- We did?
- We did.
I just want
to say one thing.
You know,
if Harvey had the power
to become Mariano Rivera,
he would,
because Harvey
doesn't love the law.
It's just his vehicle
for forcing
his will on his opponents,
for winning.
But you see, Mike, that's not
how I feel about the law.
I love the law.
And I'd never trade it
for anything.
I love it too.
I also like winning.
I know.
You know what I think?
I think you're half Harvey
and you're half me.
You've had your time
with him.
Now have your time
with me.
You here for an interview?
They let you go already?
You made your point.
If we go to trial,
you eviscerate Nick.
But we still have that video,
she's on it,
and he says she knew.
And you know what?
The truth is I believe him.
And I'll make them
believe him.
Then why are you here?
Nice job, Harvey.
You got me.
They want you
to cut a deal.
Against my recommendation.
I guess they know
what you don't.
You can't beat me.
Here are our terms.
No, here are my terms.
Our original offer stands.
Hessington Oil
pleads no contest,
we pay a $50-million fine,
and all criminal charges
against Ava are dropped.
They were going
to go for that,
but I convinced them
to make one change,
nonnegotiable.
Ava Hessington
doesn't plead no contest.
She pleads guilty.
And you get
to call it a win.
Well, the record
is going to say guilty.
It is a win.
I can beat you,
and I did,
and it's going
to eat you up.
Dennis, one.
Specter, zero.
Take it or leave it.
- This deal is bullshit.
- Harvey.
Cameron can say
what he wants.
Darby asked you
to take this case.
No way he doesn't
consider this a win.
I don't consider it
a win.
Do you really want to gamble
five years of her life,
so you can prove
you're better than Cameron?
You know as well as I do,
he's only offering this
'cause he knows
he's got a loser.
It's the exact same deal
we offered
with one technical change.
Do you know how they enter
a technical knockout
in the record books?
As a knockout.
I would.
What?
You asked me before
if I'd do it again.
I would.
You put me
in that position again,
and I'll do
whatever I have to do to win.
Because we win.
Are you saying screw
this deal, let's kick his ass?
No.
I'm saying take the deal.
We already did.
Sorry.
Me too.
You were just trying
to help me.
Yeah, but I shouldn't
have said something
I knew would hurt you
just to end an argument.
I don't want
to keep secrets from you.
You don't have to.
So Louis asked me.
And what did you say?
I told him I needed
some time to think about it,
and then
I came straight here.
So you're really
just apologizing
because you need
my advice.
Well, I also want sex.
You can have one
or the other.
I really don't need
any advice.
It's a good deal, Ava.
Don't second-guess yourself.
I'm not in the habit
of second-guessing myself.
No, I just realized
when I get back to London,
my right hand
is going to be gone.
Your right hand
sold you out.
You made it
seem like he did it
for his own personal gain,
but he did it
for his own survival.
He still did it.
But that doesn't mean
I'm not going to miss him.
Good-bye, Harvey.
Goodbye, Ava.
Do you want me
to send a copy to Darby?
I do.
I thought maybe
working with Jessica
would change your mind
about taking over the firm.
- It didn't.
- Why not?
Because if she had it
to do all over again,
she would.
Harvey,
if this whole thing
is really Jessica's fault,
maybe it's time
we considered forgiving Mike.
If she's not vacuuming
properly, then just fire her.
It doesn't matter.
You'll get someone--
Mom, I gotta go.
Bye.
You make me want
to be a better man.
- You watched it?
- Loved it.
Well, you had me
at hello.
You watched
Jerry Maguire?
Jerry, did you know
the human head weighs 8 pounds?
These are the A.B.C.s
of me, baby!
Show me the money!
Ahh.
You know, normally, I wouldn't
want to jinx anything,
but I got us something.
Okay.
It’s the perfect way to consummate
our relationship.
So just wait right here.
It's in the kitchen.
Sure.
I can't let you do this.
Let me?
Don't do this.
I already said yes.
I can't go back
on my word.
You're not going back
on your word.
You're going back
where you belong.
I am.
I am sorry.
I know.
Look, why don't you
take tonight off
and go out
with your girlfriend?
Thanks, Harvey.
No, we're going up top.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
But if you come in
late tomorrow, you're fired.
We'll see.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net