I get Ava Hessington acquitted,
Darby backs me
for managing partner.
I don't want it anymore.
Get out of my sight.
You called Mariga
to offer him a bribe.
Doesn't matter--
Dennis never
had him in the first place.
But he does now.
You're saying
he traced my call.
You're suing me for ownership
of the Mikado?
He said he might as well
have left his cat
with Michael Vick.
I'm offering you
a settlement.
You get back the associates,
I get back my cat.
Clifford Danner is 18.
I put him in jail 12 years ago.
He's innocent.
Cameron buried the evidence.
Emmanuel Mariga,
20 years ago
at the University of Cape Town
on the rugby team.
You know who else played rugby?
Stephen Huntley.
Stephen was the one
who ordered those killings.
I'm so sorry, Harvey.
Aah!
Tell me he looks worse.
He does.
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
I hope you didn't do that
because of me.
It was a fight, Donna,
not a duel.
- How could I not have--
- Listen to me.
Stephen betrayed us all.
You don't understand,
Harvey.
I was with him.
And he was capable
of something like that,
and I didn't even see it.
You know, I'm supposed to--
Donna!
It's okay.
Just tell me
you're gonna make him pay.
He'll pay.
Let's not talk about it.
Talk about what?
What do you need me to do?
I need you to keep going
with everything you have
to impeach
Mariga's testimony.
What about the stuff
on Stephen?
- Not yet.
- Why not?
Because we don't have proof.
The trial's in two days.
We should bring Ava in
and tell her--
- Not yet.
- Why not?
Because we don't have proof.
Harvey, we have
to do something.
And how would
that conversation go?
"Hi, Ava, turns out
one of the lawyers from our firm
"is trying to frame you
for a crime he committed.
But right now we're not sure
we can do anything about it."
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna go home,
get a good night's sleep,
and then tomorrow
I'm gonna find out
what the whole story is.
Harvey, Stephen
isn't gonna tell you
what the whole story is.
No, but there's
someone else who can.
You knew this case
was heading your way
before you ever
came after us.
That's why
you wanted to merge.
Yes, it is.
And I regret the situation
as much as you do.
But what's done is done.
Is that what you told Stephen
when you found out he did it?
Found out?
How do we know
he didn't order it?
Because I am giving you
my word.
Why should we trust a man
who sent Stephen over here
to cover his ass?
I sent Stephen over here
because I care about Ava,
which is why I sent him to
the E.I.R. in the first place.
I had no idea
he would do what he did,
and I have been trying
to fix it ever since.
- Then fix it right now.
- And how exactly can I do that?
By stating in court
Stephen acted alone
without Ava's knowledge.
- I can't.
- Why not?
Because he never told me.
And you never asked because
you never wanted to know.
You piece of shit.
You care about Ava
so much.
How could you
do this to her?
I wasn't doing anything
to her.
I was trying to do
something for her.
Remind me never to ask you
for any favors.
Well, I'm not asking
for a favor.
But you are going to agree
to do something right now.
And what is that?
It's not gonna work.
I cut you off
to get your attention.
Well, you have it.
Good, 'cause I just have
one question for you.
How can you live
with yourself?
- What?
- You know what?
I don't have any questions
for you.
I just came in here to let
you know that you make me sick.
Obviously
I hurt you, Donna,
and I never meant
to do that.
Oh, you didn't hurt me.
You just made me somebody
who slept with a murderer.
Murderer?
I don't know
what you think you know,
but those people that
were killed were terrorists.
They were people...
Who lived on top
of something that you wanted.
People who had guns--
murderers, Donna.
Now, if you're so appalled
by how business is done,
may I suggest
that you return
all of your designer clothes
that you look so ravishing in,
because they're paid for
by the dirty work
this firm does.
We don't kill people.
You mean chemical companies
that Harvey represents
or car companies
that Harvey defends?
How about insurance providers
whose claims he helps deny?
- Don't bring him into this.
- He's always been in this.
You know what?
I've had enough of this.
I didn't really cut off your
shit to get your attention.
I cut it off because
you don't need it anymore.
You're fired.
Darby would never allow that.
Edward Darby signed
your pink slip an hour ago.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ Suits 3x08 ♪
End Game
Original Air Date on September 3, 2013
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The Greenback Boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
2 months, 5 days, and 3 hours
under Nigel's tutelage,
and this is what
you have to show for it?
That's over 20 motions.
20 dog shits.
Did you get this
out of a Grisham novel?
Because that's fiction.
And you...
My mother can get
this motion thrown out.
And you--well, you're gone
anyway in two days.
Listen up, people.
I've reviewed your work
in my absence.
And guess what.
It's pathetic.
Every stinking one of you
should get down on your knees
and thank God and me
for letting you continue
to exist in our kingdoms.
Louis, what was that about?
What's going on?
It was about me letting
these assholes know
who's in charge.
They know you're in charge.
They put you in charge.
They didn't put me in shit.
They sat there in judgment while
my character got ripped apart,
and not one of them
lifted a single finger to help.
They ruled in your favor.
They chose you over Nigel.
No, they made me
give up Mikado for them.
Okay, you're displacing your
anger over Mikado onto them.
They didn't put you
in this position.
It's not fair.
You're right.
They didn't put me
in this position,
but I know who did.
Goddamn Darby--
unleashes his dog, leaves us
to clean up the mess.
We can still go after Mariga
in court.
I mean,
he's an admitted murderer
who cut a deal
to save his life.
Wait a second.
That deal is only good
if he's telling the truth.
We can't go after him
with the truth on the stand.
Maybe, but we can go after him
with the truth not on the stand.
Cameron would have
to be willing to listen.
Then I better
get him to listen.
And I better
go after Mariga.
- And change your clothes.
- What? Why?
If they see a lawyer
within 20 yards of that lobby,
they'll lock the place down.
- Oh, you're not room service.
- No, I'm not, but...
I do need to talk
to Colonel Mariga.
And I need to stop paying
alimony to my cheating ex-wife,
but that's not going
to happen.
If you let me in,
maybe I can make that happen.
And how the hell are you
gonna make that happen?
I'm a lawyer.
You don't look like
a lawyer to me.
Okay. All right.
You got me.
Look, I'm not--
I'm not a lawyer.
In fact, between you and me,
I'm a complete fraud.
But what I am
is Colonel Mariga's cousin.
On his mother's side.
- All right.
- Okay, all right!
All right,
you don't believe me?
That's fine.
Just do me a favor, okay?
Give him this photo
of him and my Uncle Stephen.
Then let him decide
if he wants to talk to me.
Louis, how did you
get in here?
I told them
I was your uncle.
Though how they could believe
that we share
the same DNA is beyond me.
This is about your trial,
isn't it?
You're goddamn right
it is!
Why the hell
would you do that to me?
I had no choice.
I was subpoenaed.
It was a mock trial.
You could have refused.
What do you want
from me, Louis?
I want to yell at you!
Well, you can't do that
anymore--you fired me.
Is that what this
whole thing was all about?
You're damn right it was.
And you want to know the truth?
When I found out
about your stupid trial,
I called Nigel
and volunteered.
How dare you?
Me firing you was business.
You bringing up the death
of my cat--
that was personal.
You made me take care
of that stupid cat.
I'm allergic.
It could have killed me.
And when that cat did die,
not only did you never tell me
that it wasn't my fault,
you then fired me
in front of my very best friend.
If that's not personal,
then I don't know what is.
Now get the hell
out of my office.
I will.
But before I do,
I have some personal news
for you
about how your firing
really went down.
Ah, I love this.
We'd just won the championship.
Might I get a copy?
Yeah, I'll get one
framed for you.
You can look at it
in the ten minutes
before they
put you to death.
The photograph
proves nothing.
Trust me, there's a whole
lot more where that came from.
We know all about the ties
between you and Stephen.
Then bring them up.
But I made a deal
to testify against Ava,
and that is what
I'm going to do.
No, you made a deal
to put away
the person responsible
for ordering these killings,
and I suggest you do that
while you still can.
Young man...
If your intention is to shake
my testimony,
that is not
going to happen.
It doesn't need
to happen,
'cause once we prove
that you're lying about Ava,
Cameron Dennis is going
to cancel your deal,
and you're gonna come to me
begging for help.
Do you think
you're the scariest man
I've ever sat across from?
I know
you're not scared of me.
But you are scared
of your own people,
and you should be,
because you and I
both know
they're gonna kill you
the minute you get back.
That I know Stephen doesn't
mean I'm lying about Ava.
But you are.
Ah, and you can see
into my soul.
It doesn't take a fortune
teller to know you're lying.
And it doesn't take one
to know that if you had proof,
you wouldn't be here
talking to me.
So you're not protecting
Stephen out of principle.
I'm not a man
of principle.
I'm a man of expediency.
I get it.
If you change your tune now,
you'll lose the deal you have.
Therefore, I prefer to--
how do you say it--
dance with the one
who brought me.
Harvey, what are you
doing here?
Game time's tomorrow.
We got nothing to say.
I'm here to help you.
I don't need your help.
And you wouldn't be here
unless you need mine.
You're wrong.
I can help you do what you
always said you're all about--
putting bad guys away.
You got a confession for me?
You're going
after the wrong person.
You're her lawyer.
That's what you would say.
I'm not here as her lawyer.
This isn't a speech
for a jury.
I'm here man-to-man to talk
to the guy I used to know.
All right.
Talk.
- I know who really did this.
- Then tell me who it is.
I need a guarantee
you won't use
what I tell you
against Ava.
If you think
I'm gonna guarantee you
anything but a war tomorrow,
you are sadly mistaken.
I can't tell you who did it,
but somebody else can.
Who?
Colonel Mariga.
Are you kidding me?
I've got the murder weapon.
He says Ava Hessington
pulled his trigger,
and you want me to have him
change his story?
He's only pointing at Ava
because that's what
you want to hear.
Change his deal,
he'll tell you the truth.
He changes his story now,
anything he says
about anybody means shit.
It means shit in court,
but if you are
who you say you are,
it should mean something to you.
You know what, Harvey?
I believe that you believe
she's innocent,
and if you can convince me
of that,
I won't go after her,
but I'm not gonna guarantee
I won't use what you say
before I hear it.
- You want me to just trust you?
- That's what you're asking me.
But if you think that I'm gonna
kneecap my star witness
the day before the trial,
you are out of your mind.
Harold.
What's up, man?
it's good to see you.
I thought
you were my friend.
I am.
What the hell?
Friends don't say they tried
to save your job
when, really,
they hung you out to dry.
So it's true.
Look, Harold,
I didn't mean to--
You know what? Save whatever
bullshit explanation you have,
because I don't want
to hear it.
I'm not trying to give you
a bullshit explanation.
Because there is none.
You got to choose
between you and me,
and you chose yourself.
And then you lied to me
about it.
Yes, Harold, I did.
And then after I lied to you,
I got you a job
at a huge, powerful firm.
Yeah, you got me that job
so I'd owe you one
when the time came.
I got you that job
because I thought you deserved
a second chance.
And then you came calling
when you needed a lawsuit filed
to get rid of your witnesses
in your murder trial.
I trusted you
with that lawsuit
because I thought
you were a competent attorney.
And you were more than happy
to take it.
And that murder trial you just
mentioned is about to start.
So you can choose to be
pissed off with me or move on.
But right now
I have a job to do.
- Rachel.
- Louis, what did you do?
What do you mean?
What is this?
Fairfield Computers
is being sued.
- How's that my fault?
- Because they're your client,
and the attorney of record
is Harold Gunderson.
He also sent
a settlement offer.
He wants to pick
a fight with me.
He's gonna regret
the day he was born.
Aren't you the one
who picked a fight with him?
Rachel, whose side
are you on?
Don't answer that question.
You shouldn't be here.
Stephen said that we're
no different than he is.
I need to see you show him
that he's wrong.
This isn't his trial.
It's Ava's.
You're not gonna put him
on the stand?
You said you were gonna
make him pay.
Donna, I will,
but now is not the time.
Then when?
Because he killed people,
and if we let him
get away with it...
Then maybe we are
no different than he is.
Had these insurgents
had their way,
they would have blown up
the pipeline.
Instead, Ms. Hessington
retained a valuable asset,
and I, in turn, was compensated
for a job well done.
And this compensation came
directly from Ava Hessington?
Yes.
She specifically directed you
to kill people?
Yes.
One more thing,
Colonel Mariga--
do you and I have a deal
for you to testify
in exchange
for a more lenient sentence?
Yes.
And why should
the jury believe
that you aren't making this up
to save yourself?
Because if what I say to you
proves to be a lie,
you'll send me back home,
where I will be dead
within minutes.
No further questions.
Ten minutes recess.
Why didn't you just
jump right in there?
I get it--
you read a book that says
you don't let the jury
sit with things.
The only problem is...
We're not inside
of a book.
And I don't want
to seem defensive.
Harvey, we still have
a ton of shit to hit him with.
Were you in there?
They're buying what he's saying.
Then we make them
buy something else.
We got a pair of aces.
If the jury believes that
Cameron's got three of a kind,
we're not gonna win.
We can't go after Stephen.
Cameron
won't go after Ava
if I can convince him
it was Stephen.
- You went to Cameron?
- Yes.
And you're going
to trust him?
I'm not sure
we have another choice.
If you're thinking
what I think you're thinking,
don't.
I'm thinking I'd like
to rip your face off.
You get Mariga
to point the finger at me,
I will point it
straight at Ava.
Stephen, Jessica
doesn't respond well to threats.
Well, I don't make threats.
I give warnings.
You've been warned.
Mr. Specter...
I have no questions
for Colonel Mariga, Your Honor,
but I'd like to call
a rebuttal witness.
Harvey, come on,
you know what he's gonna say.
I don't care
what he's gonna say.
He's talking to the jury.
I'm talking to Cameron Dennis.
The defense calls
Stephen Huntley to the stand.
What has Stephen Huntley
got to do with this?
Harvey knows
what he's doing.
This is what
you wanted to sell me--
a lawyer from your own
goddamn firm?
You want to put away
the bad guy?
I'm about to hand him to you
on a silver platter.
Mr. Huntley,
did you work at the law firm
headed by Edward Darby
last year?
Yes.
Did Mr. Darby ask you
to solve any problems
for Hessington Oil
regarding their pipeline
in the E.I.R.?
I decline to answer under
my fifth amendment rights.
The right
against self-incrimination.
How long have you known
Colonel Mariga?
I decline to answer.
Is it true that you
went to school with him
at the University
of Cape Town?
I decline to answer.
Well, let me refresh
your memory.
You were teammates
on a championship rugby team.
Objection.
Counsel is testifying.
The witness is hostile,
Your Honor.
Hostile? They work
at the same law firm.
He was fired yesterday.
Gentlemen, approach.
He's making things up
to create reasonable doubt.
I'm bringing things up,
so you'll see the truth.
The only thing tying Ava to this
is Mariga's testimony.
You only have Mariga because
you tapped Stephen's phone.
That's a ridiculous
accusation.
Cameron, please.
Why did he call him?
How did he call him?
Enough.
You're on a short leash,
Mr. Specter.
The gentleman
invoked his rights.
Mr. Huntley, did you meet
with your old friend
Emmanuel Mariga
and direct him
to kill the opponent
of Hessington Oil's pipeline
without Ava Hessington's
knowledge?
I decline to answer.
I have
no further questions.
Mr. Dennis,
do you have any questions?
Mr. Dennis.
Mr. Huntley,
until you were let go,
you worked at the same firm
as Mr. Specter, correct?
Yes.
And his job today
is to give this jury
cause to doubt that
his client is the murderer?
- Yes.
- In your experience...
Is pointing the finger
at someone else
a good strategy?
It can be
an excellent strategy.
And why do you think
that Mr. Specter
is pointing the finger
at you?
Well, maybe it has something
to do with the fact
that a few weeks ago
Ms. Hessington approached me
and asked me
to bribe witnesses
who were about
to testify against her,
and I refused.
And if you think
I'm lying under oath,
then, please,
ask Mr. Specter.
He knows that's the truth.
And a woman who bribes
witnesses against her
is not innocent.
Objection.
Withdrawn.
One last thing.
Did the defendant
ask you to arrange a meeting
with Colonel Mariga
where she she would pay him
millions of dollars
in exchange for...
Killing opponents
of her pipeline?
I decline to answer.
Can't blame a guy
for trying.
No further questions.
Is Stephen Huntley involved
in this,
or is it some kind of stunt like
he just told the jury it was?
He ordered the killings.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- We didn't have proof.
Why would you put
that man on the stand?
It was a calculated risk.
You took a calculated risk
with my life
without telling me.
I'm sorry.
You screwed me.
I said
I wouldn't go after her
if you convinced me--
you didn't convince me.
Then take a recess
instead of twisting
everything he said.
I'm not gonna let the jury
sit with that shit.
And thank God I didn't.
Otherwise,
I would have found out
that she tried
to bribe witnesses
and you kept it from me.
It had nothing to do
with the murders.
That's funny--
when I kept things from you
that had nothing to do
with other murders,
you called me a criminal.
Well, that ended up
with you
putting an innocent person
in prison.
And now you're doing it again.
Oh, don't give me that shit.
Stephen Huntley is up
to his goddamn neck in this,
and you know it.
So he just goes around
killing his clients' enemies
behind their backs?
I don't think so.
You want corroboration?
Ask Mariga.
I just did.
And he answered me
in open court.
And I'm not putting
an innocent woman away.
I'm doing my job.
Cameron-
Lawyers killing people?
That's a hell of a firm
you got your name on, Harvey.
You must be proud to have left
the D.A.'s office for that.
Let's do racquetball,
James.
Again? Louis, you were
supposed to be waiting
in the conference--
I don't wait for anyone.
And you don't sue me.
Yes, I do.
Because I realized
I now work at a huge firm,
and I have the power
to do this to you.
Now, we can negotiate
a settlement,
unless, of course, you don't
think you can handle me.
Do you really want
to embarrass yourself
with your mother watching?
It kills you that they
don't ban us having pictures
of our mothers,
like you did, doesn't it?
A man is judged
by the photos he displays.
You have a photo
of yourself.
And now you're making
my point for me.
You don't intimidate me
anymore, Louis.
Really?
I know you, Harold.
I know that you gargle
before meetings
that make you nervous.
And I...smell...mint.
- I--
- We don't agree
to paragraph three or four.
I need to have four.
Or seven through ten.
My mo--my client
won't stand for that.
Your client will stand for
whatever the hell I give them!
Please, can I have nine?
You know what?
I'll give you nine...
Because it's meaningless,
and I want it
to tell all the other paragraphs
out there what happens
when Harold Gunderson
goes after Louis Litt.
That doesn't make any sense.
Haven't you ever seen
a mob movie?
They always let one survive
to tell the others.
Well, yeah,
but paragraphs can't talk--
Okay, whatever. Fine.
Just type this up as agreed,
and don't you ever let me see
your pasty, Norwegian,
Carrot Top-wannabe
face again.
Carrot Top is a very
underrated comedian
who's never done anything
to anyone.
Did you know that Harvey
was going to ambush Stephen
on the stand?
I wouldn't have stopped him
if I did.
And to hell
with the ramifications?
The ramifications for who,
Edward?
I didn't come here to fight
with you, Jessica.
But Stephen didn't take
the most direct hit.
Ava did.
You keep talking about
how much you care about Ava.
But I've only just met her.
And you're the one who did
what you did.
I treated you
as if you were my own blood.
Ava...
Did you do this to me?
Of course I didn't.
Did you keep this
from me?
I want to hear you say it.
I didn't know
until it was too late.
I didn't want to burden you
with what had been done
to get your pipeline,
and there was nothing
I could do to undo it.
Burden me?
What about protecting me?
Well, that's exactly
what I was doing
when I assigned Harvey
to the case.
And after I was brought up
on murder charges,
rather than tell me,
you send the very man
who committed the crime.
Who were you trying
not to burden then?
You once asked me if she knew
about her father and I.
In those days,
to be a lawyer and to be out--
not possible.
Her father
was in the oil business.
He would have been finished.
What does that have to do-
We used to go away
on occasion.
In order to do that,
Ava joined us and pretended
to be my girlfriend.
She did that for us.
Ava is family to me.
I sent Stephen out there
to help her.
I didn't know what he'd do.
And I would give anything
to undo it.
What do you want
from me, Edward?
I want you to put aside
your anger
and figure out a way to help.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to put aside
my anger.
We're in the middle
of a murder trial.
We can spare
five minutes for this.
Wait a second.
I gave you that bottle
when you took over from Daniel.
- I know.
- I told you to only open it
in case of an emergency.
You think this isn't
an emergency?
We're about
to lose a huge murder case,
and it turns out
the person behind it
is one of our own lawyers.
And we're in business
with the man
who helped cover it up.
But the thing
that's been most on my mind
is that you goddamn
betrayed me.
Now...
The truth is, you warned me
about all of this.
And I am tired
of feeling betrayed by you.
I'd rather forgive you.
Can you?
Why do you think I'm here?
I never should have come
after you.
I'm sorry.
You didn't kill anybody.
And if I'm really
going to forgive you,
then I need
to tell you I'm sorry
that I made you want to do it
in the first place.
What changed your mind?
Edward.
He said Ava
was family to him.
You're family to me,
and you did what he didn't.
You came clean.
Is that all you came here
to tell me?
Like you said, we're in
the middle of a murder trial.
And you have an idea.
We're not the only people
that are like family
to each other.
And sometimes
you have to put your family
in a position
where they don't have a choice.
What do you need me to do?
New plan-we're gonna
convince Cameron
that Ava's innocent.
Have you been drinking?
Yeah. Why?
Because wasn't that
the old plan?
That was the old goal.
This time, it's you
who's going to Cameron.
If he won't hear
the truth from you,
how's he gonna hear it
from me?
Cameron can't see the truth
because all he sees
is that he has
a winnable case.
How does that affect
what I just said?
Prosecutors are hammers,
and they see the accused
as nails.
How am I gonna change that?
You're gonna gonna remind him
about the time
he hit the wrong nail.
Can you tell me
how the waffles are here?
Mike Ross, my man.
It's good to see you, man.
It's good to see you too,
Clifford.
What the hell you doing out
in the middle of the night?
Oh, you know, I told you.
I got an urge
for some waffles.
This isn't a coincidence,
is it?
I need a favor.
No doubt.
What you need?
I need you to talk
to Cameron Dennis.
No.
Hell, no.
- Clifford...
- Look at me, man.
Look where I am...
Cleaning up people's shit!
I know.
You know this is all I can get
because of him?
My life passed me by
because of that motherf--
I get in a room with him,
I'll kill him.
And I need you to tell him
all of that
so that he doesn't do
the same thing to somebody else.
You need?
I know who "you" is.
And I don't owe Harvey shit.
Now, he may have
got me out,
but he and Cameron put me there
in the first place.
Yeah, you're right.
You don't owe Harvey.
But you do owe me...
'Cause I didn't have anything
to do with putting you in there,
but I broke the law
to get you out.
I am feeling generous,
so absolutely, 100%,
without a doubt,
go screw yourself.
Everything okay?
Yeah, of course.
I was just using
tactic number 36
in Louis Litt's handbook,
due to be published never
because I don't share
my tactics.
Tactic number seven,
by the way.
Okay.
Well, whatever tactic you used
on Harold didn't work.
He's not caving.
I don't know
what you're talking about,
because he gave me
everything I wanted.
The client just called.
The contract Harold sent over
has a loophole in it.
It leaves him open
to punitive damages.
Paragraph nine.
Get that contract back.
We need to renegotiate.
Oh, my God, Harold
pulled one over on you.
Don't you dare
say that out loud.
Call him up,
set up the appointment
for me to go over there.
I tried.
He insisted on coming here.
He's on his way right now.
He?
What the hell
are you doing here?
He's here
to tell you who you are.
I know who I am.
I don't need
to hear it from him.
You think I'm giving you
a choice?
Okay. We were supposed to meet
in the conference room.
I don't need to wait
in the conference room
to knock your dick
in the dirt.
What'd you just say to me?
It's from The Breakfast Club,
asshole.
Not all of us only watch
The Sound Of Music.
You little bastard.
You just crossed a line.
Julie Andrews
is a national treasure.
Maybe your client
would be better off with her.
Maybe they would be.
But she isn't here.
And I am.
And here are a few
of my favorite things--
countersuit for slander,
motion to decertify class,
motion for summary judgment,
change of venue, sanctions,
depositions, discovery!
Great use
of folders there, Louis.
Too bad none of them
are gonna work.
Well, they may not work
on the case,
but they're definitely
gonna work on you.
What are you talking about?
Oh, I'm talking
about you may win in the end,
but it won't justify you
spending every waking minute
of your life
on this bullshit,
instead of doing everything else
you've been assigned to do.
- You'd do that to me?
- I won't be doing it to you.
I'll be doing it
for Bratton Gould.
And you'll be laughed
out of there
the same way you were laughed
out of here.
- Louis--
- We got nothing left to say!
Drop the suit
by the end of the week,
or one of my associates
will see you in court.
Get out!
I don't want him here.
Ava, whatever he did,
he's here to help,
and he's an asset.
Then what does the mighty
Edward Darby have to say?
You're innocent
until proven guilty
beyond a reasonable doubt.
Take the stand.
Any juror that hears you
will have that doubt.
She opens that door,
the first question
Cameron asks is, did she try
and bribe those witnesses?
The answer is yes.
There goes reasonable doubt.
How much did you pay him?
- Cameron.
- Pay who?
Don't play dumb.
Clifford Danner.
Who the hell
is Clifford Danner?
He was an innocent person
that Cameron put behind bars.
And I thought
he would make you see reason.
That has nothing
to do with this.
And I didn't put him
behind bars--you did.
Then I got him out.
Well, you're not getting
her out, because she did it,
and yesterday your own colleague
said that she did it.
He did not say that,
and you know it.
- You willing to take that risk?
- What are you suggesting?
I've worked with him
long enough
to know what he's suggesting.
Cameron Dennis
doesn't go to verdict.
He cuts deals.
Then let me tell you...
About what's
behind door number one--
Eight years.
Eight years instead of forever.
Leave us alone.
Court's in ten minutes.
You have until then.
Harvey...
He's got us,
and you know it.
No, he doesn't.
She's not going to prison
for one day.
She's going
for the rest of her life
if we don't take this deal.
I am not losing to him.
You-your blood feud
or whatever it is
you have with that man
is what put the target
on my back in the first place.
Ava, we need
to face reality.
She is not taking that deal.
She better, because
she can't buy her way out of it.
And you can't cover up
your way out of it.
- I don't care.
- Well, what's your idea?
Because unless
you're gonna testify
that Stephen did this
without Ava's knowledge,
you can't help.
And as you said,
you have no proof.
So why don't you get out of the
room and let the grown-ups talk?
What if I was
to testify to that?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about putting
words to a conversation
that should have happened
but didn't.
You'd say that you confronted
Stephen, and he admitted it?
I made this mess.
It's up to me to clear it up.
This isn't gonna help.
You're her old friend coming
to her aid at the last second.
It's a lie.
The jury will see
right through it.
Then we need to make Cameron
believe it.
Harvey, Cameron wants a win.
You need to convince him
this is a win.
Can you do that?
I guess it's the best shot
we have.
I knew you would cave.
With five minutes to spare.
We're not here
to take your offer, Cameron.
We want you to take ours.
Nah, I'm not negotiating.
Eight years is final.
This isn't about making
a deal for Ava.
It's about making
a deal for me.
If he's got something
to say about this,
you should put him
on the stand.
I already trusted you once.
I need your word.
Go ahead.
Off the record.
I instructed Stephen Huntley
to do whatever it took
to get Ava her pipeline,
and I told him
to do it behind her back.
So you authorized
these murders.
Absolutely not.
When I heard people
had been killed,
I confronted him immediately.
And what did he say?
He didn't care
that he'd resorted to murder.
His job
was to get things done.
You just admitted to being
an accessory after the fact.
No, he didn't.
I get it.
Off the record.
What do you want?
Edward pleads
to obstruction of justice--
five years probation.
You drop the charges
against Ava.
And he testifies
at Stephen Huntley's
murder trial.
And why would I swap out Ava
for her minion?
Cameron, you gave us
that offer for a reason.
You're at the finish line--
you can taste the win,
but it's not 100%,
and you know it,
because you're still banking
on an admitted murderer
with an incentive to lie.
I'm giving you
a respected lawyer
with an incentive to keep
his mouth shut.
You know who has
a better chance
at getting you a win.
Draw up the paperwork.
I thought you never wanted
to see me again.
I thought
about what you said.
What, about the kind
of business your firm does?
Yes.
And I realized that maybe
you're not as bad
as I said you were.
- No?
- No.
You're much worse.
Harvey and Cameron
made a deal to take you down,
and part of that deal
was that I got to be the one
to tell you about it.
I meant it when I said
I never meant to hurt you.
And I meant it when I said
that you make me sick.
It's all there.
You testify, you get
five years probation.
And he pleads
obstruction of justice.
- What is this?
- What is what?
This says that I forfeit
my license
to practice law
in this country.
Oh, that--that's just
something I added in.
- This is unacceptable.
- Wait a minute.
How could you add that in
if we did the paperwork?
And if he can't practice law
in the country,
he can't be a member
of our firm.
We must have agreed to it
in advance.
You set
this whole thing up.
Jessica set
But what's it matter?
You really gonna put this
on Ava
when you can get off
with a slap on the wrist?
I asked you to put aside
your anger.
I did.
You said Ava was family.
The thing about family
is they make it easy
to put you in the position
where you don't have a choice.
Now, you gonna
sign the deal,
or do I just pick up the trial
right where we left off?
You're doing
the right thing, Edward.
We'll worry about the terms
of our dissolution tomorrow.
And, Edward...
We may be getting a divorce,
but I fully intend on keeping
ownership of the house.
Who'd have thought
we'd end up here?
I did.
No, you didn't.
You took a chance
with Clifford Danner,
and you know it.
It wasn't a chance.
I played the man.
And, Cameron, you're not
only about winning.
You're about putting
guilty people away.
Nice working with you.
Onetime deal.
I guess this means
you're not looking
for another name partner?
Goodbye, Cameron.
Norma said you
had something for me?
I do.
He dropped it.
I win.
Do you?
What?
What are you talking about?
Why do you hate Harold
so much?
- I don't hate him.
- Yeah, you do...
Because I've never seen you
be as mean to anyone
as you are to him.
Rachel, I-
- don't "Rachel" me.
He's a human being.
What's the matter with you?
When I was a kid
in gym class...
We had to climb the rope.
Every day I tried
really hard,
and every day...
Everyone would laugh at me.
The one thing in my life
that I've always been great at
is training
the associates...
Except for Harold.
He's my failure.
And every time
I look at him, it...
puts me right back
in gym class.
Louis...
Harold's climbing
that rope.
He's succeeding.
And the way
you got this victory
was by going
after his career.
And you're just yanking him
right back down.
We never got this.
Send back his original offer
marked "accepted."
I never want this
spoken of again.
You never want what
spoken of again?
Harvey,
what did Ava have to say?
She'd already left
for the airport.
Someone saves my life,
I might stop to say thank you.
You really blame her
after what this firm
put her through?
When you put it
that way...
It doesn't matter.
It was a huge win.
Go celebrate.
Whoa.
Hey, hey.
Don't you mean
"let's go celebrate"?
Am I really the person
you want to celebrate
this big murder-trial
victory with?
I don't know. It depends.
Do you put out?
- Why don't you ask Rachel?
- That's not funny.
Harvey.
Donna.
How'd it go?
As well as it could.
Harvey...
Thank you.
Why don't you keep the car?
I feel like walking tonight.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net