Previously on "Suits"...
You think that I don't know
that all your problems
are solved if I tell them
that Harvey did this?
I would be lying if I said
it didn't cross my mind
that maybe Mike should think
about making a deal.
And now that they've taken in
your father, you can't tell me
that the thought
hasn't crossed yours too.
Thinking about it and talking
about it aren't the same thing.
I got a call about an article
on Mike Ross' meteoric rise
to Junior Partner.
The problem is
there is no Mike Ross.
You reported it
anonymously,
because you didn't want
to look bad.
I reported it anonymously
because I was ashamed
that it happened on my watch.
I loved you, and you let
some stupid secret
come between us because
you couldn't trust me with it.
All you have to do
is admit what you did,
and all of this goes away.
Sheila came forward.
She admitted she was the one
who wrote the e-mail.
You and your partners
are hereby subpoenaed
to hand over every single
document in the entire firm.
Harvey, I'm not sure
this is the best idea.
We need to know what she has.
What's the downside?
The downside is
that we move up the trial.
Mike, this trial's coming,
whether we like it or not.
And the more time we have
knowing her game plan,
the better off we'll be.
Holy shit.
What?
I took the LSATs
with this guy.
So what?
So he can give Gibbs something
she doesn't even have on me yet.
Yes, but to do that, he'd
be ruining his whole career.
Which means, even
if he remembers you,
he's more afraid of you
than you are of him.
So calm the hell down.
All right, let's make
this quick.
Your Honor,
making it quick is exactly
what we're asking you to do.
She hasn't handed over
her discovery yet.
I'm still building a case,
and we haven't even set
a date for the trial yet.
And the check's in the mail,
and all the other things
people say when they don't wanna
do what they have to do.
What I have to do
is protect the public
from the likes of you.
All right, that's enough.
Get that discovery to them
by the end of the day.
In that case, we'd like to ask
that the day of the trial
be set in the next two weeks.
Objection, Your Honor,
she's had weeks to--
You can't have it both ways,
Mr. Specter.
You can't demand discovery
and ask for more time.
Trial starts in two weeks.
Jessica, we have
a problem.
Thanks for pointing
that out, Jack.
I had no idea.
I'm not talking
about the trial.
I'm talking about this.
What the hell is that?
An Op-Ed in the Journal.
"There is no way
on God's green Earth
"that at least one
of the three name partners
"at Pearson Specter Litt
didn't know what was going on
under their own roof."
"God's green Earth."
Who wrote it?
A partner at Skaaden.
If it wasn't them,
it would've been someone else,
because they smell blood.
I don't care what they smell.
I've given up everything
for this firm,
and if anybody tries
to take it from me,
they'll have to pry it
from my cold, dead hands.
- And what's your goddamn plan?
- Excuse me?
Jessica, our reputation's
taking a beating.
We need to rehabilitate it.
That means pro Bono,
and you know it.
One free case is not going
to move the needle,
no matter how worthy it is.
I'm not talking
about one case.
I'm talking about
a series of cases
for our clients'
most valued charities.
Oh, this better not be
another scheme, Jack.
You think this is a move?
Now why would I ever
think that after you tried
to take my firm from me six
times in the last ten minutes?
I did try
to take over from you.
But I've been at this firm
my entire career,
and I am fighting for it now.
- And you think I'm not?
- I'm sure you are.
But you're also the reason
I'm holding this indictment
of our firm
in the first place,
because what they're
saying is true.
And don't you dare
try to tell me
you didn't know
about Mike Ross,
because we both know you did.
What the hell do you want?
Oh, since you made me come
all the way down here,
I thought I'd save the taxpayers
some money on hiring a server.
A server for what?
For your fiancée. I'd like
to ask her some questions.
Get the hell out of here.
You want to serve a subpoena,
you serve it to her.
Well, then I wouldn't get
to see the look on your face.
Did you really think I wouldn't
hit you where it hurts?
I was saving
your weakest spot for last.
Have a nice day, gentlemen.
- What?
- You know what.
It's time we give that woman
a taste of her own medicine.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
It means we hire a lawyer
from an outside firm,
and we dig up dirt on someone
she cares about.
- Are you out of your mind?
- You saw what she did to Donna.
It's only a matter of time
before she tries to pull
the same shit with Rachel.
Mike--
Harvey, you're the one
that taught me that when someone
puts pressure on you,
you put it back on them.
I also taught you if you're
gonna take a swing at someone,
you better knock them out,
and if we pull the shit
that you're talking about
and get caught,
all that happens is
I get thrown off this case,
and it's game over.
Harvey, I can't stand by
and watch while the people
I care about get attacked,
and neither could you.
Mike, I promise you,
I will be there for Rachel
every step of the way.
In the meantime,
I need you going through
every one of those boxes.
Because if that woman
is ready to go to trial,
she's got a lot more
than an e-mail
from Louis' girlfriend.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 5x13 ♪
God's Green Earth
Original Air Date on February 10, 2016
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
- Rachel Zane.
- Yes?
My name is Anita Gibbs.
I'm the--
Yes, I know who you are.
I'm flattered you came
for me personally.
But we aren't supposed to talk
for another three days,
and I don't have my lawyer
with me, so--
This isn't
a formal interrogation.
That won't be necessary.
Then I'll tell you
what is necessary.
You're going to put in writing
that anything I say to you
is inadmissible.
I suspected you'd
say that, which is why
I prepared this.
I understand if you'd prefer
to ask somebody who's actually
completed law school
if that's legally binding.
I'm perfectly capable
of determining
if this is legally
binding or not.
and I'm not going to let you
bait me into saying
anything to you.
Well, that's fine with me.
I'm not looking for you to talk.
I'm looking for you to listen.
Well, it's official.
No matter what
happens at trial,
this firm isn't surviving
Mike Ross.
I know about
the editorial, Louis.
What editorial?
I'm talking about the summer
associate applications.
- How bad is it?
- Three people.
Not just any three people,
the three people that never
should've made it to Harvard
in the first place.
Goddamn it.
Sheila's sending us
the bottom of the barrel.
She's giving us
the sludge that grows
at the bottom of the barrel.
Then...
I think it might be time to
start looking beyond Harvard.
Yeah, that's a great idea.
You know what?
We should start shitting
in the urinals
while we're at it.
I'm not talking about
the University
of Arizona, Louis.
I'm talking about Columbia,
Yale, Stanford--
And I'm talking
about appearances.
We break our rule and suddenly
hire outside of Harvard--
We already broke our rule
for Rachel with Columbia.
Please, that was different,
and you know it.
No. It was because of Mike,
which makes it the same
goddamn thing.
One way or another, we are
going to keep this firm going.
So if you don't wanna go
outside of Harvard to do that,
then I suggest you go up
to Cambridge,
and convince Sheila
to start feeding us
some worthy
goddamn applicants.
♪
Okay. So first
you pick me up,
then you bring me
to my favorite café.
What can I say?
I do my homework.
As do I, Ms. Gibbs,
which is why I'm not falling
for you pretending
to be my friend.
You're right.
I'm not your friend.
But I am willing
to pull some strings
to get the man you love
into Columbia Law School.
And if you think that I'm
gonna buy that fairy tale,
the only strings you're trying
to pull are mine.
The only fairy tale here
is the one where you believe
you get out
of this thing unscathed.
Okay.
We're done here.
Rachel, I'm just trying
to give you your options.
I know my options.
Then you know you have
no spousal privilege,
which means you're going to
have to tell the truth,
and put your fiancée away.
Or you're gonna have
to plead the Fifth.
Or I can say that
he didn't do this.
Perjuring yourself is
the same as taking the Fifth,
as far as your future
is concerned.
What the hell
does that mean?
I'm saying that someday
you're going to face
the character and fitness
committee of the Bar,
and I seriously doubt they're
going to admit somebody
who did that.
Are you trying to
intimidate a witness?
Because yes, someday
I will face that committee,
but tomorrow they're going
to be hearing about you.
I'm your only way
out of this mess.
Just give me the people who are
actually responsible for it,
and I'll see to it that both
you and Mike can practice law
for the rest of your lives.
Please tell me
that's the last one.
It is.
Except for the hundred
in the other conference room.
- Holy shit.
- Yeah.
Trial Strategy 101.
Bury the other side
in paperwork,
so they can't find
what they're looking for.
And what are we looking for?
Gibbs' trial strategy.
Somewhere in these boxes
are the pieces
that she is putting together
to make her case.
We find them,
we know specifically
what we have to fight.
And what specifically might
those things look like?
Witness lists, interviews,
anything to do with Lola Jensen,
utility bills from when I was
supposed to be at Harvard--
Wait, wait, wait.
Slow down.
- Why are you writing this down?
- So I can remember it.
And because we need a system.
And because you've never done
doc review before.
I don't believe it.
How you've been a legal
secretary this long,
and never have done doc review.
I will tell you how.
Because I'm the best damn person
you've ever seen
at reading people,
anticipating needs,
and generally
dominating everything.
So, in this situation,
you're going to be
absolutely no help at all.
- None whatsoever.
- I'm getting Rachel.
What's that?
What does it look like?
It looks like something
I don't have time for.
Well, make time.
Jessica, we've got a thousand
boxes of shit to go through,
and I've got trial in two weeks.
What?
That's right.
The date's been set.
So I'm sorry that I can't have
a doughnut with you right now,
but I've got something a little
more important to deal with.
Harvey, I understand, but
our clients are being circled.
Our reputation's getting
tanked,
and we're getting sent
shit associates.
And Mike Ross
is facing prison.
And you're handling
one thing,
while I'm handling
everything else.
- Jessica--
- No, never mind, Harvey.
It's clear that you
really don't care
about keeping
this firm together.
I resigned to keep
Well, it sure doesn't seem
to be working out that way,
does it?
Great, I'll have my secretary
set up a meeting for Monday.
If that meeting's about your
pro Bono bullshit,
cancel it.
What?
You said it yourself, Jack.
Other firms smell blood.
Well, you don't get a shark
to back off by playing nice,
you do it by clubbing him
in the face.
They come after our clients,
we go after theirs.
Clients aren't the ones
writing editorials
for "The Wall Street
Journal", Jack.
You want to poach
an attorney.
I wanna poach
a whole goddamn department.
That is definitely
another way to go.
It's the only way to go,
because if we didn't do what
we're saying we didn't do,
this is what we do.
I get it.
You're trying to convince
the world we're innocent.
Jack, I don't give a shit
if my enemies think
I'm innocent or not.
I give a shit whether they
think they can take me down,
which is why
I'm not going to cower
in some pro Bono corner,
trying to convince them
that I'm friendly.
I'm going to kick some ass,
and remind them
that I'm fierce.
There you are. I've been
looking everywhere for you.
Rachel, we need your help.
Where have you been?
With Anita Gibbs.
What? How did you
let that happen?
Because she ambushed me
on the street,
with a document that said
our conversation
would be inadmissible.
And if she did that
is because she didn't want
to talk to you, she wanted
to get in your head.
Mike, I know what
she wanted to do.
What did she say?
She said that she could
get you into Columbia,
and that you could be a lawyer
after all this is over.
Rachel, she's lying--
You think I don't know that?
Well, we've already
been over this.
The only way she is gonna help
us is if we help her
put Harvey and Jessica away.
Yes, Mike, I know that,
but we didn't go over the part
where I don't get into the Bar
because I took the Fifth.
Oh, goddamn it!
This is exactly why I wanted
Harvey to be there.
She got into your head.
She didn't got into my head.
She dangled our dream
in front of me,
and I know
that we can't have that.
It doesn't mean
I can't handle this.
It doesn't seem
like you're handling it.
- I am.
- You're crying.
No. I'm releasing my emotions
so that I can persevere
instead of denying them
and losing my mind.
Which I can't do today,
because I have a meeting
with the dean.
Now, I came in here
to be alone
so I can deal with my shit,
so if you don't mind,
I would like to be alone
so I can deal with my shit.
Hey, did you find something
in the discovery?
Yeah, sure as hell did.
I just discovered that Gibbs
picked up Rachel.
What?
She arrested her?
No, she pulled up to the curb
with some document.
I don't give a shit what she
pulled up with.
Rachel should know
not to go with her.
Yeah, and that would've been
an excellent thing
for her lawyer to tell her,
except her lawyer wasn't there.
- Excuse me?
- You promised me
that you would be with her
every step of the way.
I promised I'd represent her
at a deposition,
not babysit her
24 hours a day.
Maybe instead of getting mad
at Rachel, it is time for us
to figure out
how to go after Gibbs.
- This again.
- Yes, this again.
I told you she was gonna go
after Rachel, and now she has.
And I told you if you're
gonna go after someone,
you better knock them out.
Then you better figure out
a way to knock Gibbs out soon,
because if you don't, I will.
Louis.
What are you doing here?
What?
You thought you could lie to
my face and get away with it?
- I never lied to you.
- Really?
Because you swore
you wouldn't come forward
about that e-mail,
but you did.
And you you're pulling
this associate shit.
I didn't come forward.
They found me.
And I'm not pulling
any associate shit.
Then what do you call
this pathetic excuse
of a candidates list?
I call it inevitable.
Because our students can read.
- The editorial.
- Yes.
The editorial.
So you're not
sending us sludge.
Louis, I'm not
doing anything.
Your firm is being investigated
by the U.S. Attorney's office.
And no one is going to risk
their career on a place
that may not even exist
in a month.
They might,
if you convince them to.
- Louis, I can't do that.
- Sheila, please.
I came here once before,
hoping for a second chance
and you wouldn't
give it to me.
What does that
have to do with this?
Because if we'd gotten
back together then,
I wouldn't even be
at the firm now,
but I am.
And it's all I have.
I understand you not giving
me a second chance then.
But I'm begging you...
give my firm one now.
Louis, even if I wanted to,
it won't work.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
Because they're going to ask me
if I think it's a good idea
for them to work at Pearson
Specter Litt, and I don't.
- Sheila--
- Louis.
Please don't ask me
to lie to them.
What are you doing?
I'm just wondering
if you're gonna stay in here
going over stuff all day.
What else would I be doing?
Going to the ball game?
I don't know, Harvey,
I thought maybe you'd be doing
something to get Anita Gibbs
to back off Rachel.
Donna, she threatened
to go to the Bar.
It's a bullshit hypothetical
that she couldn't do
until after Rachel testified.
Which is after
the trial starts,
and that's what I'm
goddamn working on.
Harvey, all I'm saying is
that when Mike gets worked up
about something,
he doesn't tend to make
the best decisions.
Well, if he doesn't work
on the discovery,
he's gonna go to jail, so...
what do you want me to do?
I don't know, Harvey.
But you better at least
go talk to Anita Gibbs,
because Mike gave you
a warning loud and clear.
If you don't do something,
he will.
Jack, I don't often come
outside for my coffee,
but when I do is because
I'm feeling the need
for a little alone time.
Well, I came out here because
I knew you wouldn't want
anyone hearing
what I have to say.
Are you here to tell me
you can get the job done?
No, I'm here to tell you
if you want me to get it done,
you're going to have
to open your wallet.
I'm not paying you
more money,
just to get you to
poach a department.
I'm not talking about me.
I'm talking the real estate
division of Baker Hostetler.
- How much do they want?
- Double what they're making.
Are you insane? That's what
broke Dewey Ballantine.
You can't have two classes
of partners.
Then we can't poach
a department,
because they're the only ones
even willing to come here,
considering what's going on.
Then make the offer.
And let me have
my goddamn coffee in peace.
Ms. Scott,
there's a Harvey Specter
here to see you.
He says it's urgent.
Send him in.
I don't believe it.
You have some balls pretending
to be Harvey to get in here.
Well, you did call me
"Baby Harvey" once.
I don't give a shit
what I called you.
Get out! Now!
Scottie, Scottie, please.
Listen, I knew you would
never agree to see me,
and I need to talk to you.
About what?
I need someone
to bring an action
against Anita Gibbs' sister.
Are you insane?
Listen to me.
She's not just coming after me.
She's coming after my fiancée.
I don't care.
If I do that, I might as well
call the woman up,
and tell her that I'm in
on your whole bullshit too.
We get someone
from your firm--
Not to mention I told Harvey
that I never
even wanted to hear
your name again.
He didn't tell you
about that, did he?
Well, I guess
he hasn't changed,
because he didn't
tell me about you
until it was too late either.
So I am sorry
about your fiancée,
but I need you to go now.
Scottie, this woman
is not gonna stop
until she gets
what she wants.
And what she wants
is Harvey.
So I'm not asking you to do
this for me and Rachel.
I'm asking you
to do it for him.
Is that an invitation
to your bar mitzvah?
because I'm busy that day.
It's a motion
to have you sanctioned
for improperly
contacting a witness.
I didn't improperly
contact anyone.
Oh, bullshit.
You got Rachel Zane alone
so you could offer her
a deal to turn on me.
And there's nothing wrong
with that.
You listen to me.
You've been pulling shit
like this
from the second
this thing started.
You denied my client access
to his attorney,
you fabricated charges
against Donna,
and now you're tampering
with a witness.
And all witness tampering
would do is hurt my own case,
and why on God's green Earth
would I do that?
Why did you just say?
I said you're insane
if you think that--
No, you said,
"on God's green Earth,"
which is exactly
what that editorial said.
I remember because I thought,
"What person under 80
uses that phrase?"
Well, looks like I found her.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You sure as hell do, because
you planted that goddamn thing.
You have any proof?
No, you don't.
But even if I did plant that,
it would only have been
because there's no way
that one of you
did not know
what was going on.
And until one of you
admits that,
I'm going to take apart your
firm brick by brick.
So you want to file that thing?
You go ahead.
It's not going to stop me
for one second.
Rachel, please.
Have a seat.
Thank you, Dean.
I have to say I've
so been looking forward
to my first student review.
And ever since
your first interview here,
you've done nothing
but impress me.
Which is why I'm sorry
to have to bring this up now.
Bring what up?
The fact that your last LSAT
score was significantly higher
than your previous ones.
That is because I studied
incredibly hard the last time.
Did you study hard? Or did
your fiancée study hard for you?
You think Mike took
the LSAT for me?
I think he's been indicted
for more serious crimes
than that.
And now there are allegations
that he's taken the LSATs
for people.
I can't believe this.
I took that test myself.
And I have a responsibility
to protect the reputation
of this university.
And how exactly
are you proposing
to protect that reputation?
By expelling
any dangers to it.
Unless, of course,
for some reason
these allegations against him
are dropped.
Anita Gibbs called you,
didn't she?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I'm simply giving you
the courtesy
of letting you know
that if I have to choose
between your future
and this university's,
I'm not choosing you.
Well, then, please,
tell Ms. Gibbs
thank you for the courtesy.
Scottie, what are you
doing here?
I can't believe
you sent him to me.
- Sent who?
- Oh, don't give me that.
The last time
you came to me,
you said it was
because Mike made you.
Well, this time,
you made him.
-I didn't made him do anything.
Well, then, you taught him
well, because he came to me
and pulled on my heart strings
to get me to do
something for you,
but this time
the answer is no.
I am not going after
Anita Gibbs.
Scottie, I would never ask you
to do something like that.
That's funny, because you
asked me to throw a case
to keep Mike
from getting caught.
Throwing a case doesn't put
a target on your back.
If you really wanted to keep
a target off my back,
you never would've told me
about Mike in the first place.
Scottie, I didn't tell him
to do that.
Well, then, I guess you two
are having the same problem
we did: You don't talk
to each other.
Since you chose him over me
it's not my problem anymore.
I didn't chose him over you.
Yes, you did.
And whether you choose
to admit it or not,
it was Mike's secret
that broke us up
in the first place.
You let her in here
without telling me?
I was in the conference room,
going over discovery.
What are you going to do?
I don't know what I'm gonna
do, but whatever it is,
I'm gonna do it right now.
Harvey, calm down.
I'm not gonna calm down,
you told me to go after Gibbs
to stop Mike from doing
something stupid,
and I did, and all that did
was waste our time
like I said it would.
Harvey.
Gibbs is attacking Rachel,
the woman he loves.
You of all people should be
able to understand that.
I don't give a shit.
He had no right to go after
someone I love.
Okay, you know what, Harvey?
Mike is the one on trial here,
not Scottie.
And all he did was ask her
to do something.
So maybe the thing that you're
really upset about
is that she was right.
Well, how did it go?
We've known
each other a long time, Jack,
and I'd really like to help,
but it's not gonna happen.
You said if I could
get them double--
I said it would take at least
double just to get me to ask.
I did, and they laughed me
out of the room.
What if I could
get you more?
There's no number that's
going to get them to come
to Pearson Specter because they
don't believe there's gonna be
a firm to come to.
Then why did you ask
to meet me here?
Because after I asked them
about your offer,
I asked them about mine.
What are you talking about?
I told them a former
fraternity brother of mine,
who happens to be
a kick-ass lawyer
might be looking for a change.
You're offering me a job?
Jack, Pearson Specter's
a sinking ship.
We've taken on some water.
You've taken on an ocean.
Why the hell would
you wanna stay there?
I'll tell you why.
Because if that ship sinks,
I'll find myself another job.
But if it doesn't,
I have the chance to be one
of the captains.
If I come to you now, I'll
never be more than a lifer.
As my friend,
tell me I'm wrong.
You're not wrong.
♪
Don't tell me they printed out
a special evening edition
on us too.
Not yet.
I read it, by the way,
on the flight up to Boston.
And did it fire you up?
Pissed me the hell off.
You couldn't get it done
with Sheila, could you?
Jessica, she didn't send us
the candidates on that list.
They were the only three that
even asked to be submitted,
and it was because
of bullshit like that.
People are scared
to come here.
They are.
I tried to get Sheila to make
them unafraid, but I couldn't.
That's all right.
It's all right, Louis.
It's not your fault.
♪
Once word got out about Mike
this was bound to happen.
What I learned
from hiring Mike
was that not all great lawyers
went to Harvard.
What are you saying?
I contacted Stanford,
Yale, Columbia, Penn,
and all the rest...
Top 20 law schools.
I officially opened up the doors
to Pearson Specter Litt.
I know how much you hated
to do that, Louis,
but sometimes we need to do
what we have to...
to survive.
Is there anything else
I can do?
No, there isn't.
Right now, we just need to
get through this trial,
and pray to God
that Harvey gets
Mike goddamn Ross
off the hook.
Hey.
Hi.
You're doing dishes.
So?
So you hate doing dishes,
which means
something's wrong.
Nothing's wrong.
What's going on?
I don't even know
if I should say it,
because the last time I did
you got so mad.
You thought I was
gonna leave you.
And you say you want me
to share things with you,
but I don't know if you do,
because when I do
you seem to get so upset
that I--
I get it. You want to talk
about making a deal.
I don't know
what I wanna do.
I just--
She said that she could
get you into Columbia,
and you're right.
It got into my head.
Rachel, we've been
over this.
She was lying.
That was before I knew she
was able to get to the dean.
What are you talking about?
I had my meeting
with him today,
and I thought he was
going to tell me
how well I've been doing,
and instead...
he threatened to expel me.
Okay.
Okay, that--that doesn't mean
that it was Gibbs.
- You weren't there.
- No, I wasn't there, all right?
But it's not crazy to assume
that they would question
whether or not you knew about me
without talking to Gibbs.
Is it crazy for them
to mention a crime
you haven't even been accused of
without talking to Gibbs?
- What?
- They said there are rumors
of you taking the LSATs
for people
and they're accusing you
of doing that for me.
Well...at least now
I know what I need to do.
Harvey.
I know how we can stop Gibbs
from pressuring Rachel.
Does it involve going
to Scottie without telling me?
- Harvey.
- Goddamn it, you had no right.
I had every right,
because I knew Gibson
would keep crossing lines,
and that's exactly what she did.
What are you talking about?
She manipulated
the Dean of Columbia
into threatening
to expel Rachel.
Where's your proof?
They accused her of having me
take the LSATs for her,
and the only problem is,
there's no record of me
ever having
being accused of that.
- The guy you saw in court.
- Yes, his name is David Green.
He must've told Gibbs about me,
and then she used that
to get the dean
to strong-arm Rachel.
That's abuse of power.
I told you, the only problem
with that theory is,
David Green tells Gibbs
about you,
and his career is done.
Then he must've told her
anonymously.
Which doesn't help us,
'cause we still don't have
any proof that she
contacted the dean.
No, we don't, but it wouldn't
be that hard for me to get.
No, it could be a setup.
It's too risky.
This whole goddamn thing
is too risky,
but right now Rachel's future
is in jeopardy,
and if I have to risk tacking on
a few years to save her,
is not even a close call.
All right.
Do what you have to do.
Just don't get caught.
You're knocking.
That means it's either bad news
or you want something.
- I couldn't get the department.
- Don't tell me.
They said we're in no position
to poach anybody.
That's exactly
what they said,
right before they
offered me a job.
So you're here to tell me
you took it.
I'm here to ask you
if you want me to take it.
What the hell difference
does it make what I want?
Jessica, when I left Boston,
people said I was a traitor
and that I thought I was
too good for my own hometown.
Well, it wasn't true.
But I knew
the real test for me
wasn't making it
in my own hometown.
It was making it
in the toughest city
in the world, and as far
as I'm concerned,
I haven't done that yet.
You want to be made
name partner.
I wanna know if it'll ever
even be on the table.
I could say yes
to that right now,
but how would you know
you could trust me?
I have no other choice.
And how do I know
I can trust you?
What's this?
You know what it is.
It's what Daniel Hardman
has on you.
Now you have it too.
David Green.
What are you doing here?
So you do remember me.
Of course I do.
You're the guy
we're prosecuting.
The fake lawyer.
Oh, I'm more than that
and you know it.
What are you talking about?
You hired me
because I'm smart.
What you don't know is that
I have a photographic memory,
which means I have
your drivers license number
from seven years ago memorized.
Not that it matters, because
I also made a copy.
Like I made a copy of all
my clients' licenses.
That doesn't prove anything.
Maybe not, but I also remember
every answer I put down
on a 104 question test.
If that's not proof,
I don't know what is.
What do you want?
I want proof that Anita Gibbs'
pressuring the Dean of Columbia
to expel Rachel Zane.
- I can't do that.
- Yes, you can.
Okay, they went
to law school together.
There's your connection.
Circumstantial public record
not good enough.
I do what you're asking
and get caught,
and my career at the U.S.
Attorney's office is over.
I give what I have
to the D.A.,
and your career as a lawyer
is over.
If you do that, you only
implicate yourself.
Yeah, maybe
you didn't notice, asshole,
but I'm already on trial,
and now you're coming
after the woman I love.
And the truth is you don't
deserve to practice law.
Maybe I don't either,
but she does.
And, believe me,
when it comes to this,
I really don't give a shit
about me or you.
And what if I can't find
what you're looking for?
You know what, David?
You might not have been smart
enough to get 178 on the LSATs,
but I'm pretty damn sure
you're smart enough to do that.
What's this?
That's what
you're gonna sign.
This says you're dropping
a charge
of malicious prosecution
in exchange for me admitting
a sanctionable offense.
And for backing the hell off
going after Rachel Zane.
- Is this a joke?
- No.
And neither is getting
the Dean of Columbia Law
to do your dirty work.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You know exactly
what we're talking about.
And unless you want us
to tell the world
that you intimidated a witness
by colluding with your old
law school buddy,
you're going to sign that.
You don't have
a shred of proof
that I had anyone do anything.
I have a copy of an anonymous
tip sent to you,
saying I took the LSATs
for people,
and a record of a phone call
from your office
to the Dean of Columbia
ten minutes later.
That's no proof of anything.
It's proof enough for us
to sue Dean Herrick
for every penny
he's ever made.
You think when we get him
in a deposition
he isn't gonna crack?
You think you're pretty smart,
don't you?
Smart enough to outwit
a U .S. Attorney.
And if we can do it here,
what makes you think
we won't be able to do it
in court?
Because court is not about
bullshit like this.
It's about facts.
And the fact is, you're not
a goddamn lawyer.
You got it done.
- How'd you know?
- Because you're doing
that puffy chest thing you do
when you feel really good
about yourself.
I do not do
a puffy chest thing.
Yes, you do.
And relax,
because I love you
and your chest.
Well, I love you
- Hey!
- Oh, that came out wrong.
Seriously,
I meant your mind.
Your brilliant legal mind.
Well, if it wasn't for you
and your brilliant legal mind,
I might not be
in law school right now.
♪ ♪
No, I-I understand
that a lot of them already--
Okay, well,
if anyone wants to--
No, I see.
I see.
Maybe next year.
Bye.
Louis.
I need to talk to you
for a second.
What now?
Jack Soloff wants to know
if we'll someday consider
making him name partner.
Why the hell
would we do that?
Because I sent him
to poach a department
and instead
they offered him a job.
I get it.
Nobody wants to come here,
so your answer
is to give our in-house enemy
the promotion
he's always wanted.
Louis, you're the one
who wanted me to do it before.
And you talked me out of it.
Because you were right.
Just like you used to be right
about everything.
But now it seems like you're
wrong about everything.
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
I just heard back from
the last of those 20 schools.
And it turns out they have
a lot more in common
with Harvard that we thought,
because none of them
wants to do anything
to do with us
because our leadership sucks.
You watch yourself, Louis.
I don't need to watch myself.
I need to light a fire
under your ass.
Because our future
is slipping away,
and offering Jack
name partner
or praying to God
that Harvey
just gets Mike off the hook
isn't going to stop it
from happening.
Okay, Louis.
You want to do something
more than pray,
Harvey gets Mike acquitted,
then you get your ass back up
to Harvard
and you make sure Sheila
doesn't show up to that trial.
Hi, Donna.
Is there, um...
is there something
I can help you with?
I just wanted to say
that I'm sorry
about what happened
with the dean.
And I'm glad
that Mike took care of it.
Thank you.
I'm sorry that...
that I didn't come to you
with this whole thing,
but I-I...
They were pressuring you
to turn on Harvey
and based
on our last conversation,
you didn't think I was the right
person to talk to about that.
As usual, you're right.
Rachel, I got upset
because I didn't want to think
about what I do
if I have to choose
between my dad and Harvey.
Because this whole
situation sucks.
And we may have to make
hard choices,
and I want you to know
that no matter what you do,
you're my friend.
And I will always love you.
I will always love you too.
Thank you for coming.
I only came here
because I don't want you
or Mike Ross or anyone else
from this firm
showing up at my firm
ever again.
So what can I do for you?
I was thinking
about what you said
about me not admitting
things to myself
and I wanted to
talk to you about it.
Why?
I wanted you to know
the truth.
And what exactly
is the truth?
Our relationship didn't
end because of Mike.
It ended because I wasn't
ready to confront
what was wrong with me,
and I don't know
if I'll ever be ready,
but...
I've been seeing someone, and
I wanted to tell you about it.
And why does it matter
that I know that?
Because if I ever get out
of this in one piece,
I want to know if is okay
to call you again.
Harvey, it's always okay
to call me.
I've actually been going
to therapy myself,
and I don't know
where I'll be
when this whole thing
is over.
But I do hope that you get out
of this thing in one piece.
♪
Excuse me.
Hi, excuse me. I, uh--
I'm not sure if you know
who I am--
I worked here
for two months, Rachel.
I know who you are.
I just--I wanted to say
that I know
that you got caught
in the crossfire.
And I know how that feels.
And I just wanted to say
I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Rachel.
Have you thought about what may
happen when this is all over?
You mean if Mike
goes to jail.
I mean even if he doesn't.
What are you talking about?
Even if he is acquitted,
there is an excellent chance
he will be thrown
out of the bar
and never be able
to practice law again.
It wouldn't matter,
because Mike is prepared
to never practice
law again anyway.
And sometimes people think
they're prepared
and they're not.
I don't understand.
Rachel, Mike is going to
have to watch you do
what he dreams of doing, and
if he's anything like Harvey,
he probably thinks he can do it
better than you.
And there is a possibility
that he might resent you
for it.
I appreciate the advise.
But Mike is not like that.
Then I'm sorry
I overstepped my bounds.
Louis.
What are you doing here?
We've been over this.
There's nothing I can do--
I'm not here
about the associates.
I need you to take this.
- What's that?
- It's a ticket to Argentina.
I need you to go there
until the trial is over.
And why would I do that?
Because the prosecution has
no power to subpoena you there.
Let me get this straight.
You want me to flee the country,
so you can protect yourself.
I want you to flee the country
- Louis--
- Sheila, you take that stand,
and you're gonna say things
that hurt us,
which means Harvey is going
to say things that hurt you
and I will not be able
to handle that.
The truth isn't gonna
hurt me, Louis.
Isn't it true, Ms. Sazs,
that while you claim
no one had unauthorized access
to the Harvard file room,
there were times you were
derelict in your duties?
I've never been
derelict in my life.
Then how does that explain
the fact that there's a man
in this courtroom
that had unauthorized access
to that very room?
- Louis, please.
- Was it because you had
a relationship with that man?
A relationship
that ultimately failed?
- That's not--
- Relevant?
It's more
than goddamn relevant!
Because when he broke up
with you,
you started this vicious rumor
to get back at him.
That's a lie.
Those are all lies.
It is a lie that you had sex
with that man,
and left him alone
in the supposedly
impenetrable Harvard
file room?
Louis, this could
cost me my job.
Goddamn it!
Harvey is not gonna care.
No.
It's not a lie.
And if you did that
with him...
why should we believe
you didn't do that with others?
I'm sorry.
Sheila, I'm only trying
to protect you.
If you really wanted
to protect me,
you wouldn't tell Harvey
those things in the first place.
He's gonna want me
to tell him.
Anything I know
that would help.
You asked me
to not make you lie.
Please, don't ask me
to lie to him.
Okay, Louis.
I'll go.
♪
What are you
still doing here?
We've still got a trial
coming up.
I'm gonna make any headway
on my defense,
I need to get going.
Your defense?
Yes.
My defense.
Are you saying
what I think you're saying?
Because there's an expression
about that.
It says, "if you're
thinking it, you're a fool."
You heard her.
She said,
"the fact is that I'm not
a goddamn lawyer."
Well, the only way to change
that fact is for a jury
to see me being
a goddamn lawyer.
You try that,
all they're gonna see
is someone going to prison.
That's bullshit.
I can handle her.
You've never
even gone through
a criminal trial before.
Oh, yeah, and when was
the last time you did?
How many years ago was it?
I don't believe it.
You think you're better than me?
This isn't about
who's better.
It's about who's better
for this case.
And my life is on the line.
If I go down because
of my call, I can take it.
If I go down
because of yours, I can't.
This isn't just your life.
This is all of ours.
Well, like I said,
it's my call
and I'm making it.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
This isn't over.
I just finished going
through discovery
and we have a problem.
What is it?
They found Trevor.
♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net