Previously on Suits...
This is Harvey Specter.
He's our best closer.
Recruiting, your interviews
are set up for tomorrow.
I work better
alone anyway.
We only hire
from Harvard,
and you haven't even gone
to any law school.
What if I told you
that I consume knowledge
like no one you've ever met,
and I've actually passed
the bar.
Okay, hotshot,
fire up this laptop.
Stock option backdating.
Under IRC section 409a.
You forgot
about Sarbanes-Oxley.
Impressive, but you're sitting
at a computer.
Playing Hearts.
If you want to beat me,
you're going to have to do it
as something else.
How can you know all that?
Once I read something,
I understand it.
And once I understand it,
I never forget it.
I'm inclined
to give you a shot.
But if they find out I lied
about you going to Harvard,
they'll take away my license.
You what?
Not now, Donna.
The Harvard law school
alumni database.
I'm not saying
you won't get caught,
but it won't be because
your story doesn't check.
I'm Rachel Zane.
I'll be giving you
your orientation.
I love you.
Harvey's
your commanding officer.
However, Louis Litt,
he oversees all associates,
so you'll also answer to him.
Welcome to Pearson Hardman.
How many more chances
are you going to give that kid?
I didn't realize
we were keeping score.
But if that's the case, I still
think he's coming out ahead.
This habit of you empathizing
with every client--
it's not getting
you anywhere.
You need to deal in information
that can hold up.
- That's what a real lawyer does.
- Why?
- What?
- Fire me.
Why would you do that to me?
Life is this.
I like this.
It's tough to have a
relationship with a first-year,
or any year.
You're playing with me,
and you know it.
You kept flirting with me long
after you started dating her.
How about you find yourself
some other paralegal?
Because, as far
as I'm concerned, we're done.
How did you two meet?
I dated his best friend.
You always liked her.
Nothing happened
until Trevor and I were done.
- Never?
- Well, we did kiss once.
- I can't.
- It's a real firm.
But you can't tell
anyone ever.
This guy is not your friend,
he is an anchor
dragging you down.
Get rid of him.
He's my oldest friend.
I know you're seeing Jenny,
but I can't stop thinking
about the kiss.
I'm Trevor Evans.
I'm a friend of Mike Ross.
Yes.
I wish I didn't have
to do this.
There's something you need
to know about him,
something Harvey Specter
hasn't told you.
Nervous?
I'd be lying if I said no.
Well, I wouldn't
want you to lie.
- She knows.
- She can't.
She does.
What's holding
on my Swinton merger?
Are you kidding me?
We've been over this, okay?
If she knew, you'd know.
I do know.
The woman barely knows my name,
and she just summoned me
for dinner.
What is so funny?
Watson, Klyman, Gallo,
Goldberg, and Specter.
- Why are you naming--
- The last five senior partners?
Every one of us was taken
to dinner by Jessica
as a first-year.
And now she's taking you,
which means--
- This is a good thing.
- Exactly.
Oh, God.
- What now?
- What do I wear?
Wh-what do I say?
What do I wear?
We can discuss the prom
at recess.
Tell me what the hell's
holding up my Swinton merger.
Oh, it's just
a nuisance suit
that needs to be cleaned up
before we can clear escrow.
I'm all over it.
Why wasn't that
the first thing you told me?
Uh, I thought
I was getting exposed.
This is
a little less important.
My merger--
your panic attack.
Your compassion.
And I didn't have
a panic attack.
I had a legitimate reason
for concern.
Really? Why would she ask you
to dinner just to fire you?
I don't know. A little
movie called Goodfellas.
Did you see it?
Joe Pesci thought he was
getting made--he got dead.
That's your idea
of a legitimate reason?
"Karen!
Where's the money, Karen?"
- Go back to your cubicle.
- Hey, wait a minute. Do you--
do you think that I might get
an office out of this dinner?
A second ago, you thought
you were gonna get whacked.
Now you want an office?
What?
I'm adapting
to changing circumstances.
Huh. Well, maybe you won't be
the worst lawyer
in the history
of everything.
"Put the gun down, Karen.
Karen?"
They never checked.
What do you mean
"they never checked"?
The Internet was not
what it is today.
It was not so easy
to catch plagiarism.
God,
that's awesome.
Wait a minute.
If you graduated college then,
then that--
that would make you--
Old enough
to run my own law firm.
But you look so young.
- Well, you know what they say.
- Mm-hmm.
- True beauty is ageless.
- Black don't crack.
That's what I meant to say.
Uhhuh.
Well, enough about me.
I want to hear about you.
What was Harvard like?
I was three
when I realized
that I wasn't like
the other kids.
When school started,
it was like a joke.
I didn't take notes.
I never studied.
Every year
people would tell me,
"Next year
you won't get away with it."
Kept waiting for it
to get harder, but...
it just never did.
And Harvard?
I knew it would end.
I mean, it had to.
I thought, "Yeah,"
I'd finally found a place
where I'd be, uh...
exposed.
But it turns out, even
at the mighty Harvard Law--
You weren't the same
as the other kids.
- I know it sounds cocky.
- Not to me.
The fact is, you don't think
of yourself as smart.
You've always had your mind,
it just is what it is.
Yeah,
that's exactly what it is.
I don't think of myself
as smart, you know.
I just think
of everybody else as...
- Idiots.
- Not smart.
That's what
I meant to say.
Why the law?
It's kind of,
uh, personal.
Isn't that why
we're here?
When I was 11,
my parents were
on their way home from dinner,
and they were involved
in a really horrible accident.
And, uh, they--
my grandmother
took me in.
And it wasn't until I was,
uh, much older
that I realized
that we had a case.
See, it turns out
this restaurant...
they kept feeding
this Mr. Fenton drinks
long after they knew--
didn't matter.
I just--
I felt so helpless.
And I didn't want
to feel that way...
ever again.
Harvey was right.
About what?
I hope you brought
your checkbook.
Dinner's on you.
Wait.
What was Harvey right about?
- How was dinner?
- Free caviar.
What's not to love?
If you want to know
something about me,
you should have just asked me.
Why can't I just be getting
to know Mr. Ross
the way I got to know you?
Because if you're just trying
to get to know him,
you would have told me
about the dinner.
Something's going on,
and I want to know what it is.
An allegation
was made
that Mike Ross
never went to Harvard,
or any other law school
for that matter.
So I had him checked out.
Squeaky clean.
Graduated top
of his class.
So I took him
to dinner.
I wanted
to see what you saw in him
that makes him
so special.
And?
I get it.
He's a total package.
Maybe even the best
of both of us.
I hope this doesn't mean
you're gonna put me
in charge of recruiting.
Not to worry.
You are off the hook.
Harvey,
one more thing.
He might have
checked out clean,
but I know
that kid's full of shit.
Because there may be
a record
of him graduating
from Harvard Law,
but there's no record
of him graduating
from any college anywhere
on the face of the earth.
So I'm gonna give you
the benefit of the doubt
that you didn't know.
Because I don't want to do
what I would do if you did.
And what you're going to do is
fire that goddamn kid.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ all right
♪ all that time
imagine this ♪
♪ the greenback boogie
♪ Suits 2x01 ♪
She Knows
Original Air Date on June 14, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Donna, do me a favor
and get Mr. Sherman
on the phone, please.
Thank you.
- What was that?
- Excuse me?
"Please," "do me a favor,"
and "thank you,"
all in the same sentence?
You think
I'm not gonna notice that?
- I don't have time for this.
- You got time.
You're gonna sit right there
while I figure out
what the hell's going on.
Nothing's going on.
Dimple in your tie's
too far to the left.
That says that your mind
is on something else.
Mr. Sherman's called 136 times,
you've never called him back,
which means
you're feeling guilty
and you're trying to compensate.
I'm not trying to-
I didn't say
overcompensate.
As long
as we're clear.
The only time
I've ever seen you wear lavender
was when your brother
was in the hospital.
You're feeling protective
in an older-brother manner.
Whoa.
Either your mother's
somehow appeared in your life,
or Jessica found out
about Mike.
Oh, my God.
Does he know?
♪ Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
What's playing
on that thing?
Uh, audiobook.
Fall of the Roman Empire.
Ah. I was just rocking out
to Einstein's biography
this morning.
Ah.
See, I prefer
his acoustic stuff.
So you're
awfully chipper.
Maybe you got some good news?
Uh, yeah.
That led to an amazing dinner
with an incredible woman.
I'm really happy
to hear
things are going well
with you and Jenny.
Whoa, no.
No, no, no.
I was out with Jessica
last night.
Isn't she just
a little old for you?
Uh, I do okay
with the cougars.
You realize you're talking
about the managing partner
of the firm?
Please don't tell anyone
I said that.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna fire him.
How can you do that?
What do you want me to say?
If I don't, Jessica will.
What's up,
mother fleckers?
Wow. Oh, my God.
That's a beautiful day.
Hey, did you guys get that memo?
You know, the one about how...
I am the greatest.
What's wrong with you two?
Somebody die?
I'm gonna be outside.
"I'm gonna be outside.
I'm so serious.
All the time."
- Mike?
- Uh-huh.
Sit down.
No can do.
I've got too much energy.
I just wanted
to come and give you an update
on the Swinton merger.
Turns out
this woman thinks
that publishing stole one
of her book ideas.
Filed suit.
Listen.
Normally,
I'd suggest that we settle.
But then I got
to thinking.
WWHD--
what would Harvey do?
- Steamroll her.
- Exactly.
Which is what
I'm gonna do.
Myra Harrison is not gonna know
what hit her.
Why embrace
my philosophy now?
Come on.
Your merger--Myra Harrison.
Mike.
Sit down.
You okay?
I can't talk
right now.
Okay, just get it over with.
Tell me what happened.
The talk and the plan and
the whole "what I would do,"
is just whatever.
You couldn't do it.
I didn't do it.
You got overwhelmed
with a wave of emotion
you didn't see coming.
You cried, and you let him stay.
No.
I thought of the amount of work
I would have to go through
to replace him
and decided against it.
Did you see the amount
of work through a pool of tears?
- Are you finished?
- Can I get you anything?
Tissue? Glass of water?
Tampon?
Okay, wait a second.
You listen
to all my private conversations.
- So?
- This time you didn't.
- Yeah, I was busy.
- Busy?
That's what you're going with?
Very busy.
You didn't listen
because you couldn't listen.
Because you were
too overwhelmed with emotion.
I am not the topic
of conversation here.
Can I get you anything?
Tissue? Water?
I got it.
Harvey,
you said if you didn't fire him,
Jessica would.
So what are you gonna do?
Buy us some time.
Hey.
If you didn't
tell him anything,
why was he so dazed
when he walked out of here?
I told him
I was proud of him.
You need to give that boy
more encouragement.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Could you tell me
where I could find a copy
of James Jenkins'
latest book?
Um, right there
in new releases.
Oh, that's funny.
'Cause I have a complaint here
that says
that you're claiming
to have written his newest book.
Sorry, who are you?
My name's Mike Ross.
I represent Drecker Publishing.
I want to tell you
the story
of how your bullshit
lawsuit pans out.
Best case, you prove
that they stole your idea.
You know what?
It doesn't matter.
Because you signed
an employment agreement
giving Drecker Publishing
the rights
to all work product
that you create.
So the next step is that
my firm's going to assign
as many Mike Rosses as necessary
to dispatch your claim.
And after we do,
we're gonna add up
all of those hours,
and we're gonna petition
the court
to have you
pay for our work.
Now lucky for you, we happen
to be in the middle of a merger,
and you're kind of being
an inconvenience.
So I get to be the good guy
who comes down here
and strongly advises you to just
go ahead and give up now
and save yourself
a whole lot of money.
Anyway, that's all.
Thank you so much
for your time,
and have a nice day.
I bet your mother's proud
of you.
- Excuse me?
- You heard me.
Standing there
in your fancy suit
calling my story bullshit?
You don't even know what it is.
Ms. Harrison,
it's not my job to--
To what?
To care?
To be a human being?
To listen for two seconds?
I was an assistant
at Drecker for five years,
and I finally got an idea
for my own book.
And my boss,
who I thought was my friend,
encouraged me
to pitch my idea to her.
So I did.
And she took that idea,
served it up to James Jenkins,
and completely shut me out.
You have no evidence of this,
all right?
It's just your word
against hers.
That's not true,
my pitch was oral,
but I wrote a treatment
to prepare for it.
I can email you a copy.
Myra, wh--
what are you
looking for here?
These ideas aren't easy
to come by.
I might not have another one
in my entire life.
I just want to be paid
for my idea.
Finally get your big promotion
to file clerk?
For your information,
I happen to be compiling
a redundancy list
for the Swinton merger.
Well, while you're at it,
why don't you compile
a redundancy list
for the Swinton merger?
Instead of trying
to be hilarious,
maybe you can just close
the deal,
so then I can do my job
and determine which departments
get bashed in the head.
- What, are you killing seals?
- Would that it were.
Rodents of the sea.
Listen, I need you to lay off
Mike Ross for a while.
Oh, do you now?
Because he may be
your associate,
but as I've told you, like,
I don't know, a million times,
I run the associates.
I'm not disputing that.
It's just with Jessica's
new interest in him--
- What interest?
- Hadn't you heard?
- Heard what?
- Never mind.
No, tell me.
Tell me now.
Jessica took Mike
to dinner last night. Iago's.
Iag?
That's where she took me.
Really?
Oh.
Anyway, I'd consider it
a personal favor
if you'd just lay off Mike
for a few days,
but it's your call.
Hey.
Thanks.
What are you doing here?
Right now,
I want to know what's going on
with you and Rachel.
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
Jenny, how many times
do I have to answer this?
Excuse me?
Every day it's a new time
you don't trust me.
No, everyday it's
the same "I don't trust you."
You kissed her.
Tell me that's not true.
I--I didn't kiss her.
She kissed me.
- Like that makes a difference.
- It does, all right?
It happened,
but I didn't follow up on it.
And what
you're leaving out
is that even after
all that happened,
you asked me to choose,
and I chose you.
I asked you if anything
ever happened
between the two of you,
and you lied.
When you asked me that,
you weren't asking about a kiss,
and you know it.
I didn't lie,
I just answered the question
that you really asked.
Oh, you are such
a goddamn lawyer.
Oh, wait, that's right--
you're not.
All right, if kissing
someone else is so awful,
then what about you?
I seem
to remember you kissing me
when you were still with Trevor.
When I kissed you,
it was because you were the
person that I wanted to be with.
Obviously, that's how
you feel about Rachel.
That wasn't true!
Wasn't?
Well, I hope...
that you two
are really happy together.
I'm sorry.
You know,
you didn't ask me how I knew.
Trevor told me.
- What?
- Two days ago.
Right before he told me
that he was gonna tell
Jessica Pearson
that you're a fraud.
Well, if it isn't
the anointed one.
Where the hell
you been?
Well,
I'm not feeling very well.
I don't really care.
And I also don't care how
special Jessica thinks you are.
Because you still
answer to me.
And you're gonna do every piece
of work that I assign to you
until you don't.
Yeah, um,
I just have to see Harvey first.
Oh, no, no, no.
Harvey can't help you.
Now I want
the detailed listing
of every redundant position
in the Swinton merger.
And I want it yesterday,
capisce?
And get a mint, because
your breath is disgusting.
You drunk dialed him?
I didn't drunk dial him.
I called him.
Yeah, I left the room
for two minutes,
and you called him
after a glass of whiskey.
What would you call it?
Stupid.
So what did you say
on the message?
I said that I couldn't stop
thinking about our kiss.
- You kissed him?
- Yes.
- Where?
- On the mouth.
- Where did it happen?
- In the library.
- The Pearson Hardman library?
- No, the Library of Congress.
- Was John Boehner there?
- Are you gonna help me?
Or are you gonna
amuse yourself?
- I can multitask.
- Oh.
So what's the problem?
The problem is
I left him that message
three nights ago,
and he hasn't said anything.
I don't know
what to do.
Well, when a person
gets a message like that,
and they act like they didn't,
it's one of two things.
Either they got the message, and
they don't feel the same way,
or they didn't get
the message.
And who doesn't get
their messages?
He made his choice.
- Whoa.
- What?
I got to go.
- Okay.
- Wait a second.
How was it?
The kiss?
Good enough
to make me drunk dial him.
Well,
what are we talking about?
Jeremy Lin?
Yeah, I can make that happen.
You knew.
I got to go.
- When?
- Last night.
What are we gonna do?
We've got no choice.
We have to leave the country.
What?
I can get us two tickets
to Buenos Aires
and have the chopper
on the helipad in ten minutes.
Wait. She knows?
And you know she knows?
And you're joking about my life?
What the hell is wrong with you?
- Are you mad at me?
- No, I want to kill you!
Good, because if you're mad,
that means you're not panicking.
Now calm the hell down.
Okay, what did she say?
- She told me to fire you.
- That's not calming me down.
Haven't I taught you that
there's more than one response
when someone has a gun
to your head?
Right now there's
not even a gun in here.
No, no.
It's not in here.
It's out there roaming
the halls.
And when it sees me,
it's gonna start shooting.
Weren't you supposed
to give that plaintiff
the Harvey Specter treatment?
Yes.
- Did you wrap it up?
- I'm working on it.
That means you didn't give her
the Harvey Specter treatment.
So why don't you go do your job
and have some goddamn faith
that I'll do mine?
Donna, not now.
Oh, you're gonna want
to hear this.
What?
Alicia Hardman died
last night.
Hard
as in Pearson Hardman?
- Wife. Is it public yet?
- No.
When were you going
to tell me she knew, Harvey?
I wasn't.
- Jessica.
- Louis.
- How are you?
- Never better. You?
Top of the world.
- Did you need me?
- No.
But I do have something that...
will make you happy.
Oh. Fire away.
Well, as you know,
I've been compiling a list
of redundant departments
for the Swinton merger.
You should also think
about compiling a list
of redundant departments
for the Swinton merger.
That is awesome.
Anyway, I thought
you'd be happy to know
that I, uh,
assigned it to Mike Ross.
Excellent.
When?
Just now.
Harvey mentioned your dinner,
and I knew
that was an indicator
of you being very fond--
Louis, it's one
of the things I love about you.
You get me.
I do.
Yes.
Oh, I forgot something.
You go ahead, all right?
And Louis, thank you.
Sure.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Not here.
No.
You think I don't know
what you're doing?
I know you know what I did.
You baited Louis
into working with Ross,
so if he leaves abruptly,
Louis will
start asking questions.
I said I knew you knew.
Now you're just showing off.
You think I'm gonna
let you get away with it?
I think we've got bigger fish
to fry.
Alicia Hardman's dead.
Which means Daniel Hardman's
coming back.
You don't know that.
Yes, I do.
And so do you.
No, you're just using
this situation
to get Mike Ross out
of the crosshairs.
Need I remind you that
the only reason we were able
to get rid of the other half
of Pearson Hardman
in the first place
was by threatening
to tell her
about his affair?
That was the means,
not the end.
We had a good reason,
and you know that.
That's not my point.
Alicia's dead.
Our leverage is gone.
That was five years ago.
A lot can happen
in five years.
And what Daniel Hardman's
been doing
for the last five years
is dreaming of the day
he comes back
and screws us both
out of our jobs.
There's an easy way
to find out.
Then let's do it.
'Cause I can tell you this,
that asshole's coming back.
And he isn't coming because
he wants to be number two.
I got to say,
he looks good.
Being a prick
keeps you handsome.
Are you saying
that I'm handsome?
The fact that you think that
comment was directed at you
makes you self-centered and vain
at the same time.
Doesn't mean
it wasn't directed at me.
It was.
Which means
I'm also omniscient.
And handsome.
You left out arrogant.
You know, you and Daniel
are cut from the same cloth.
That's why
I don't like him.
"There can be only one."
We're at a funeral,
and you're quoting Highlander?
Yeah,
a lot of people die in it.
Seems appropriate.
You know the one key difference
between the two of us?
He's a lying snake
in the grass
who'll say or do anything.
Mr. Ross,
the truth is
I don't remember
where the James Jenkins pitch
came from.
Then it could have come
from Myra.
Well, it could have,
but it doesn't matter.
Even if I had stolen it, she
signed the employee agreement.
Which gives Drecker Publishing
the rights to her work product.
Yes, I know.
Well, then you also know
I'm not going
to taint my company's reputation
by giving Myra credit.
I'm not asking you
to give her credit.
I'm asking you
to give her compensation
in exchange for a confidential
settlement agreement,
which protects
your reputation.
That sounds
like blackmail.
Ms. Beckman.
This lawsuit
is the only thing
holding up
a billion-dollar merger.
And every day
that it drags on,
it's costing your company
more money.
What I'm talking about
is giving Myra Harrison
a crumb of a crumb.
So stop worrying
about what it sounds like,
and start writing a check.
How much
is it gonna cost?
That's what
I want to hear.
Just look at 'em.
Sycophants.
It makes me sick.
I'm not gonna stand in line
for the privilege
of kissing Daniel Hardman's ass,
and neither are you.
- It's a funeral.
- The man was a slave driver.
All he ever did was shit on me
and make me work long hours
for him.
I mean,
where was the kind word?
You know, the tiny gesture?
Yeah, I don't think so.
- To be fair, it's not--
- Zip it, I'm talking.
And then he just ups and leaves,
you know?
To take care
of his dying wife.
So?
I'm not waiting in line, okay?
I'm not gonna give the guy
the satisfaction.
What I meant was
now that she's dead,
does that mean
that he's coming back?
Actually, this line looks
like it's flowing.
And you're not com--no.
What is that?
- That's my, uh, cancer ribbon.
- No, I know what it is.
Why are you wearing it?
Well, I wanted to show
my support for Mrs. Hardman.
It's what she died of,
and I-I also had this aunt
that, um, she--
- $30,000.
That is a lot of money.
Yeah, it is.
It's as much as they've ever
paid for a freelance pitch.
But those people
also got credit,
which helped them sell
their next idea for more.
I thought you said
you were worried
you'd never have
another good idea.
Myra, this is-
this is the best deal
you're going to get.
I'm not exactly sure
that's true.
No, trust me,
it is.
You said you're
in the middle of a merger
and that
I'm an inconvenience.
I did my research.
It's a huge merger.
- I told you that to help you.
- You told me that to bully me.
- You only tried to help later.
- And I succeeded.
Which is why you have a check
for $30,000 in your hands.
Do you believe
that was my idea?
I know you do.
That's why you agreed to help.
- What's your point?
- My point is...
Lesley was my boss,
but I thought we were friends.
So when she asked me
to trust her, I did.
And she betrayed me.
Can you imagine
what that would be like?
Got to say,
up close, I feel bad for him.
Just don't forget
why we're here.
Daniel.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
Harvey.
My condolences.
Doesn't sound the same,
coming from you.
You have my sympathy
for your wife,
but I don't pretend
this is page one of the story.
You must think
I hate you both.
Well, that might have
something to do with the fact
that I was listening
the last time you spoke to me.
I was pissed,
wasn't I?
You threw your phone
at my head.
I did miss though.
That's because
you throw like a girl.
You're still angry, Harvey,
and I don't blame you.
But what you don't understand
is the last five years
have changed everything for me.
How so?
I reconnected
with Alicia.
I cared for her.
I know you can't get back
lost time with your family,
but you can make up
for it.
Look at Sarah.
I never really knew her,
and now I do.
Last time I saw her,
she was a little girl.
She just graduated
high school.
Going to Harvard,
this fall.
The truth is...
what you did to me
was the best thing
anyone could have done for me.
That mean
you're coming back?
It's my wife's funeral,
Harvey.
I haven't given it
any real thought yet.
I am a changed man,
Jessica.
And I have you
to thank for it.
You actually buying
that pious bullshit?
Not for a second.
He's coming for us.
I can stop him before
he even gets through the door.
I don't see how you're gonna
be able to do that.
I'll have
extra motivation.
- You want the kid to stay.
- Yes.
Like I said,
cut from the same cloth.
Make it happen.
You've got yourself
a deal.
Why haven't I been notified
that my merger's closing?
Uh, the plaintiff's refusing
to settle without credit.
What happened
to steamrolling her?
She realized that she's
in a unique position
to hold up the merger.
How the hell
did she realize that?
Oh, no, wait.
Don't tell me.
You fell in love with her,
and then you told her.
No, I did not fall
in love with her,
but... yeah,
I believe her.
- You're kidding me.
- What?
I'm fighting
for your job,
and you're gonna screw up
this merger?
- Are you?
- Am I what?
Fighting for my job.
Because if you're not,
this is gonna be my last case,
and I'm not sure
I want to go down
fighting for the wrong side.
What makes you think
I'm not fighting for you?
Mm, I don't know.
Your career--my anything.
Oh, you got a lot of nerve.
You have no idea
what I've been doing for you.
Maybe.
But you and I both know
you were gonna fire me
the other day, don't we?
Don't answer that.
I can see the look on your face.
It's the same look
I can see in here,
from that morning,
clear as a bell.
What I was going to do
and what I did
aren't the same thing.
Like the first day
I met you,
when you were gonna deal drugs
and you didn't.
Look, I can't tell you
everything that's going on here,
all right?
But you have
to trust me.
You are not getting fired
on my watch.
I trust you.
Then stop worrying
about what side you're on,
and take care
of that lawsuit.
Hey, Rachel,
do you have a minute?
- I need to--
- No, I don't.
Got your message
loud and clear.
- Wait. What?
- Look, I'm not mad.
I'm just in the middle
of a lot of work right now.
So if you're looking
for a friend, I--
I just really don't have
the time. Sorry.
What message?
You must really be
needing some love.
Why do you say that?
Those cookies are from
the Eisenhower administration.
You know...
sometimes--
sometimes I wish
I could go back.
To when?
Before... it.
When I was little,
I used to sit
with my grandmother
whenever I was upset.
A mother loves you,
but a grandmother--
Always on your side.
Do you remember
that time that I...
Ran away to your place?
You were so mad
they wouldn't let you stay up
to watch The Cosby Show.
I know.
It's so unreasonable, right?
But you were six.
You took me in,
told me that story--
the time you ran away
from your parents.
Yeah, I ended up getting found
by some dock workers
3 miles
from the house.
Yeah, that's the one.
- Never happened.
- What?
I just wanted to make you
miss your mom and dad.
I basically told you
Hansel and Gretel.
What? No.
It ends so differently.
I added
some touches.
You wouldn't have bought
me getting eaten
by the dock workers.
You were six,
you weren't an imbecile.
There is nothing new un--
under the sun.
What?
I suddenly feel
so much better.
Thank you.
Mwah!
Oh, and is there anything else
you haven't been telling me?
Like, am I from Krypton?
Possible.
Hi.
Harvey Specter.
I'm Sarah.
Um, I saw you talking
to my father at the service.
We used to work together.
Did you know my mom?
Not as well
as I would have liked.
Um, I was
just going out.
I need a walk.
Dad's just over there.
I'm sure he'll be happy
to see you.
I'm sorry
for your loss.
Thank you.
Will you excuse me
for one second?
- Mm-hmm.
- Thanks.
Harvey?
You brought food.
New York's finest.
You didn't want
to come empty-handed.
I didn't want to come here
at all.
But you want to make sure
I don't come back.
When we found out
about your little scam,
I wanted to go public.
Jessica said no.
Didn't want
to damage the firm's reputation.
She always was
a strategic thinker.
But you've been gone
a long time.
Now when we tell everyone
what you were up to,
our reputation will be fine,
yours won't.
As I said before,
I haven't decided
what the future holds for me.
And all your little threat
is doing is...
making me want
to come back.
When I was growing up,
I had a friend who found out
that his mother never loved
his father.
She cheated on him their
whole marriage, then left him.
He never forgave her.
If you come back,
here's what's gonna happen.
Your daughter's gonna find out
what kind man her father is.
Everything.
You think I won't do that?
I will.
Why are you doing this?
To protect my own.
Do us all a favor
and set up shop somewhere else.
It's done.
He won't be coming back.
Think I figured out a way
to get everybody what they want.
Well, that's good.
What's she doing here?
Well, she's here
to get what she wants.
Which is what,
exactly?
- Credit.
- That's all Myra's looking for.
So just admit that
you remember the pitch
and that you know
what you did.
I have no intention of doing
that because it's not true.
So you'd be willing
to take a lie-detector test
to that effect, then?
I most certainly
will not.
And I don't appreciate
being spoken to like this
by my own counsel.
Well, the thing is, Lesley,
that Myra's not the only one
who signed an agreement
with Drecker Publishing.
So did you.
And that agreement
gives them the right
to terminate you if you refuse
to submit to a polygraph.
And I happen to represent them,
not you.
I took it.
- Hmm.
- I was under the gun.
I was entitled to it,
so I took it.
You offered me advice,
and I trusted you.
She's threatened
by you, Myra.
Not a good choice
of mentor.
Now look,
you got the credit you wanted...
so sign the deal.
No, I want public credit.
Not credit in here.
This doesn't do me any good.
I thought you might say that.
Which is why I have spent
the last 24 hours
scanning the entire
Drecker Publishing catalog.
Robert Fallow,
Jonathan Daken,
and, my personal favorite,
Lester Collins.
Any one of them
could have been written
on the basis of your pitch.
But they weren't because they
were written years before it.
Are you saying
I plagiarized them?
I'm--I'm saying there's
nothing new under the sun.
Now I suggest you sign that deal
and go home.
Otherwise
we're gonna countersue
for plagiarizing your pitch
from our previous works.
But it's not true.
It's no less legitimate
than claiming
we stole something
you gave us the rights to.
And, more importantly,
it puts you over a barrel,
which is where you think
you have us.
Myra.
You want to be writer?
Then write.
But don't ever threaten me
or my firm again.
- You look happy.
- I am happy.
- Anything I should know?
- Welcome to Pearson Hardman.
Anything I should know?
Settled the case.
Merger paperwork's on the way.
You slammed the plaintiff?
- Oh, I slammed everybody.
- That's I like to hear.
When I ran Pearson Hardman...
I was charming, witty
and adorable.
I was also unscrupulous...
power-hungry and greedy.
I thought I could get away
with anything.
And that's exactly
what I tried to do.
I risked the firm's reputation
and the careers
of everyone in it.
These last few years
have humbled me.
And I've decided to come back
and show that we can be
a successful law firm
without breaking the rules.
Unfortunately,
the only way that I can do that
is by coming clean
about my past.
Because if we are busy hiding
what we have done...
it leaves us vulnerable
to anyone
who discovers our secrets.
And we become so consumed
with keeping them,
that it is a slippery slope
to doing even worse things.
While I was head of this firm,
I borrowed funds
from various escrow accounts.
The clients never found out
about it.
I paid back every cent.
But make no mistake,
I could have been convicted
of theft,
plain and simple.
I want everyone here
to know the kind of man I was.
And the kind of man I am.
Thank you.
Go home now.
Don't come back.
You and I
are gonna have a talk.
I understand why
you had Harvey do what he did.
But I'm not the same person.
And the only way
that I could think to prove it
was by doing
what I just did.
I told my daughter everything.
I hope we can figure out a way
to work together.
Didn't think you'd have
the guts to show up.
- What do you want?
- What do I want?
I want to know how my best
friend could do this to me.
Do what to you? Huh?
Betray you?
Go behind your back?
I stood there joking with you--
my friend, my buddy.
And my girlfriend was
in your shower, three feet away.
Hope you two
had a good laugh about that.
I was gonna
tell you, Trevor.
But you didn't.
And I wasn't gonna tell Jenny
about Rachel,
but I did.
How'd you even know
about me and Rachel?
You know what?
You're so smart,
you figure it out.
Okay, yeah, you got me.
Jenny broke up with me.
But you went to my boss.
You tried to ruin my life.
We're even.
990-36-7249.
It's your
social security number, right?
I saw it on your dad's desk
when we were in the sixth grade.
See, you think
that you can mess with my life,
and I can't mess with yours,
but I can.
The only thing
that's stopped me until now
is the fact
that I actually cared about you.
But now, after this,
I really don't give a shit
about you anymore.
You might not have my memory,
but you better remember that.
What the hell did you say
to Daniel?
Does it matter?
What matters
is I don't ever want
to see Mike Ross
in this office again.
- Well, that's not gonna happen.
- Excuse me?
I'm not firing him.
Then I'll fire him.
No, you won't.
You said you gave me
the benefit of the doubt
that I didn't know about Mike,
otherwise you'd fire me too.
Well, I knew.
You trying
to force my hand?
I'm trying
to stay your hand.
He goes, I go.
Pack up your things.
You're done.
There's only one problem
with that.
Daniel's coming for your job.
If I leave now,
he'll smell something's wrong,
he'll figure out what it is.
You'll look reckless
for letting me hire a kid
without a degree,
or foolish
for not knowing I did it.
Neither quality being an asset
in a managing partner.
Which makes you vulnerable.
All because you hired
the goddamn kid
in the first place.
Be that as it may,
he'll use it against you.
You need me.
And I'm not staying
without Mike.
Hey, Mike, it's Rachel.
I know I shouldn't be
doing this,
and I-I know
you're seeing Jenny,
but I can't stop thinking
about the kiss.
And... I can't go back.
- Hello--
- Get your ass in here.
On my way.
I thought--
Harvey said
he wanted to see me.
He said,
"Get your ass in here."
Am I fired?
You should be.
That imply that I'm not?
Not necessarily.
However, if I'm going
to accept this situation...
then I want to know everything
there is to know.
Okay.
Where do I start?
Why don't you tell me
how the hell you got Harvey
to hire you in the first place.
Fire up that laptop
and I'll show you.
Ask me anything there is
to know about the law.
That's how you did it?
You beat him?
Well, I'm not Harvey.
I don't need a computer.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net